<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="670">
   <yearpublished>1976</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>1</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>2</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>120</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>120</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>120</maxplaytime>
   <age>12</age>
       <name  sortindex="1">Robert Heinlein_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Starship Troopers</name>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">Starship Troopers</name>
         
   <description>Starship Troopers is based upon the popular novel of the same name written by the dean of science fiction writers, Robert A. Heinlein. In the novel, Heinlein describes a futuristic war involving homo sapiens from our Earth (Terrans) against a Humanoid race (nicknamed the 'Skinnies' for obvious physical attributes) and their cobelligerents, the totally alien Arachnids. Since this is a story of future wars and future advances in technology, much is changed in the fields of weaponry and tactics and strategy. One thing remains the same, however; the fighting still rests on the shoulders of the individual infantryman. Although great starships has shuttle men between the distant solar systems and the power of individual weapons has risen to awesome heights, wars still cannot be won unless men venture onto the face of alien planets and fight the enemy on their home ground. As Juan Rico, the protagonist of the novel, relates:_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;We are the boys who go to a particular place, at H-Hour, occupy a designated terrain, stand on it, dig the enemy out of their holes, force them then and there to surrender or die. We're the bloody infantry, the doughboy, the duckfoot, the foot soldier who goes where the enemy is and takes him on in person._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Although the mission remains the same, future inventiveness has changed the method considerably. In a galaxy-wide war, manpower is at a premium. Platoons fight where entire armies once tred. But these platoons possess the firepower equivalence of a Twentieth-Century mechanized division. More importantly, each man in the platoon is provided with a piece of hardware that allows him to fight and survive in the holocausts of future combat_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;mdash;his powered armor suit. As Rico describes it:_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;A suit isn't a spacesuit _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;mdash; although it can serve as one. A suit is not a space ship but it can fly_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;mdash;a little . . . Suited up, you look like a big steel gorilla, armed with gorillasized weapons. But the suits are considerably stronger than a gorilla. If a Mobile Infantry man in a suit swapped hugs with a gorilla, the gorilla would be dead, crushed; the man and the suit wouldn't be mussed . . . The real genius in the design is that you don't have to control the suit, you just wear it, like your clothes, like skin . . . Even riding a bicycle demands an acquired skill, very different from walking. But a suit you just wear._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;With the suit and the incredible array of weaponry that go with it, the Mobile Infantry soldier is an exceedingly formidable opponent. He had better be. The enemies he faces are the most awesome adversaries in the galaxy. Of the two extraterrestrial races fighting the Terrans, the Humanoids are the least revolting. Rico describes them as_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; . . . humanoid, eight or nine feet tall, much skinnier than we are and with a higher body temperature; they don't wear any clothes and they stand out in a set of 'snoopers' like a neon sign._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;In early scenarios they are fighting on the side of the Arachnids.  In later scenarios, after successful negotiations with Earth, they switch over to the Terran side. They're only effective fighters within the confines of their small city terrain and strong points on the board._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;But the 'Skinnies' were mild looking in comparison to the Arachnids:_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;The 'Bugs' are not like us. The Pseudo-Arachnids aren't even like spiders. They are arthropods who happen to look like a madman's concept of a giant, intelligent spider, but their organization, psychological and economic, is more like that of ants or termites; they are communal entities, the ultimate dictatorship of the hive . . . But don't make the mistake of thinking that they act purely from instinct . . . their actions are as intelligent as ours (stupid races don't build spaceships!) and were much better coordinated. It takes a minimum of a year to train a private to fight and to mesh his fighting with his mates; a Bug warrior is hatched able to do this ..._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;As the Arachnid Player, uses an Alien Control Pad sheet to record the placement of his underground central Hive cell complex and the attached tunnels radiating outward. Tunnels are used to move the Warrior units, along with Worker units mixed in as expendable decoys, to locations where they can pop up to the surface through a breach hole and attack the Terran units.  Completely unseen, and only paper recorded, Engineer units are used to create the breaches and, later, to extend the tunnels._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The game is set up in a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Programmed Instruction_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; system of scenarios to slowly introduce the game concepts. Scenarios range from Scenario I, which starts players off with a basic MI raid on a Skinny city (just like the book. _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Flores died on the way up_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;) to Scenario VII, The Battle of Klendathu: the final Terran assault on the Arachnid Homeworld._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Warfare in the Twenty-second Century is the ultimate test of survivability of the human race. It was a very near thing._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Avalon Hill Complexity rating - 5_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/QPwb3xhi2Zl43sbOxyzcWkFNnWE=/fit-in/200x150/pic3214.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/sTKRwLsE6eUp2rTmzaMtEfYnTwc=/0x0/pic3214.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamehonor objectid="10872">1976 Charles S. Roberts Best Tactical Nominee</boardgamehonor>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="5">The Avalon Hill Game Co</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="24877">First edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameartist objectid="20202">George Goebel</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="172962">GrogCast Season 3, Episode Uno!</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgameartist objectid="19">Richard Hamblen</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2026">Hex-and-Counter</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="103961">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! episode 47: Ignoble successes and serious SF games</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgameartist objectid="20204">Looking Glass Photographics</boardgameartist>
               <boardgameartist objectid="20203">Emily March</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1093">Novel-based</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="319">Randall C. Reed</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgameartist objectid="319">Randall C. Reed</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1016">Science Fiction</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2016">Secret Unit Deployment</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="5666">Solitaire Games</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="8164">Solitaire Wargames</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="61268">Starship Troopers: Canine Troopers</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
                      <boardgamesubdomain objectid="4664">Wargames</boardgamesubdomain>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="13">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="9" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="9" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="7" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="8">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="3" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="5" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="8">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>1106</usersrated>
     <average>6.4685</average>
     <bayesaverage>5.93365</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="2485" bayesaverage="5.93365" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="4664" name="wargames" friendlyname="War Game Rank" value="624" bayesaverage="6.28781" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.42604</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>3214</owned>
     <trading>207</trading>
     <wanting>50</wanting>
     <wishing>165</wishing>
     <numcomments>541</numcomments>
     <numweights>134</numweights>
     <averageweight>3.097</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Oct 2004 17:18:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 05 Jun 2005 19:33:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, unplayed. VERY light shelf wear. All components pristine, includes:
Rulebook
3 map boards
1 6-sided die
1 chart/table sheet
2 counter sheets, unpunched
1 pad of control/record sheets, unused
Vintage AH promo materials</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 02 Feb 2005 06:32:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Apr 2005 14:08:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is punched, but no pieces/components are missing or damaged.  Game pieces are stored neatly in clear plastic storage tray. Gamebox shows some scuffing, but is completely intact.  Control/record pad is nearly complete.  Shipping rates are available upon request.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 19 Mar 2005 01:26:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 22:47:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>22</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Roughly half punched with plenty of log pads, good condition</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 13 May 2005 20:12:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 25 Sep 2005 14:01:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>english version +++++ will be shipped with insurance +++++ payment for germany : personal pick up in berlin or bank transfer +++++ payment for usa, canada, asia and australia : paypal or cash (by letter, exchanged already into euros) or bank transfer +++++ payment for european countries, that have no euro : paypal or cash (by letter, exchanged already into euros) or bank transfer +++++ payment for european countries, that have euro : direct bank transfer (wich is cost-free !) or cash (by letter) +++++ for all : no checks ! +++++ foreign buyers beware : german postal sadly is very expensive for foreign packages (about 18 - 45 euros, it depends on, where the package has to be shipped or what´s it´s weight), pleask ask for prices, before you buy !) +++++ shipping inside germany will cost 8 euros</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 27 Jul 2005 06:57:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 20 Mar 2006 20:33:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>unpunched and in great condition...  box is solid but slightly dented and worn from storage.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 17 Aug 2005 00:47:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 Oct 2005 02:52:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>9</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Components are complete and in very good condition.  Counters are punched and separated into bags.  Box has minor to moderate shelf wear. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 14:33:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 18:37:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>19.99</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 28 May 2006 03:36:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 08 Sep 2006 02:27:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The box is scuffed but otherwise everything is present and in good condition.  Many of the counters have not yet been punched out.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 21:55:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 12 Jan 2007 18:59:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Only been played a handful of times.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 08:37:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Jun 2007 13:33:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Game is 100% complete.  Box has some wear and tear.  Front of box has taken some sort of hit at some stage. (see photos)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 12:15:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 01:03:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>21</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Based on the classic sci-fi novel.  Man vs. monster.
This copy is UNPUNCHED and has NEVER BEEN PLAYED.  There is a bottom corner of the box lid wherein a very small piece of the paint has peeled away, but the box is fully intact.
Other than that one slight defect, everything is in EXCELLENT condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 08:46:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 19:43:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Purchase by auction reserved for Harvey O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;Brien
1976 Vintage Avalon Hill Bookshelf game.
Contents complete _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; only partially punched.  3 game boards.  7 sheets from the pad have been used.  Occasional highlighting on rules _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; table.  
Box is solid but shows shelf wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 23:20:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 08:22:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>In good condition with counters bagged. Will include 53 pages of articles on the game from Ah_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s General magasine and the board gamer.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 07 Dec 2007 18:27:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:35:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is partially punched. A little yellowing on the Terrain Chart. Box is solid.
Outside US PayPal only.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:43:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 May 2008 20:21:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>63</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>new and unpunched !!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 15:40:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 16:48:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>13</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Some chits are punched, the majority are not and all seem to be there by count.  Everything else is in great condition, with the box showing a little compression. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 22:45:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 19:59:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Completely Unpunched!!!  Box is sold with no torn corners.  100% complete.
Paypal ID - jatwood@putnamcityschools.org
Will ship same day.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 18:07:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 09:31:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Everything present, some unpuched units.  Bonus:  Vol 15 Number 1 of the General magazine with mission scenarios for the game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 03:10:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 05:03:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>8.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>100% complete and very clean copy of STARSHIP TROOPERS!
Game appears to have never been played, the Alien Control Pad is unused. Box shows very little wear with no corner tears.
All my games are priced under the listed Avg. selling price on BGG Price Competitor! Please check my other games and I will combine shipping.
Great Find of a Great Game! If your are at all interested, please e-mail me for more pictures.
Paypal Id is jatwood@putnamcityschools.org Credit Cards Accepted.
Flat Shipping 11.50</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 21:24:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 20:37:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>27.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>CONDITION: Excellent condition overall, contents mint, unused and complete, with unpunched counters. The box has some wear and creasing and a split corner.
POSTAGE COST:
UK postage:  £5.50
European Postage: £10.50
Rest of World Postage: £21.00
Any buyers in and around London are welcome to collect in person (cash on collection).
COMBINED SHIPPING:
I will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.  Please note that it is NOT always cheaper to combine shipping on games outside the UK due to the weight limit of 2KG on the Small Packet service. As a rough approximation, outside the UK it is usually cheaper to combine 5 or more games, while 4 or less are best sent individually.  This depends entirely on the specific games - please contact me before buying if you wish to purchase multiple games so that I can give you an accurate shipping cost.
ABOUT ME:
I have been playing and collecting games for over 25 years and I also sell games and magazines on ebay with the same username (saabdastard) where I have a 100% positive rating and a feedback score of over 4000. I am a verified PAYPAL Premier account holder (since 2004), with over 650 PayPal Verified Buyers.
SELLERS TERMS AND CONDITIONS:
PAYMENT TERMS: 
Please wait until you receive my invoice before sending payment. 
Payment is due within 5 days of the date you receive my invoice. 
Please do not purchase if you do not intend to pay, or cannot pay within this time frame.
PAYMENT METHODS: 
UK buyers may use PayPal, cheque or cash-on-collection.
Overseas buyers MUST USE PAYPAL only.
SHIPPING:
Buyer is responsible for all shipping costs. Europe and Rest of World rates shown above are for Airmail. Surface Mail rate to Rest of World is available if you wish (same as Europe Air rate), but Surface Mail to Rest of World can take up to 2 months!  There is no real difference between Air and Surface rates for Europe.
INSURANCE:
Insurance is optional on all items, unless noted. Failure to take out optional insurance limits my liability for loss or damage in the mail to the amount automatically covered by Royal Mail (currently £39 per package for Small Packets, £150 for International Standard).
CUSTOMS:
Buyers outside the EU are responsible for all Customs charges applicable to their country.
RETURNS:
New Unopened items may be returned for a refund of the purchase price of the item, excluding shipping charges, within 7 days of the delivery date. All returned items must be in the original packaging and in the condition that they were shipped to you.
Defective or damaged items can be returned for an exchange or refund within 7 days of the delivery date. All returns require authorization from me BEFORE returning the item.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 24 May 2009 10:06:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 12:38:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box lid split and taped at one corner.
Game components very good - unpunched
Shipping to UK destination  £6.50</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 02:03:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 07:40:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>13</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 17:53:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 01:05:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 16:51:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 21:33:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Sarissa _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Flamberge Support Missiles: Two Mobile Infantry Missiles
For auction winner: runescience</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 05:18:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 17:58:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>19.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box shows just a bit of wear. Only part of the counters punched. Game has hardly been played.
Shipping at actual cost dependent on destination, total weight and method of shipment chosen.
Usually shipping a single (regular sized) board game (surface) costs 12.90€ worldwide and 8.60€ within Europe. Smaller games ship cheaper. Of course multiple games can be combined.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 14:04:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:57:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, components in mint condition. The box lid has a little wear and paper bubbling. Includes 1982 AH parts list.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 19:26:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 22:00:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12.5</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>The box corners are torn, but the game is complete and in nice shape.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 03:33:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 03:03:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12.5</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>The box has some wear and the box lid is torn at the corners.  The game itself is in good condition, with all the counters neatly bagged.
I generally give a couple of shipping options and charge my cost rounded up to the next quarter.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 21:27:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 08:17:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>12</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Starship Troopers by Avalon Hill
Box intact but worn 
Contents in excellent condition (counters pucnched)
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 19:02:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 15:37:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>minor box wear.
one corner split
punched sorted and bagged.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 19:37:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 05:47:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>100% complete, box shows some wear, components are excellent!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 19:13:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 02:00:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Starship Troopers (1976) from Avalon Hill
Box: Moderate to heavy shelf-wear with several dings, dents, and wrinkles. Three corners of the top and one corner of the bottom have been repaired with clear tape. If you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re looking for a beauty contest-winner, look elsewhere; this box is fucntional and does its job just fine, though.
Contents: The original 6-sided die is missing (I can supply you with one if needed) but all of the other components are here and in new, unplayed condition. The chits are all on the sprues (with the exception of two that fell out - a couple more may come loosed while in transit). Everything is in very nice shape!
SHIPPING
U.S. shipp
ing will be via USPS Priority Shipping and based on a weight of 4 Lbs. International buyers are very welcome, but please contact me for a shipping price quote to avoid any surprises or misunderstandings.
I will gladly combine shipping for multiple purchases. The final cost will be based on the total weight, but be aware that large packages that are shipped more than a certain distance accrue a large surcharge, so combining shipping may not save any money.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 14:15:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 02:38:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box wear to corners and edges with minor surface tears. Components are in excellent condition, with chits sorted and bagged neatly, flat board, and a 95% complete pad of game sheets. 
Buyer will pay to ship by discounted FedEx Ground with insurance and tracking provided for free IF you have a non-residential address to ship to (this is guaranteed to save at least $2-3 over USPS). Otherwise, it will cost a bit more, and shipping will be by USPS Priority with Delivery Confirmation.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 12 Jun 2010 12:54:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 09:45:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Excellent, light box corner wear, partially unpunched, unplayed. Two sheets are loose from the pad, but the contents are pristine.
I will throw in some mini-zip baggies for sorting bits when you get the game. How_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s that for service, lol?
I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll ship via USPS Priority Flat Rate Box with Delivery Confirmation, unless you have a non-residential address and want to save a few bucks. In that case, I will use FedEx Ground with $100 insurance and tracking included for free.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 01:55:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 15 Oct 2010 01:20:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Counters unpunched. Log pad complete.  Box in very good condition with only minor wear on corners.  I charge only exact shipping costs.  Will ship outside US but will add confirmation charge to postage to verify its arrival. Payment by PayPal.  Any questions, please don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t hesitate to ask.
Thanks.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 17:13:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 02:26:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>For alvae64</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 05:37:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 14:56:14 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14.95</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Components including the mounted game boards, counters, carts, and rules are in excellent condition. Box is solid but has moderate shelf wear on top. I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and I package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly - within 24 hours of receiving payment. Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 21:56:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 03:57:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Partially and complete. Box a bit shopworn but good to very good.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 03:05:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 03:15:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for Jim Horvath.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 02:18:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 14:29:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box has minor scuffing, components complete and in great condition!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 10:18:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 16:17:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For Shedding for the wedding auction winner Andy Foulke.
$10 bid plus shipping cost. Paypal e-mail  eternallove79@juno.com
Thanks</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 15:25:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 16:51:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>8</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>THIS GAME IS FOR SPROUTGRRL ONLY!
FROM A GEEKLIST AUCTION.
Thanks!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 21:06:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 15:30:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched. Includes articles from The General.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 08 May 2011 17:21:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 06:35:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Some counters are punched but game has never been played.
Minor Damage to the box but components are in perfect condition.
Within Germany money transfer preferred .
Feel free to ask for further information.
Shipping costs depending on buyer Location please ask before buying.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 30 Jun 2011 14:31:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 19:26:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game in original shrink wrap 
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling - Priority Mail excl. Insurance: 
Switzerland: CHF 10.-- 
Europe: USD 41.--
US/ Canada: USD 48.--
Others Overseas: USD 52.—
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 15:45:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 10:50:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game in original shrink wrap 
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling - Priority Mail excl. Insurance: 
Switzerland: CHF 10.-- 
Europe: USD 39.--
Others Overseas: USD 53.--
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 01:29:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 19:44:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is mostly unpunched (a few counters have fallen from the spures) and 100% complete. I bought it years ago and have not gotten around to playing it and probably wont. It needs a good home. I like to ship in a USPS flat rate box so shipping will be around $14 in the US, $26 to Canada.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 02:09:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 11:22:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>First Edition.  Unpunched.  Box in like new condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 23:12:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:15:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Auction item
Reserved for Username: dochogan
Shipping is USPS Medium Flat Rate box</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 00:03:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 02:11:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for MisterG.
Shipping and handling is $11.00, for a total of $21.00.
PayPal payment can be sent to themilkcrate@hotmail.com</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 22:11:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 29 May 2012 15:41:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Starship Troopers (1976) from Avalon Hill
Box: Moderate shelfwear with multiple dings, dents, and creases, including several areas where the top layer of box paper was pulled off during tape removal. Overall the box is in good but not great condition.
Components: Complete and in excellent condition! Pieces have been sorted and stored in plastic bags for convenience and protection - you will be very pleased with how the game has been packaged. 
SHIPPING:
U.S. shipping will be via USPS Priority Shipping and based on a weight of 4 Lbs. from zip code 85208. International buyers are very welcome, but please contact me before buying for a shipping price quote to avoid any surprises or misunderstandings.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 16:10:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 May 2014 13:23:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game in original shrink wrap 
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling - Priority Mail excl. Insurance: 
Switzerland: CHF 10.-- 
Europe: USD 37.--
Others: USD 52.--
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 19:47:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 01:03:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39.95</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Game is opened but the components are in like new condition, the game is unpunched.
Will ship in medium US Priority Mail flat-rate box.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 15:56:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 12 May 2012 21:26:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>27.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>CONDITION: Excellent condition overall, contents near mint, unused and complete, with unpunched counters. The box has some wear and creasing, a couple of small tears on one side and a split corner.
POSTAGE COST:
UK postage: £6.50
European Postage: £13.00
Rest of World Postage: £24.00
Any buyers in and around London are welcome to collect in person (cash on collection).
COMBINED SHIPPING:
I will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible. Please note that it is NOT always cheaper to combine shipping on games outside the UK due to the weight limit of 2KG on the Small Packet service. As a rough approximation, outside the UK it is usually cheaper to combine 5 or more games, while 4 or less are best sent individually. This depends entirely on the specific games - please contact me before buying if you wish to purchase multiple games so that I can give you an accurate shipping cost.
ABOUT ME:
I have been playing and collecting games for over 25 years and I also sell games and magazines on ebay with the same username (saabdastard) where I have a 100% positive rating and a feedback score of over 4000. I am a verified PAYPAL Premier account holder (since 2004), with over 650 PayPal Verified Buyers.
SELLERS TERMS AND CONDITIONS:
PAYMENT TERMS:
Please wait until you receive my invoice before sending payment.
Payment is due within 5 days of the date you receive my invoice.
Please do not purchase if you do not intend to pay, or cannot pay within this time frame.
PAYMENT METHODS:
UK buyers may use PayPal, cheque or cash-on-collection.
Overseas buyers MUST USE PAYPAL only.
SHIPPING:
Buyer is responsible for all shipping costs. Europe and Rest of World rates shown above are for Airmail. Surface Mail rate to Rest of World is available if you wish (same as Europe Air rate), but Surface Mail to Rest of World can take up to 2 months! There is no real difference between Air and Surface rates for Europe.
INSURANCE:
Insurance is optional on all items, unless noted. Failure to take out optional insurance limits my liability for loss or damage in the mail to the amount automatically covered by Royal Mail (currently £39 per package for Small Packets, £150 for International Standard).
CUSTOMS:
Buyers outside the EU are responsible for all Customs charges applicable to their country.
RETURNS:
New Unopened items may be returned for a refund of the purchase price of the item, excluding shipping charges, within 7 days of the delivery date. All returned items must be in the original packaging and in the condition that they were shipped to you.
Defective or damaged items can be returned for an exchange or refund within 7 days of the delivery date. All returns require authorization from me BEFORE returning the item.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 04 May 2012 01:58:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 04 May 2012 04:54:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is for auction winner pendragon714.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 19:38:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 08:00:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.99</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched and complete!
I ship fast and can combine shipping</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 11:19:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 11:16:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>A brand new unused, unopened, and undamaged game in perfect condition. The original packaging and all materials are in brand new condition with the exception of the shrink wrap which is missing on the top left front corner and also has a small 1cm tear on bottom of box (refer photo).
All reasonable offers will be considered.
Delivery charges:
Within the UK - Recorded (Signed For) First Class stamps including full insurance £8
Outside of the UK - please geekmail before purchasing to determine the delivery charge.
Buyer responsible for all Customs charges.
Buyer is responsible for all shipping costs, postage for Europe and the rest of the world is by airmail with delivery confirmation/tracking.
I can combine multiple purchases to reduce shipping costs where possible.
UK buyers can send a personal cheque or use PayPal and add and additional 3.9% (unless the funds are sent as a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;Gift_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; under the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;Personal_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; tab rather than _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;Purchase_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; tab in PayPal).
Buyers outside the UK must use PayPal.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 17:54:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 08:08:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>23.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For xispo only (price reduced to $23.99 from $29.99 due to bump on box corner).
Game is complete, unpunched and in excellent condition.  Includes an extra punched counters (mostly Arachnid).
Game box has a ding on the bottom right corner (not broken) and box shows light to moderate shelf wear.  Overall in good to very good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 00:42:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 01:14:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for user Funbelievable</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 23:43:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 08:07:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched and sorted, played only a few times</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 02:11:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 06:03:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>game is complete and in good condition.
i carefully counted all the counters.
the game is only partially punched.  some counters still on the sheet, the rest are bagged.
box has minor shelfwear.
i accept payment via paypal only.
shipping costs are added after purchase.
feel free to message for a shipping estimate.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 18:18:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 07:39:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Player_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s copy still in good condition. Pad still fairly full.
Shipping charges paid by the buyer. Combined shipping  available. Please let me know if you wish for the shipment to be insured.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 05:35:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 00:22:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>12</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Game components complete and in good (but used) condition except that one unimportant radiation counter is missing.
 Game box is poor, split and taped at corners.
Shipping to UK destination £7</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 04:40:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 21:52:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Contents are unpunched but box has tear down edge</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 07:48:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 16:10:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, contents excellent, minor wear and tear on box due to age.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 25 May 2013 12:37:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 May 2013 01:15:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>12</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>A classic game, i haven_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t played it much though (not the wife_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s cup of tea so to speak). Can be send internationally.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 14 Jul 2013 04:15:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 10:35:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>44.94</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.  Contents verified complete and in excellent condition.  Mapboards are crisp and fresh.  Countersheets in excellent shape.  Box is square and straight with 4 tight corners.  One small doink on the back of the box.  Some shelf wear.  Worldwide shipping and will be packed well.  All forms of negotiable instruments considered.  Combine ship with multiple purchases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 17:31:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 22:47:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is 100% complete and in excellent condition. Maps and counters are in mint condition.  There are lots of alien control pads included.Rule book and tables are in very good condition.  Box is in very good condition with one split corner and average shelfwear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 20:47:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:10:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>(near) mint. Payment by Paypal, Moneybookers or bank transfer.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 20:12:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 03:09:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Game is still in shrink, though box shows a little sign of shelf wear.
Expected postage and packing to UK is £7.50 (1st Class), Europe (EU) is £10 (up to five day delivery) and USA is £16 (delivery aim is five days). Please let me have delivery address details when buying the game and I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll confirm exact postage and packing costs.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:09:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 20:31:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Partially punched. Some box wear and one corner of box top torn. Otherwise excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 23:26:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 13:41:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For user kaufmad only for his auction win.
Box has shelf wear but is structurally sound. 50% punched and bagged. Appears complete.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 13:26:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 03:22:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 14:27:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 26 May 2014 16:55:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>1/4 sheet punched and clipped, others unpunched, great condition, near mint.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:22:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 25 May 2014 04:25:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Game is partially punched and is missing 1 generic WIA (Wounded in Action) counter.  (I verified the counters based on images of unpunched counter sheets on BGG.)
Box in fair condition.  It has some shelf wear, tape marks, minor dishing, etc.
The board, rules, Alien Control pad, and players aid chart are in good condition.
Buyer to pay shipping.
Please let me know if you have any questions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 31 May 2014 22:41:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 14:43:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>RESERVED FOR SquadronROE
Starship Troppers for $15 plus $10 for shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:40:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 16:04:27 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>PREWAR TROOPERS: Magazine with variants that adds canines (not neodogs), and 2 solitaire prewar scenarios. (Overseas shipping = $6.00, Canada = $3.50)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 22:54:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 11:32:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>The box is a bit damaged.
The counters have been reinforces with thick cardboard and plastic film.
Everything is a bit glossy.
Outside that, it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s complete and fully playable.
The shipping cost is 10 euros in France, 17 euros in The European Union and 36 euros everywhere else</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 05:14:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 12:59:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Possibly the best copy I have ever seen!  Unpunched with all promotional material that was originally in it, the Bug movement pad is as new.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 23:55:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 01:49:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/189432/item/3820808#3820808]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;My Third Auction - Buy My Crap Pt. 3 - Return of the Crap (1ish Hour Left)_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 00:10:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 22:38:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Tiles are intact. Never been played.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 19:41:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 13:49:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Mint condition game in great shape.  Contains some facsimile variant counters by Richard Gutenkunst, from an old General article.  Buyer to pay flat rate medium box rate.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 11 May 2015 18:37:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:43:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched.  Components in good shape.  Box has some wear and dishing</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 19:48:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 01:52:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>My late husband was an avid board gamer/collector.  All his games have been well taken care of,  most of them never even played.  All were stored in a non smoking household.  If the game was played, no food or drinks were allowed by the games.  Hopefully I will be able to find good homes for all his beloved games.  If you have any questions or concerns, please don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t hesitate to ask</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 00:56:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 19:01:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.  Plus some articles copied from the General Magazine included.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 12:54:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 21:18:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched
Box corner taped
Most of the Alien Control Pad sheets unused</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 18:04:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 18:31:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Auction win for Chapel - MWChapel</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 23:33:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 01:55:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/198350/item/4222993#4222993]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;[US only] Big Auction - Too Many Games Not Enough Money - Part 3 [Lobster Trap]_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 02:29:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 23:05:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 19 May 2013 16:34:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 20:14:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Shipping costs Germany:    4,50 €
Shipping costs Eurozone:   9,00 €
Shipping costs worldwide: 16,00 €
Payment via PayPal or bank transfer
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 01:18:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 10 May 2016 13:10:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This copy of Starship Troopers is in excellent condition.  It was only played a few times; only 70 of the 504 counters have been punched out of the counter sheets! All components are present - instructions, planning sheets, etc. The game boards are in perfect condition. The box is sturdy and sound but has some minor cosmetic shelf wear. Happy to provide pics on request.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 19 May 2016 10:39:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 26 May 2016 22:17:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/208660/item/4623969#4623969]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Geekway to the West 2016 Virtual Flea Market_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction. For Craigc only
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 09 May 2013 10:23:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 15:36:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All counters present and in counter trays.
Boards covered in plastic.
Rules used and worn.
Everything present.
Box worn.
One of my 1st wargames - heavily played!
I do come to the UK every couple of months and can post this game from there. For UK buyers this would obviously be cheaper.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 15:39:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:07:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>ONLY FOR DIGNAN
This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/214798/item/4982390#4982390]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Virtual Flea Market for Delivery to BGG.Con 2016_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 19:49:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:16:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>game is complete
G</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 10:39:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 22:07:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched. Components as-new. Light shelf wear to box.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 18:33:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 20:03:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 21:34:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 10:09:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Has had a fair bit of play and love.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 22 May 2017 21:24:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 05:26:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Shipping is additional</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:27:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 18:46:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Buyer pays UPS from 17602</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 00:45:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 14:43:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Original owner, smoke free and dry home. Priority mail or usps parcel depending on distance from NY state.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 06:07:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 22:13:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, unplayed.
SHIPPING: Buyer pays shipping costs. I prefer to ship by USPS Flat Rate Priority Mail if the games will fit into one of their boxes or envelopes, but will ship otherwise upon request. 
If you wish to buy several games at once, please let me know via geekmail so I can pack them together and perhaps save you some postage.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 18:16:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 08:25:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>44.9</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Language: english
Publisher: Avalon Hill
Game Condition: Played Once
Box Condition: Minor Wear
Availability: Now Available
ID Gis: 18282 (for reference)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:39:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 16:51:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box is used inside verry good</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 22:32:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 13:01:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>mostly unpunched. Played (solo) once.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 19:33:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 09:27:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>45</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Never played. 10 euros for shipping in Italy, everywhere else ask me for a quote</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 05:34:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 06:51:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>9</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>punched</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 15:37:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:07:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Game is like new box is in excellent shape. Game has never been played.  Comes from a smoke free home.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 05:39:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:06:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>unpunched, fine box (pictured) plus General feature issue V13n6 and some aftermarket variant counters (about 2 dozen) purchased from a 3rd party seller</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 10:26:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:06:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Played, but complete.
BONUS: includes a bound copy of all the published add on rules plus homemade counters for all new units!!!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 11:08:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:09:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is the 1976 Avalon Hill board game of _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Robert Heinlein_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Starship Troopers_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;.  There is some shelf wear to the box; the contents are complete, and apparently unplayed.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 21:31:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 14:27:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Counters unpunched, minimal shelf wear</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:34:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 12:01:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box is undamaged and shows very  little wear and tear.  Counters are punched out, corner clipped and sorted into ziplock bags.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 19:16:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 05:10:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game itself is unpunched an in excellent condition. Box has some dishing.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 07:09:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 18:36:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>36</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>unpunched, fine box (pictured)  some aftermarket variant counters (about a dozen) purchased from a 3rd party seller</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 04:00:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:07:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Contents in good condition.  Box has moderate to heavy shelf wear, no splits.
Missing 5 of 504 counters:
Mobile Infantry Marauders - 2 of 84
Arachnid Warriors - 1 of 50
Strong Point - 1 of 14
Breach - 1 of 21
Blank counters are present as well.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 22:35:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 02:16:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>In bestem Zustand und komplett. Versand innerhalb Deutschlands 6 Euro. 
In perfect condition and complete.  Shipping within Europe is 15 Euros.
If you have to insist on Paypal, pls add 8% to the game and shipping costs. I do prefer bank transfer however.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 02:49:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:36:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Counters are punched, all components are like new.  Box has a crease in one corner and one split end.
Game was stored in a dry, pet free, smoke free home.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:26:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 02:07:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28.44</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is in good shape, and for the most part, the counters are UNPUNCHED. There_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s a small tear at crease of one mapboard that is pictured. Box is scuffed, but corners are intact. Pad 75% full.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 15:35:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 05:04:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>7</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>***** THIS IS NOT THE BOXED GAME *****
This is a CD with the entire game in PDF form as well as a copy of The General, Vol. 13, No. 6
Feel free to look over my entire BGG collection as nearly everything can be available for purchase and discounts may be available if multiple items are purchased at the same time.
PayPal accepted with Verified Account/Verified Address.
USPS Money Orders accepted.
Personal checks accepted only if drawn on BB_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T bank.
Collectibles, easily damaged or higher value items require insured shipment.
Please ask for more information or images if you have a particular question or concern about a game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 02:17:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 19:25:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Counters are unpunched, all components are like new.  Box does have a few bubbles in the paper on the box and a crease in one corner.  Box has some shelf wear.
Game was stored in a dry, pet free, smoke free home.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 23:29:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 22:31:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>bought used never played</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:51:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 07:57:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete. Counters sorted and stored in 4 ziplock bags.
The box is in good condition. It has some shelf wear. 
Includes translation in Italian.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 17:57:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 13:21:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Some scuffing of the box.  Counters are punched.  Overall condition is excellent, especially for a game of this age.  Includes a photocopy of the solitaire rules.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 15:19:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 17:13:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>59.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Condition: Scuffed on top and sides of cover. </notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
