<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="1561">
   <yearpublished>1988</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>3</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>10</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>60</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>60</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>60</maxplaytime>
   <age>8</age>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">Clue Master Detective</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Cluedo Master Detective</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Super Cluedo</name>
         
   <description>This is the same as the basic Clue game, but with more of everything._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The publisher's description:_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Was it Madame Rose in the Carriage House with the Poison?  Monsieur Brunette in the Trophy Room with the Horseshoe?  Or was it our old friend Colonel Mustard whodunit in the Library with his trusty service Revolver?_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;You'll need your sharpest detective skills to solve the ever-changing CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE mystery, because in this expanded version of our classic game of detection, there are more rooms, more weapons, more suspects -- more mayhem!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The late Mr. Boddy's country manor has a total of twelve possible Murder Locations, both outdoors and indoors, with secret passages, plus new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Snoop Spaces_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; that let you broaden your investigation.  A vial of Poison and a Horseshoe bring the number of Weapons up to eight.  And the devious bunch of Supsects has grown to ten with the addition of Miss Peach, Monsieur Brunette, Madame Rose and Sergeant Gray._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;With all these additional people, places and things to unravel, your most expert powers of interrogation and deduction will be called into play._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;So shuffle the Suspect, Weapon and Murder Location cards, slip one of each into the Confidential Case File envelope -- and start sleuthing!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Turn by turn you probe, collecting evidence and pinpointing certain culprits, means, and rooms.  Then, when you think you've got it, make your accusation: Whodunit? Where? With which weapon?_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE ... it's so entertaining, it's criminal!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/bgEmWzqfkfG_WM3p_vzKLitm4lA=/fit-in/200x150/pic4456791.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/TsQwV2ichcc1ToGHOJwWx5S57KE=/0x0/pic4456791.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamedesigner objectid="3">(Uncredited)</boardgamedesigner>
                      <boardgamefamily objectid="71">Cluedo</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgameversion objectid="256077">Croatian edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1039">Deduction</boardgamecategory>
                      <boardgameversion objectid="435711">English/French edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="5499">Family Games</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgameversion objectid="154847">French edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="35407">German edition</boardgameversion>
                                    <boardgamepublisher objectid="51">Hasbro</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="319651">Hasbro English edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameartist objectid="14232">Tim Hildebrandt</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2047">Memory</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1040">Murder/Mystery</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2055">Paper-and-Pencil</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="28">Parker Brothers</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="23824">Parker Brothers edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="329708">Parker Brothers English Australian edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2035">Roll / Spin and Move</boardgamemechanic>
                      <boardgamepublisher objectid="95">Waddington_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Games, Inc.</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="59">Winning Moves Games (USA)</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="411997">Winning Moves Games USA edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameimplementation objectid="1294" inbound="true">Clue</boardgameimplementation>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="20">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="18" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="14" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="7" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="10" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="2" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="5">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="9" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="6" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="1" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="6">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="7" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="7">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="4" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="8">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="5" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="9">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="7" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="7" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="10">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="9" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="10+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="13" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="4">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="4" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="5">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>1108</usersrated>
     <average>6.59112</average>
     <bayesaverage>5.98412</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="2248" bayesaverage="5.98412" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="5499" name="familygames" friendlyname="Family Game Rank" value="656" bayesaverage="6.04568" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.47346</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>2206</owned>
     <trading>98</trading>
     <wanting>33</wanting>
     <wishing>136</wishing>
     <numcomments>410</numcomments>
     <numweights>84</numweights>
     <averageweight>1.8452</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 20 Apr 2003 02:06:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 13 Dec 2003 16:23:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE 1988 Parker Brothers.  Complete with 10 wood tokens, 8 metal weapons, confidential envelope, 30 cards, notepad, 2 dice, gameboard, instructions.  The Cadillac of Clue games, absolutely beautiful with heavy gameboard and nicely detailed heavy metal weapon pieces.  Box is in above average condition with no broken corners.  Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 07 Jun 2004 19:36:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 11 Dec 2006 15:13:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Good to acceptable. The box is in Pretty bad shape. The game is complete. The cards are well played. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Jul 2004 00:31:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 13 Sep 2004 21:38:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE 1988 Parker Brothers.  Complete with 10 wood tokens, 8 metal weapons, confidential envelope, 30 cards, notepad, gameboard, green die, instructions.  Looks like it was carefully played one time, then put away.  All pieces look brand new.  Box has some minor wear including a slightly bowed edge, but overall in very good shape.  Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Jul 2004 08:52:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 24 Aug 2004 17:45:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box has minor wear on the corners. Contents are in very good condition and complete.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 02 Dec 2004 02:39:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 13 Dec 2004 04:09:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Complete and in good playing condition.  The box has a torn corner, but is otherwise in good shape.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 03 Dec 2004 03:59:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 19 Dec 2004 00:40:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>CLUE MASTER DECTECTIVE 1988 Parker Brothers.  Complete with 10 wood tokens, 8 metal weapons, confidential envelope, 30 cards, detective notebook sheets, tri-fold gameboard, 2 translucent green dice, instructions.  The wood tokens _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; metal weapons are in excellent condition with no breaks or cracks.  The cards have minor wear from being handled but nothing that would tell someone which card is which.  One of the green dice has a small crack but is still fine to play with.  Box is worn with a torn corner but still complete.  Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 Apr 2005 18:00:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 00:00:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Good to very good condition. Components look unplayed, and are complete with all cards, pawns, weapons, board, box inserts, rule book, etc - even the dice are the  original clear green. Notepad is nearly full - only a sheet or two have been used. Box has minor shelf wear and is very slightly concaved, otherwise it is in great shape.
Another copy is available for $32. Also complete and in good condition, but notepad sheets are seperated due to decomposed glue. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 10 Aug 2005 21:28:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 23:17:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Clue Master Detective 1988 Parker Brothers.  Complete with 10 wood tokens (yellow, peach, brown, creme, white, red, green, blue, gray, purple), 8 metal weapons (gun, candlestick, horseshoe, wrench, rope, poison, pipe, knife), confidential envelope, 30 cards, detective notebook sheets, tri-fold gameboard, 2 translucent green dice with white pips, instructions.  Game is in excellent condition and looks like it was carefully played a couple of times.  Box has some minor wear where it is a little dirty but nothing where it is obvious and distractive.  The box is solid with no broken corners.  A great addition to ones collection for this low production game.  Shipping weight is 6 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 01 Feb 2006 10:55:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 21 Feb 2006 18:07:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>21</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Just a luscious game:  wooden tokens!  great little metal weapons!  nice clean board!  The rules sheet is simply minty!  Unfortunately, the box has suffered some scratches and has a little tape on it, thus the acceptable mark for condition.  I have always loved this original of this game, and the addition of more characters, etc., just makes it better.  A good playing copy of this game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 04:28:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 28 Mar 2006 02:40:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components look unplayed, and are complete with all cards, pawns, weapons, board, box inserts, rule book, etc - even the dice are the original clear green. A few notepad sheets have been used from the pad, but still plenty left. Box has minor shelf wear and is somewhat concave, otherwise it is in great shape.
Or choose a copy in good condition:
Components look unplayed, and are complete except for one original green die. Notepad sheets are seperated due to decomposed glue. Box has minor shelf wear and is concave and bent in places, but still solid. Price $32.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 08 May 2006 19:46:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 11 Oct 2006 05:03:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components are complete and original, including clear green dice. Cards are straight and crisp. A few notepad sheets have been used, but still plenty left. Box has minor shelf wear and is very slightly concave, but still solid with no split corners.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 29 May 2006 21:03:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Jun 2006 21:42:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Components are complete and in excellent condition.  Box has moderate edge wear, heavy on the corners, and is dished in somewhat.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 01:38:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Oct 2006 00:19:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Between _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;good_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;acceptable_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;.  It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s been played a lot; but I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m the original owner, and I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve kept in good condition all these years.  The cards, box, and rule book look their age (there_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s some white markings on the front of the rule book - a spill? but inside it all looks old but good), but gameboard and pieces all look very good.  There_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s still lots of blank detective pads still on the pad sheet.  Passing the fun along...
Proceeds go to charity (Voice of the Martyrs).
Shipping (US) would probably be about $7 parcel post.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 29 Oct 2006 01:48:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 19:48:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>100% complete copy in good condition. Game has been played a few times, but components are still in great shape and all original – including the clear green dice. All paper components are straight and crisp, showing very little use. Some notepad sheets have been used, but most remain. The box has slight dishing and some shelfwear, with a couple of raw corners, but still solid with no split corners. Game is free from offensive odors (pet, mildew, smoke, etc).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 16 Nov 2006 15:54:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 05 Dec 2006 21:04:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 02 Dec 2006 22:06:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 03 Dec 2006 12:19:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>100% complete copy in good condition. Game has been played a few times, but components are still in great shape and all original – including the clear green dice. All paper components are straight and crisp, showing very little use. Only a few notepad sheets have been used, but the binding glue has disintegrated so that sheets are loose. The box has slight dishing and some shelfwear, with one box lid corner carefully glued - repair is almost unnoticeable. Game is free from offensive odors (pet, mildew, smoke, etc).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 23:58:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 24 Dec 2006 01:00:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>100% complete copy in good condition. Game has been played a few times, but components are still in great shape and all original – including the clear green dice. All paper components are straight and crisp, showing minimal use. Some notepad sheets have been used, but most remain. The box top has dishing and a wrinkle, and the bottom has a tape pull. It also has some shelfwear with a couple of raw corners,  but still solid with no splits. Game is free from offensive odors (pet, mildew, smoke, etc).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 04:16:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 10 Apr 2007 03:55:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>36</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>100% complete copy in good condition. Game has been played a few times, but components are still in great shape and all original – including the clear green dice, and both box inserts. Cards are straight and crisp, showing minimal use. Some notepad sheets have been used, but many remain. The box top has some dishing and shelfwear, but still solid with no splits. Game is free from offensive odors (pet, mildew, smoke, etc).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 20:40:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 07 Apr 2007 22:43:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>36.99</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Shrink removed but game never played--components are new. Box front has some light stain on left side.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 05 Apr 2007 01:09:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 18:13:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>31</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Out of print.  Hard to find vintage game.
Best of the clues--basic clue with a whole lot more.
Contents complete with all original pieces. Clean with no odors.  original inserts.  Box top shows normal wear _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; tear with one top corner slightly split.  On inside of box top, a pencil scribble.  
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 22:13:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 11 Dec 2007 20:04:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Very good to good condition. Components are complete and original, including clear green dice and both box inserts. Cards are straight and crisp. A few notepad sheets have been used, but most remain. Box has minor shelf wear and is very slightly concave, but still solid with no split corners. Game is free from offensive odors (smoke, pet, mildew, etc).
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 01:56:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 16:17:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Very good to good condition. Components are complete and original, including clear green dice and both box inserts. Cards are straight and crisp. A few notepad sheets have been used, but most remain. Box has minor shelf wear and is very slightly concave, but still solid with no split corners. Game is free from offensive odors (smoke, pet, mildew, etc).
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 04:20:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 17:48:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Components are 100% complete and original, including clear green dice and both box inserts. Cards show minimal wear. Many notepad sheets have been used, but enough remain to play and copy. Box has minor shelf wear and is very slightly concave with an indentation on the back, but still solid with no split corners. Game is free from offensive odors (smoke, pet, mildew, etc).
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 00:53:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 00:27:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Clue Master Detective
Good overall condition and 100% complete!
I welcome international buyers!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 23:14:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 19:34:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 03:17:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 13:49:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>8</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>This item is reserved for thebrainy.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 00:57:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:08:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.95</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>complete, box shows some wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 00:34:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 14:55:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Used but complete with LOTS of detective pads left.  
There are a few tiny spots on the board, and a little crushing at one seam where the board must have fallen when folded up, but it does not really affect the board art, and does not interfere at all with play.  The cards are in great condition.  The inner box has one split seam.  The box top has no splits, but some wear on two of the corners, with a lifted flap of artwork on one.  Overall, a very nice, lightly used copy.
Shipping is at-cost and may be combined across multiple purchases.
Paypal is acceptable ONLY if it is NOT funded by a credit or debit card.  (Paypal balance or bank-funded e-checks are fine.)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 18:11:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 00:08:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>21</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The box has some scratches and dings, but the contents are in great shape.  Some pages of the pad have been used.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 02:12:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 15:43:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All game materials present and in good shape.  Lots of detective notebook sheets remain as only about a 1/4 of the pad has been used.  The box top has considerable dishing and there is also a good amount of corner wear.
Shipping is $10 to the U.S.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 23:59:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 19:16:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29.85</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game has some minor shelfwear, especially to the back wrapper.  It is complete and has never been played.  There_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s a full pad of player sheets.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 18:01:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 May 2009 00:13:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22.8</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box has some wear and dishing. The game itself is complete and in good shape.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 23:02:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 03:04:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18.95</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Up for your review is a board game by Parker Brothers, 1988 - Clue Master Detective - COMPLETE. Outer box has some shelf wear (particularly in the corners) with creases in (3) corners (longest about 3.25_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;).  There is also a small bit of price tag adhesive on (1) of the long edges (about 1_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;x0.5_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;).  Interior contents are in very good condition.  Board is very solid and crisp with no signs of stains or tears.  Playing cards have the usual wear around the edges.  Insert (white) has (1) small pen mark inbetween the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;c_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;t_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; (about 1.25_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; in length).  NOTE: dice are standard 6-sided (white).  Bottom box has the most wear with several small stains and (1) large crease parallel to (1) short side (typical with a heavy box carried by one hand).  There is also a smaller crease bottom center (2.5_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; in length).  (1) corner has substantial wear (along with crease mentioned above).  See actual item photos below for further detail. This game will weigh around 5.25 pounds once it has been packaged for shipping. I will combine multiple purchases being shipped to the same address. Feel free to pm me with any questions you may have in regard to the game listed above. 
Errors:
I try to be as accurate in item description as possible however, I may miss or overlook something with the game listed above. Any oversight is purely accidental and not meant to defraud the buyer in anyway. I will try to work out those errors when possible and I do accept returned items as a last resort (with full payment refunded, minus BGG fees), however postage for the returned item is the buyers responsibility. All items are sold _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;as-is_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;.
Payment:
For domestic orders (US) I prefer payment through money order or check but will also accept paypal if need be. For international orders I prefer payment to be made through paypal. I will email you once payment has been received and again once your item has shipped (with delivery confirmation). 
Shipping:
Shipping will be actual charges plus $1.85 (for packing _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; delivery conformation). Insurance is optional but recommended. If I do end up overcharging I will simply upgrade to the next shipping rate (i.e. parcel post _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt; priority). I always ship items with delivery confirmation.
About Me: 
I have been a member of BGG for several years but have done all my selling of vintage and OOP board games on Ebay. Since last year (march ‘08) when their site went through radical modifications it became too expensive and risky in my estimation to continue business through their site. You can look up my user id: junkfield - by going to the community page on their website and read over my 100% positive feedbacks. I appreciate your interest in this game and look forward to selling through BGG. 
Thanks,
Jon</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 23:51:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 04:20:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Minor scuffing, but complete and in good shape.
I ship fast and can combine shipping!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 19:53:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 16:52:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box is in nice shape, with nice crips box colors.  There are some modest blemishes, with a little scuffing on one lid edge, and some dishing in the lid top (the long and relatively narrow shape of the box seem to result in most copies of this having a slight bow to the box top).
Game materials are complete and in very good condition.  Dectective Notepad pad of game sheets is nearly complete.  Cosmetic inner box materials (the game material box for example) are a little rough from being weighed down by the game board.  Game board in great shape.
Shipping on this heavy and awkward size box will be a little higher than normal; Generally $11 east of the Plains and $13 to go to the plains and west.
  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 19:42:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 03:20:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>1988 vintage Clue Master Detective by Parker Brothers.  Considered the Best of the Clue games, and as a bonus the components are nicer quality as well.  The 10 suspects are wood tokens; the 8 weapons are large, heavy metal pieces; and the board is a large, trifold.
The contents are clean, undamaged, complete, and bagged.  The score pad is partially used.  The box has normal shelf wear and is solid.  The bottom is slightly dished.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 20:54:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 15:46:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for rhys</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 19:26:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 19:56:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Private sale for dawgfish.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 15:17:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 21:06:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Pawns and weapons are still sealed in their original bag. Game board and cards are in great condition. Note pad is unused.
Shipping in from 44281
SELLERS TERMS AND CONDITIONS:
PAYMENT TERMS: Payment is due within 5 days of the date you placed the order.
PAYMENT METHODS: PayPal
SHIPPING: Buyer is responsible for all shipping cost.
INSURANCE: Insurance is optional on all items.
RETURNS: New Unopened items may be returned for a refund of the purchase price of the item, excluding shipping charges, within 7 days of the delivery date. All returned items must be in the original packaging and in the condition that they were shipped to you.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 14:04:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 19:22:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box is in nice shape, with nice crips box colors. There are some modest blemishes, with a little scuffing on one lid edge, and some dishing in the lid top (the long and relatively narrow shape of the box seem to result in most copies of this having a slight bow to the box top).
Game materials are complete and in very good condition. Dectective Notepad pad of game sheets is nearly complete. Cosmetic inner box materials (the game material box for example) are a little rough from being weighed down by the game board. Game board in great shape.
Shipping on this heavy and awkward size box will be a little higher than normal; Generally $11 east of the Plains and $13 to go to the plains and west.  Other locations please ask.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 25 Jul 2010 22:35:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 17:49:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box has typical wear, especially at the corners.  Components are in great shape.  About one-half the score pad has been used.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 00:00:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 06:08:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components look like new. Box has some minor shelfwear. I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and I package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly - within 24 hours of receiving payment. Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:30:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 20:50:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>23</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Clue Master Detective (1988) by Parker Brothers
Box:  Moderate shelfwear with a few dings, dents, and creases.  Overall the box is in very good+ condition!
Components:  All critical components are present and in very good or better condition!  Many of the detective notebook sheets have been used, and there are only three pencils included.  Cards show slight wear, but nothing that will interfere with gameplay.  Pieces have been sorted and stored in plastic bags for convenience and protection - you will be very pleased with how the game has been packaged. 
SHIPPING:
U.S. shipping will be via USPS Priority Shipping and based on a weight of 5 Lbs. from zip code 85208.  International buyers are very welcome, but please contact me for a shipping price quote to avoid any surprises or misunderstandings.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 02:05:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 02:13:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>complete</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:52:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 15:20:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Clue Master Detective (1988) by Parker Brothers
Box:  Light to moderate shelfwear with one split corner, one 1/2 tear along one edge of the box, and a few assorted dings, dents, and creases.  Overall the box is in good to very good condition!
Components:  All critical components are present and in excellent or better condition!  A few of the detective notebook sheets have been used, but most of them remain unused.  Rules have a corner crease.  Cards, pawns, weapon tokens, and boards are all in outstanding condition!  Pieces have been sorted and stored in plastic bags for convenience and protection - you will be very pleased with how the game has been packaged.  
SHIPPING:
U.S. shipping will be via USPS Priority Shipping and based on a weight of 6 lbs. from zip code 85208.  International buyers are very welcome, but please contact me before buying for a shipping price quote to avoid any surprises or misunderstandings.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 02:39:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 20 May 2011 00:02:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All pawns, weapons, cards and instructions are present and in great condition.  Board is in excellent shape.  Box shows some wear, but is in good shape overall.  
Domestic shipping is $14.00 on this item due to the oversized box.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 02:25:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 19:07:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All components are present and look good.  Roughly half of the detective sheets are present.  Box has some wear and dishing, but generally looks good.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 17 May 2011 03:20:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 23:14:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Clue: Master Detective - Parker Brothers, 1988
This game is complete, with most of the detective_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s pad still available - the pieces and cards are excellent, as is the board.  There is some dishing on the insert and on the outer box, but only slight wear.  There is a slight musty smell.
Shipping is available to the USA and Canada from zip code 97355, and at the buyer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s expense.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 21:21:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 02:34:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This item was won in my Geeklist Auction. Reserved for vorpal bunny</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 11:37:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 15:44:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Super Cluedo by Parker Brothers. Inflated version of the classic detective game. 10 suspects, 8 weapons, 12 rooms. Only played once. All components and box appear as new.
UK shipping 5.50</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 15:28:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 01:43:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Reserved:
Clue Master Detective Gerald/mykidsdad $10.00
Shipping will be parcel post.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 00:34:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 08:58:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>100% complete. Most of detective_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s pad is still there.
Some minor dishing and shelf wear on box, but overall very good!
I ship fast and can combine shipping</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 02:36:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 15:05:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is the hard-to-find expanded version of CLUE that includes more room, more weapons and more villains.  Game is complete with instructions and in great shape!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 17:48:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 14:16:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components in like new condition. Suspect pad only missing a few sheets. Box has some general shelf wear and minor dishing. I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and I package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly - within 24 hours of receiving payment. I have many hundreds of games for sale and would be happy to combine shipping charges for multiple games to save you money. Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 23:22:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 11:20:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete game: 
30 cards
8 weapons
ten pawns
solution envelope
detective notepad
board
rule book
The board and pieces are in very good condition. Cardboard insert is in place, but is mashed on one corner. Box top is dished a bit with a two-inch tear along one edge and a three-inch tear along another edge. Corner wear, but no split corners.
Just like regular clue except extra players and weapons, and a couple of extra rules.
Shipping is priority mail large flat-rat box at $16.35. This game has a five pound shipping weight so for anywhere in the U.S. this is a pretty good price for priority mailing.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 20:29:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 04:08:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Parker Brothers English language edition.
Good news 1st... the set of detective note pad looks like there are none missing (like this copy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;may_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; never have been played).
Now the not so good news... one of the eight weapons (the horse shoe) is missing.  Easy enough to substitute something for it but not as nice as having the original piece.  All other components are present and in very good condition.
Also the box and box insert have seen better days.  Please see the pictures.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 05:53:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 23:29:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is 100% complete.  The pad has 37 sheets left on it.  Game components are in very good shape.  The box has some wear along the edges, and some dishing on the top cover.
Shipping weight including packaging will be 4.5 lbs., from 98685.  Because this is over 4lbs., shipping outside of the US will be USPS Priority, and will be expensive.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 13:19:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 14:26:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>2</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This item reserved for GustavMahler.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 17:08:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 16:17:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>All pieces accounted for, box has very minor wear on the edges. Board and cards in pristine condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 16:56:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 01:26:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>English Parker Brothers edition.
100% complete, minus some detective sheets which were used on both sides.  Not sure how many it came with when new but there are 31 left unused on both sides (you only use one side as front and back are identical).  There are also several possibly better detective sheets in the files section here on BGG that can be printed out.
Box is in relatively good shape for the game_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s age, except for what appears to be a quarter sized coffee stain on the boxes bottom as well as a penny sized area where the box bottom_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s paper was ripped off.  Please see the close up picture attached to this listing.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:04:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 21:24:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>42.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components are like new and still in their original packaging. Box has some general shelf wear I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and I package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly - within 24 hours of receiving payment. I have many hundreds of games for sale and would be happy to combine shipping charges for multiple games to save you money. Shipping weight is 6 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 23:52:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 01:41:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>31.99</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Game is un-played _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; only very minor shelf wear.
Cards, dice and player tokens all still in original factory baggies. Full sheet of detective pads.
I ship fast and can combine shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 17:26:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:27:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24.99</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>box is rough but components are in very good condition</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 02:52:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 14:33:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game is in good shape. Parts show some wear, but nothing that affects game play. The box has a good amount of wear. Game comes from a smoke and pet free home. I can provide pictures upon request. Buyer to pay all shipping costs from zip code 55387. Free local pick up available in the Minneapolis/St. Paul area. Feel free to GM me with questions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 21:11:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 00:37:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29.99</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This is a vintage Clue Master Detective game by Parker Brothers.  The box has some wear from age and one of the corners has the beginnings of a split (see pic.)  The board looks great although it has several small discolorations (see pic.)  The game components (cards, pawns, etc.) are in great shape with no bends or folds.  All pieces are present and it is ready to play!  Shipping will be by USPS Parcel Select...actual cost only (no surcharges.)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 18:59:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:20:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Clue Master Detective
Complete, and still contains a decent number of notepad sheets.  Box showing some wear on the edges and some indentation.
Buyer to pay actual shipping cost from Zip Code 61455. Can also arrange local pickup in either Macomb, IL or (on certain weekends) Arlington Heights, IL. I am willing to combine shipping if you are interested in more than one item.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 03:41:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 12:27:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/192225/item/3968857#3968857]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;4 Day Auction: 200 games, Pickup in STL available. Ships from STL. Ends Sunday June28th 8pm(ish) CDT_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction. For rwclayton74 only
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 01:47:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 14:32:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete. Parts show some wear, but nothing that affects game play. The box has a good amount of wear. Game comes from a smoke and pet free home. I can provide pictures upon request. Buyer to pay all shipping costs from zip code 55387. Free local pick up available in the Minneapolis/St. Paul area. Feel free to GM me with questions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 16:41:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 20:54:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>reserved for BGG user: McGames</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 15 May 2016 15:15:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 12:33:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE,COMPLET NO DIRECTIONS CAN GET ONLINE</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 14:15:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 21:56:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>CLUE MASTER DETECTIVE,COMPLET NO DIRECTIONS CAN GET ONLINE</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 14:46:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 17:27:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game is 100% complete and in good shape. Components and show some wear though no cards are creased. Box has wear as well. Game comes from a smoke and pet free home. I can provide pictures upon request. Buyer to pay all shipping costs from zip code 55387. Free local pick up available in the Minneapolis/St. Paul area. Feel free to GM me with questions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 03:11:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 00:16:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box is slightly dished, but in great shape for a game from 1988!  Game is 100% complete and components are in great condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 02:35:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 02:18:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>100% complete copy including both box inserts. Components are in great shape overall, although some have very minor damage/wear.  About half the score sheets remain on the pad - plenty for play and copying. Box has some shelfwear with dishing and wrinkles, but is still strong and solid. Game is free from offensive odors (smoke, pet, mildew, etc).
Pictures to be posted shortly.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 18:55:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 03:38:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete.  Excellent used condition for its age.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 15:58:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 23:22:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game is 100 % complete, including both box inserts. All cards, tokens, and weapons are in great shape, including the two original transparent green dice.  The game board is nearly perfect, with no damage and only a couple of small light stains. The Detective Notebook pad is about 2/3 full. Box has dishing, wrinkles, and some shelfwear - but is still strong and solid. Game is free from offensive odors (smoke, pet, mildew, etc).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 20:26:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:49:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box has some light shelf wear and some dishing on the lid but no broken corners.  Contents are complete and clean.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 04:03:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 04:08:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/244071/item/6283146#6283146]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;ENDED!  **AUCTION: Great Games! Painted Games! New Games! and some crap you can_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t live without._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
