<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="1621">
   <yearpublished>1993</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>2</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>5</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>120</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>120</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>120</maxplaytime>
   <age>10</age>
       <name  sortindex="1">Mutant Chronicles: Kampen om Citadellet</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Mutant Chronicles: Kampen om Forbandelsens Borg</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Mutant Chronicles: Le siège de la Citadelle</name>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">Mutant Chronicles: Siege of the Citadel</name>
         
   <description>Precursor of the Mutant Chronicles miniatures Game and a kissing cousin of Heroquest stands Mutant Chronicles: The Siege of the Citadel_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Setting: In Mutant Chronicles, players control one of five corporations: Imperial, Cybertronic, Mishima, Capitol, or Bauhaus. Each player begins with two of their own unique Doomtroopers imbued their Corporation's special ability.  They make decisions and plan strategies to prevent the Dark Legion and its leader, the vile Nepharite, Alakhai, from conquering the solar system. Each successful mission brings a new one with the modular Citadel and events that can help or hinder you in battle. Each promotion gives credits to access more powerful weaponry!  Grab a Punisher Shortsword and Plasma Carbine to make your mark in the Mutant Chronicles!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Gameplay:  The game begins by choosing which of the 5 players will be the Dark Legion Player for the current mission.  A player fulfills this role by setting their Doomtroopers aside for the current mission and controlling the enemies.  The Dark Legion player can earn promotion points for their inactive Doomtroopers by wounding the other player's Doomtroopers.  Thus, taking a turn as the baddies is not totally thankless.  10 different scenarios are included with the game._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The Corporation players take their Player tray and 2 Doomtrooper miniatures, two Doomtrooper cards and a Secondary Mission card if specified by mission (these allow extra points if the requirements of the card can be met).  The Dark Legion Player sets up the current mission's Citadel layout with the modular boards and gathers his mission specified Force Cards.  The Force cards are deployed in rooms face-down and are revealed when a Doomtrooper enters and the corresponding Dark Legion miniatures are placed on board.  All miniatures may move 3 squares per move action and most figures get 2 actions per turn.  A figure can do one of the following: Move then Attack, Attack then Move, Attack twice or Move twice.  Corporation Players go first.  Order is determined by flipping over a face-down Corporation token.  The revealed player (Doomtrooper or Legion) takes their turn  and the next Corporation token is flipped._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Play is semi-cooperative for the Corporation players as they compete for points, but want the overall mission to succeed.   The weapon card the Doomtrooper has equipped determines whether he can attack long range, close combat or both.  There are various miscellaneous equipment that can be equipped in addition to the weapon (healing kits, laser targeting, Grenade launcher etc...).  Attacks are carried out by rolling dice and comparing the number of hits to the armor value of the target.  If the number of hits exceeds the armor value of the creature it is eliminated.  In addition Doomtroopers can use a Doomtrooper card to affect the game in some way.  These cards list two effects but only one can be used per card and are then discarded.  The possible effects range from modification of combat or movement to messing with your opponents (jamming their gun for example)._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The Dark Legion(DL) Player at the start of his turn draws the top event card, reads it out loud and follows the instructions.  The DL player then receives the reinforcements listed on the card and places them on the board.  The DL player then looks to see if any Force cards are still face-down. If there are, the player reveals one and places the revealed units in the same room the card was in.  The DL player then takes his actions with all of his creatures.  Play continues in this way until mission is successful or the time runs out and it fails._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Game End: Successful Doomtroopers receive promotion points for the creatures killed in battle and credits specified for the mission.  If they gain rank Doomtroopers improve the combat dice they use and gain extra actions.  With their credits Doomtroopers can purchase improved weaponry and gadgets (Gehenna Puker, Nimrod Autocannon).  The Dark Legion player's inactive Doomtroopers gain 1 promotion point per point of damage inflicted upon the opposing players' Doomtroopers by creatures._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;A rare poster-magazine called _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Sinkadus_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; 41# _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;amp; 42# that was produced by Target Games AB only in Sweden, added an expansion to Siege of the Citadel.  It added to the base game Brotherhood Characters (Inquisitor Nicodemus and Mortificator Sebastian Crenshaw), new equipment, spells, and two new baddies: the Pretorian Stalkers. All the minis were given their own stats and paper models for representation._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/lVzWsJeVb0JF61QIdzLfytBpU7w=/fit-in/200x150/pic314027.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/ZSeHY47K7D2ozhhl16DX7kGO0lM=/0x0/pic314027.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamefamily objectid="5607">3D Games</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2001">Action Point Allowance System</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgameartist objectid="12497">Paul Bonner</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="25">Richard Borg</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="24281">Campaign Games</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="111">Casper</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="229239">Danish edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="31606">English edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="183104">French edition</boardgameversion>
                             <boardgamemechanic objectid="2676">Grid Movement</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="111839">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! Episode 49: 2013 in review</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                      <boardgamemechanic objectid="2011">Modular Board</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="5089">Mutant Chronicles</boardgamefamily>
                                           <boardgamepublisher objectid="668">Playtoy Industries</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="115">Pressman Toy Corp.</boardgamepublisher>
                      <boardgamecategory objectid="1016">Science Fiction</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgameimplementation objectid="187056">Siege of the Citadel</boardgameimplementation>
               <boardgameversion objectid="81294">Swedish edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="112">Target Games</boardgamepublisher>
                      <boardgamesubdomain objectid="5496">Thematic Games</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2015">Variable Player Powers</boardgamemechanic>
                      <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="17">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="12" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="11" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="6" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="3" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="5">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="14" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="1" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="5+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="3" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="7">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="1" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="6" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="7">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>965</usersrated>
     <average>7.00912</average>
     <bayesaverage>6.1016</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="1828" bayesaverage="6.1016" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="5496" name="thematic" friendlyname="Thematic Rank" value="341" bayesaverage="6.31161" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.55567</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>1620</owned>
     <trading>101</trading>
     <wanting>153</wanting>
     <wishing>284</wishing>
     <numcomments>421</numcomments>
     <numweights>90</numweights>
     <averageweight>2.2333</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 29 Oct 2003 02:59:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 13 Jan 2004 19:52:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete. Slight indentation on box cover but all the components are in great shape.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 08 May 2004 00:23:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 19 May 2004 12:57:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Never played.  Game is in mint condition, no missing pieces. Figures are attached to the base and cards are punched out.  Bought it on a whim on Ebay, but after reading the rules and trying to get my gaming group to play it, there was no interest to play this game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 20 Feb 2005 16:42:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 20 Feb 2005 19:06:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>good condition.40.00 includes shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 22:30:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 29 Mar 2005 15:20:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box is caved on top and worn, but intact.  Contents are in excellent, near mint condition.  Game is complete except for 1 (out of 13) Event cards.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 21:30:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 26 Jul 2005 02:19:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>great condition for this classic game!   buy from me and i ship the next business day!
Will happily combine shipping with multiple orders.
SPECIAL! Take 5% off the total price for EACH game you buy from me after the first one!! Maximum 30% off. Save on Shipping, and get an incredible deal!
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 22 Aug 2005 22:12:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 13 Sep 2005 21:46:14 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Just opened recently.  All components accounted for and the only damage is the unavoidable box wear of a 12 year old game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 07 Nov 2005 22:48:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 19:10:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Complete with extra figures and scoring pegs (I have no idea why, but more is always better).  Box has some shelf wear.  Must have been very seldom played as all the corporation sheets have few to none of their holes punched.  The components are accounted as follows:
10 hero figures (complete)
38 legion figures: (+11 extra)
12 legionnaires (complete)
9 necromutants (11 extra)
3 centurions (complete)
2 razider (complete)
1 nepharite (complete)
1 ezoghoul (complete and assembled)
84 cards: (complete)
36 equipment cards (complete)
13 event cards (complete)
12 force cards (complete)
13 doomtrooper cards (complete)
10 secondary mission cards (complete)
three demensional citadel (complete)
8 gameboard room pieces (complete)
plastic stairs inlay (complete)
5 hero trays (complete)
5 hero sheets (complete)
rules book (complete)
mission book (complete)
sticker sheet (present; stickers already applied)
6 reference cards (complete)
5 corporation markers (complete)
9 dice (complete)
35 scoring pegs (+5 extra)
All the components are still very high quality, again most likely due to seldom play.  I live in a smoke-free, animal-free house.
Shipping will be $10 anywhere in the continental US.
I prefer PayPal, but will accept personal/cashier_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s checks.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 28 Nov 2005 13:28:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 07 Jan 2006 17:57:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete.  All pieces in good condition.  The bod lid has one split corner and is in fair to good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 05 Dec 2005 04:22:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 05 Dec 2005 13:19:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Game has been opened and played once, but is in brand new condition. Game is complete minus the decal sheet, which is not a gamestopper.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 07 Mar 2006 15:51:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 07 Mar 2006 16:38:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Only miniatures and dice removed from bags, everything else unpunched/untouched. (I have two copies of this game, hence the odd breakout.) Game is complete. 
PM me for shipping costs if interested. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 23 Mar 2006 21:05:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 May 2006 21:15:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Condition of game parts varies:
Like New/Mint:
Cards: still in shrink
Marker pegs: still in bag
board pieces: unplayed and some still unpunched
Good:
Figures, all present save 4. [SEE BELOW] No broken pieces or damage to figures. 
Acceptable:
Box cover is split in two corners and has water damage at one end. Box bottom is fine.
Missing:
-4 hero figures are missing. I have figures of the right color (from another SoTC set) but not the correct _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;poses._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; 
-Stickers for back of hero figures. This is not critical, as the figures are all different colors. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 13 Jul 2006 22:35:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 08 Aug 2006 17:13:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Complete.  Pieces are punched/seperated from sprues.  A few of the figures are painted and some others have been coated with a white primer.  I can send pictures of the painted figures upon request.  Buyer pays shipping depending on destination.  I will combine on shipping with the other games I have for sale.  Smoke free home.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 08 May 2007 17:16:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 20 May 2007 13:58:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>This is a banged up copy of Mutant Chronicles for someone who would like to play the game without paying the high price of a new copy.  The box is banged up and taped; the figures are badly painted; and there a couple of missing and broken figures.  All of the game components (except a couple of the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;monster_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;  figures) are in tact and very playable.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 15:19:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 16:27:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>49.94</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New and Sealed! </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 03:37:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 18:28:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>49.94</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in the Seal!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 04:32:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 05:49:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still Sealed! - Might have a slight indent on the cover of the box for sitting in the warehouse for the past 14 years!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 20:26:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 26 Sep 2007 18:48:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Game is brand new still in shrink wrap. However, because its so old the shrink and box has slight scuffing. Email me for pics if desired.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Oct 2007 00:36:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 07 Oct 2007 17:55:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Game is mint and in shrink wrap. It has minor marks on wrap because of age. If you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re ordering from the US remember shipping will be between $25-$35 depending on your location and type of shipping choice. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 12 Oct 2007 15:39:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 22:53:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Game is in shrink. Due to age of the game there are minor scratches on the shrink wrap or small tears in the wrap. The box is in excellent condition. Please keep in mind that if you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re ordering from the US shipping will be between $25 and $35 depending on your location and the shipping options you choose.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 21:18:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 04 Dec 2007 03:53:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>75</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Brand New and still in Shrink wrap. This is my last copy.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 17:18:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 14:30:14 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>79.89</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still sealed! Box may have a bit of dishing from sitting in a warehouse for the last 14 years but thats it!. Now it has your name on it.
Other than that - Perfect Condition!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 05:10:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 05:42:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>79.97</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New and Sealed! Last one for Sale!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 04:17:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 15:17:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>I’m selling my board collection (over 200 board games) I will list them as I get them out of storage.  The box is in good condition with some ware, all the pieces are there.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 23:00:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 22:28:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>40</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>From my personal game stash.  I charge actual postage only.  No handling fees!  payment in $US accepted, as well as Canadian.  I combine shipping!  Prices MAY be negotiable.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 04:44:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 12:19:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Box has some wear and a split corner, and Citadel piece is missing (but not necessary for gameplay).  All components complete and in good condition).
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 23:46:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 04:38:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>The game is still in the shrink. The box has been stacked, so their is very slight bowing of the box where another game sat on top. This is very slight. Shipping is actual based on how the buyer wants the game shipped.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 28 Aug 2010 07:19:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:24:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>85.3</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Complete and in excellent condition, box has minor shelf ware, only one figure (Necromutant) has a broken bayonet. Unplayed, Corporation Sheets unpunched, cards still in plastic wrap. Shipping is $14.50 to 48 states.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 14:24:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 22:33:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Board, pieces, and playing aids are in excellent condition. The box is scuffed up but there are no holes or tears. Price includes shipping!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 02:32:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 20:57:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>game is complete and in excellent condition.
the game is mostly punched out, but has never been played.  the pegs used to mark the character boards are still factory bagged and the little holes in the characters boards havent been punched out.
box has some shelfwear and minor creasing.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 07:21:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 22:10:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>52</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Some general box wear. Can provide pics upon request. Please note this is a heavy game, it will be a little more expensive to ship than your average game. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 04:44:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:18:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>77.05</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Sold together - 2 separate copies of the original 1993 
_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;Mutant Chronicles:Siege of the Citadel_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; board game.
Game (One):COMPLETE, components are in Very Good condition, the box has some shelf ware.
Game (Two):INCOMPLETE, can be used for parts, expansions, create new scenarios, etc...
Box has a lot of shelf ware (dishing, taped corner), some components missing, broken and some cards stained or creased. Complete list available.
Shipping is $12.95 to 48 states.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 04:07:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 21:56:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>59.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This box has seen some shelf-wear, but the contents are crisp and new, and there_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s a TON of extra stuff. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 21:07:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 08:53:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box has considerable wear, with a good amount of dishing and box top has a corner split.  All game materials are present, except I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m missing one of the 35 little plastic pegs (like the ones you have in battleship), which I don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t think will be an issue and/or easily proxied.  Miniatures are in great shape.  Other game materials show modest wear but are in nice condition.
Shipping will be $11 to Eastern and Central US and $13 to Mountain and Pacific.  Other locations, please inquire.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 05:38:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 03:43:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.99</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>CONDITION: Complete and in good condition.
SHIPPING: USPS Parcel Post or Priority Mail from ZIP Code 96002. Buyer pays. Insurance optional. I combine shipping on multiple items.
PAYMENT: Money order or personal check.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 16:01:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 18:13:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>reserved for auction winner jtabler</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 18:10:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 01:15:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Only for auction winner mst3k4ever, Mutant Chronicles for $45.
American English edition. Game is like new! Some counters punched but ALL figures and ALL dice still in their original baggies! Box lid has very mild compression, otherwise perfect. This is a hard one to find!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 12:29:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 13:57:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>91</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for 
[username=filadin]
Mutant Chronicles and Hero Quest (HQ2)
Please make sure your address is correct. I will combine shipping with Hero Quest.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 05:31:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 09:31:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for Keith Mudgett</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 20:05:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 20:51:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>75</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is for auction winner atklonewolf
Shipping will be $12 via USPS Parcel Post or $18 USPS Priority Mail. If you desire insurance, just add $2.
Once you checkout, Paypal payment can be made to jenks@henderson.net</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 31 May 2012 19:26:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 23:44:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Moderate box wear including a little bit of clear tape along two edges.  Some wear/aging on cards, other components in excellent condition.  Photos available on request.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 04:51:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 18:28:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box shows wear but components in great condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 10:00:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 21:15:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>55</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>A brand new unused, unopened, and undamaged game in perfect condition. The original packaging and all materials are in brand new condition with the exception of a tear in the shrink wrap on the box base (refer photo).
All reasonable offers will be considered.
Delivery charges:
Within the UK - Parcelforce express48 including full insurance £13
Outside of the UK - please geekmail.
Buyer responsible for all Customs charges.
Buyer is responsible for all shipping costs, postage for Europe and the rest of the world is by airmail with delivery confirmation/tracking.
I can combine multiple purchases to reduce shipping costs where possible.
UK buyers can send a personal cheque or use paypal plus 3.9% (unless funds sent as a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;gift_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;) all others must use paypal.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 04:40:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 04:52:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for RandomOne</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 03:53:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 20:39:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>62</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>100% COMPLETE. Yep, everything. And it looks to have maybe been played once or twice at the most. All cards are here, all minis are here, and they_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re awesome. Very light box wear for a game this age. The only thing I can spot here is that one of the 9 necro-gun guy_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s bayonet is broken off. It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s a very, very small piece, but wanted to give full disclosure!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 14:50:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 20:17:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>89</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Mutant Chronicles: Siege of the Citadel 
(UNOPENED, SLIGHTLY DENTED BOX)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 04:30:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 04:40:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>49.99</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete and in good condition. One figure_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s bayonet is broken.
Shipping is via USPS Parcel Post or Priority Mail (Parcel is usually cheaper) and with Delivery Confirmation. Insurance is optional and buyer pays. I combine shipping if you purchase multiple items.
Please PM me with any questions, and thanks for your interest.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 03:52:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 18:45:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>26</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for Charlie Johnston.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 19:22:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 23:53:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for auction winner Ken</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 01:13:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 20:34:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 02:43:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 03:03:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For Jonathan Apuan</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 14:48:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 03:19:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>1</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For user crusader4x only!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 17:04:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 15:48:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Missing the bottom half of the Citadel; the stand-up cardboard walls (came that way). Box has light damage on the bottom and general wear, but no split corners. Components are in great condition, and unpainted. *My personal copy, from the 90_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s.
Buyer to pay actual shipping. Caution: BIG Box!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 23:33:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 23:58:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Auction Win for Ronald Zero.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 04:40:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 16:48:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game is in very good condition and has been verified as complete including the original rule booklet and mission booklet. All cards are in good condition with light wear. Miniatures are not painted. Stickers have already been applied to the hero miniatures. Box show heavy wear with most corners having been taped up. Also has usual wear - creasing along the corners/edges and along the back of the box, but overall the box is fine and serves its purpose</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 00:01:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 23:20:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Almost Like New, Box in great shape, all contents in great shape and intact.  Played
The offered game is from Mike Bartnikowski’s collection.  He passed in late 2012 and we are liquidating his gigantic (over 1200 pieces) Hoard.  We have a live .xls catalog with most of the pieces, asking price and condition.  To learn more, make a bulk offer, arrange for local pick-up or inquire about other titles contact us at facebook page Bartnikowskis Hoard or email at bartnikowskishoard@gmail.com.  
Local pick-up in Wyandotte MI, cash, credit cards (3% fee), or paypal accepted upon pickup.  Shipping to be paid by buyer.
paypal payments accepted at barbarakiss@sbcglobal.net
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 22:26:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 10:00:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>never opened, still in original shrink-wrap. 
The additional pictures show the contents and pieces from another opened and used set that is also available 
US buyers; S/H for this item will be  $30.00 from here in Canada to anywhere in the USA via Canada Post_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Expedited Parcel service - which INCLUDES sufficient insurance coverage!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 21:12:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:50:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>1</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Free to a good or even acceptable home.
I actually have two copies.  You get both.  The first is basically unopened.  It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s missing the box shrinkwrap, but the figures and dice are still in their plastic bags and the board pieces haven_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t been punched out.  The box is a little battered due to all the moves it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s been through.
The second is in worse shape, I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve opened the bags and half painted a number of the figures and I think I lost the skeleton guy with the chainsaw glaive.  However, you want the nice copy, you need to take the half painted rifled through one too.
I never played these.  I found them on deep sale in a Toys _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;R_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; Us and bought for the figures.  I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m trying to free up some space in the house and will happily mail these to someone who_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll play them.  I don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t want any money I just want them out of the house.  If you live outside the US let me know and if the shipping is reasonable I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll send them to you.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 13:43:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 19:11:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Auction item for mergryphon
http://www.rpggeek.com/geeklist/153456/item/3428149#item3428149</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 02:07:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 05:09:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>89.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete and meticulously bagged.  Components are in great condition.  The box is in fair to good condition.  One split corner has been repaired and there is considerable shelf wear with some dishing and creased on the box top and bottom.  However, it is structurally sound and has no issues with holding the components of the game.  Shipping in the US is 14.95.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 20:52:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 22:38:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>64.99</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>In good condition complete send me a email for more info.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 15:19:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 03:41:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>49.99</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Shrinkwrap with very light dishing.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 21:31:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 17:18:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Listing as Very Good.
All components complete and unused/unpunched.
$9.95 Shipping to US</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 17:41:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 20:05:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:48:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 22:18:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Bought used, played, but components in very good condition, box has dishing and shelf wear, but no split corners. English first edition, Pressman Toy Corp 1993 
[ImageID=2404359 inline] [ImageID=2404360 inline]
Package Info and Shipping: 
Weight: 5 lb 6 oz, Dimensions: 26x16x5
reserved for mikica1986 - please do not buy this unless this is you, thanks!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 00:44:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 04:09:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box has some dishing. All parts are all here and in played but still great condition. buyer to pay shipping from 53189. Thanks for looking.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 30 May 2015 23:35:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 03:47:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Most figures are painted. There is an extra set of heroes unpainted but without their own bases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 19:20:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 22:20:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>99.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is in very good condition, 100% complete and components neatly separated and bagged very nicely. 
The box is also in very good condition, but has one clean split corner on side top of box. Still very solid with only slight shelf wear.
MInis are unpainted. They fit snugly in their stands, but they are not glued in, so plenty of opportunity to paint and/or customize these any way you like.
Might not have ever even been played, two of the character sheets haven_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t been pegged.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 06:02:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 15:47:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This items is reserved for OmegasSquared
This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/194587/item/4040677#4040677]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Moving Auction - Local Pickup Available - 24 Hour End Times_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 17:54:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 20:42:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This is a brand new copy still in the original shrinkwrap!!!  There is no damage to the box.  You will be very hard pressed to find an untouched copy of this game any more.  Price does not include shipping, but I only charge the actual cost to ship and nothing else.  I carefully pack the game to protect it too.
If you have any questions feel free to e-mail me and thanks for looking.  I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll ship worldwide, but be aware that shipping will be high outside of the United States.
NOTE:  The attached pictures are from my open game that I play with just to show you what the game looks like.  As noted above the game I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m selling is still in the original shrink!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 20:18:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 03:25:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>59.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components are complete and in very good condition.  Box has only minor shelf wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 22:37:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 03:34:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 01:45:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 04:06:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box and components show some wear, but the game is complete and in great condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 23 May 2016 02:18:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 23 May 2016 03:01:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>*** ITEM RESERVED FOR USER Neil Moore — _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;FLEETING SPRING AUCTION_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; RESULTS ***
Offers from others will not be confirmed.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 09:46:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 01:58:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete and in overall excellent condition.
Flaws as follows:
Box top has two broken seams.
2 Centurion minis (out of 9)have had their bayonets broken off.
Otherwise, game looks unplayed.  Cards are in _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;like new_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; condition.  Photos available on request and will be posted later if I decide to list the game on BGG Marketplace.
Please don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t hesitate to contact me via BGG messaging if you have any questions.
Thanks.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 05:28:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 05:43:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/211133/item/4730202#4730202]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Large Summer Auction in Irvine, CA (US Only)_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 20 May 2016 03:15:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 22:57:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>So this is a complete game with spare parts that I pieced together from two copies I acquired from others. Would like to play it but it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s just getting lost in a sea of games on my shelf.
1) I have both boxes. Both have seen heavy use. One has a blown out corner (pictured). The other is intact but has clear packing tape on some corners. The worst box is pictured.
2) The complete set of cards has been sleeved using Mayday sleeves (not the premium kind). There is a partial deck of spare cards that I have not sleeved. 
3) There is a complete set of miniatures pieced together from two incomplete sets. Some were primed (now grey) by a previous owner. The balance are their original color. Three Necromutants have broken rifle tips. I never received the broken parts so I had no way to repair them. I also have a few spare miniatures. On miniature is missing its base. Everything is pictured, though the spares are a bit harder to see in one of the photos.
4) There is one complete set of dice plus a few spares.
5) All of the map tiles for two games are present. Both Citadel plastic foundations are present, as well as both sets of the cardboard Citadel structure.
6) There is one complete set of player aid/reference cards.
7) There are two complete sets of Doomtrooper reference boards.
8) There is one unopened package of pegs.
9) There is one set of Rules and Mission Booklet.
10) There is one complete Doomtrooper sticker sheet.
11) There are 5 cardboard Doomtrooper faction icons and 4 slotted rectangular cardboard tokens (pictured).
Sorry that some of the pictures are fuzzy. If you are interested in seeing better pictures, let me know and I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll see if I can provide clearer photos.
It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s definitely a playable copy. It looks used. Expect cardboard to show some creases and edgewear. Same with the cards. Outside of the damage described above to a few Necromutants, the complete set of miniatures are in great shape. Some of the spares are whole and in great condition as well.
I am selling this all as one lot. If you want to buy it but don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t want everything (maybe to save on shipping) I will most likely throw away whatever you don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t want. If you want me to toss the box in the worst condition I will still have to package most of the spare parts outside of the other game box as they will not fit.
Reserved for BGG User Brandon Bowling. Please do not order if you are not this user.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 11:50:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 19:09:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Classic 90_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Space Hulk alike, complete and in good condition.
Paypal fee will be added to the total</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 19:40:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 21:33:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>75</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Box is creased and one corner is torn, but the components are complete and basically like new (player boards have all the pegs and still have the original gloss, etc.)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 13:20:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:43:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This listing is for a used copy of Mutant Chronicles: Siege of the Citadel in very good condition. The black pegs are still sealed in their original packaging but one corner of the box lid as well as base are split and the mission booklet has mild distortion (see photos).
All reasonable offers will be considered.
Buyer is responsible for all shipping costs that will depend on buyer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s location.
Overseas shipping can cost a lot and will always be via airmail with delivery confirmation/tracking: please ask before buying.
Buyer responsible for any and all Import/Customs charges.
I can combine multiple purchases to reduce shipping costs where possible.
Additional PayPal purchase fee (5%).
No additional fee when funds sent direct in British pounds (e.g. sent not using a credit card as the source of funds in PayPal when using the family/friends option, personal cheque, bank wire transfer, cash, etc).</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
