<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="2228">
   <yearpublished>1977</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>2</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>3</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>180</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>180</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>180</maxplaytime>
   <age>12</age>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">War of the Ring</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Wojna o Pierścień</name>
         
   <description>'War of the Ring'. On a large map of Middle Earth, armies are mustering and heroes are readying to fight the shadow spreading out of Mordor. The game is played on two levels. Both sides (or three if someone wants to play Saruman) have great armies that battle in a typical wargame style while another game is going on at the same time with individual characters around the fate of the One Ring. In the Campaign game Sauron's forces are the more powerful but the free peoples get the edge in the Character game._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Highly sought after as a collectors item. It could be purchased with either a paper map or a full mounted map, and was also sold in a three-game set with the folio games Gondor and Sauron.  This set is called The Games of Middle Earth._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/I_2sytin2nFo6hIk9KUfDUgrJck=/fit-in/200x150/pic613309.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/qOvi6w1bWVUdwbzPciDBoyR0Oao=/0x0/pic613309.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamehonor objectid="10886">1977 Charles S. Roberts Best Fantasy Board Game Nominee</boardgamehonor>
               <boardgamehonor objectid="10884">1977 Charles S. Roberts Best Fantasy Board Game Winner</boardgamehonor>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1022">Adventure</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2080">Area Control / Area Influence</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgameartist objectid="15260">Ralph Bakshi</boardgameartist>
               <boardgameversion objectid="26541">Bakshi Movie Art cover</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="722">Howard Barasch</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="135">Richard H. Berg</boardgamedesigner>
                             <boardgamepublisher objectid="5018">Encore (for boardgames)</boardgamepublisher>
                      <boardgamecategory objectid="1010">Fantasy</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamecompilation objectid="144845">The Games of Middle Earth</boardgamecompilation>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="214173">GrogCast Season 5 Episode 12 – A Cast of Many</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2026">Hex-and-Counter</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="74796">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! episode 31: Three player games</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                      <boardgameartist objectid="20676">Tim Kirk</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1093">Novel-based</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgameversion objectid="33184">Polish edition</boardgameversion>
                      <boardgameartist objectid="1030">Redmond A. Simonsen</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="120">SPI (Simulations Publications, Inc.)</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="200456">SPI Deluxe Edition with Mounted Mapboard</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="76228">SPI English edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="182783">SPI Flat Pack British Edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="4263">Tolkien Games</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2015">Variable Player Powers</boardgamemechanic>
                             <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="4664">Wargames</boardgamesubdomain>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="21">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="12" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="15" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="4" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="8" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="15" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="5">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="1" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="4" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="12">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="10" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>863</usersrated>
     <average>6.60898</average>
     <bayesaverage>5.92716</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="2505" bayesaverage="5.92716" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="4664" name="wargames" friendlyname="War Game Rank" value="527" bayesaverage="6.38481" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.5947</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>1965</owned>
     <trading>84</trading>
     <wanting>80</wanting>
     <wishing>173</wishing>
     <numcomments>397</numcomments>
     <numweights>95</numweights>
     <averageweight>3.4526</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 26 May 2003 21:28:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 23 Jul 2003 11:43:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This is a rarity among rarities. S.P.I._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;#039;s The Games of Middle Earth, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;The War of the Ring: S.R. 1418 to 1419_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; with _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Sauron_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;. This is the Deluxe version of the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; game which includes two smaller games _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Sauron_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;. The Ring game was played a couple of times but all 400 counters are present and in excellent condition (see the four photos). All 112 character cards are present in plastic sleeves and are in excellent condition with one small blue line on the text side of #75, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Boromir attempts to steal the Ring._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; The counters for _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; are punched but counted by hand and all 200 are present in excellent condition. The counters for Sauron are unpunched.
The main map hardly shows any age stress, the creases present are to be expected with a 25 year old folded paper map and there is one small stain on the portion where the Magic Item cards are placed. The maps for _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Sauron_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; are pristine.
There is one blank Character Endurance Level Chart (both sides) and the charts for all games are in good to excellent condition. The rules for The Ring game are well worn but entirely readable and functional, there is a stain on the back page and the cover is splitting at the binding fold but all pages are attached and readable. There are three sets of Standard Rules for Gondor and Sauron and the exclusive rules for each game are in perfect condition. The original counter tray is present in excellent condition.
This is an incredible find but that_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;#039;s not all folks! As shown in one of the photos there is a spare Character/Monster card sheet which remains unpunched. It is the fourth of the sheets with numbers running from 85 to 112. Amazing.
Ask any questions before buying.
Shipping will be $8.50 in the continental US and both insurance and return receipt are MANDATORY on this item. Insurance is $3.50 and return receipt is $1.75.
Any foreign buyer will also pay insurance and return receipt (if available) and S/H will be calculated based on destination.
I must receive payment within 10 business days or the sale will be canceled and the item relisted with appropriate negative feedback.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 24 Sep 2003 16:59:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 24 Sep 2003 19:18:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Won as an auction item.  This was used when obtained.  It is complete.  However, I have mounted the mapsheet onto old game boards and to do that, had to cut the mapsheet to fit the boards.  While I feel the result is fine for more ease in playing on a flat surface, a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;purist_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; may not want this copy.  Definately a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;to play_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; version.  Bos is definitely showing age but the components are complete and in very good condition.  Mapsheet is the main issue here.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 11 Dec 2003 16:24:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 02:31:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>145</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Ring Trilogy_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; edition, includes Gondor and Sauron. Much tougher to find than the version without the expansions.
 One split end, but otherwise very good condition. The maps are particularly nice condition (normally they wear easily as they_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re not mounted or laminiated, but these are in very good condition).
Shipping within the US via insured priority mail.
Note to International (non-US) buyers:
I must declare actual value on all customs forms. **I will not falsify values on customs forms, no exceptions!**. For International orders, only Paypal is accepted.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 12 Dec 2003 23:27:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 20 Dec 2003 09:38:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>65</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This is a very nice condition copy of the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;war of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; it is actually the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Middle Earth_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; version the ring trilogy.  It includes  _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Gondor - The Seige of Minas Tirith_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Sauron - The battle for the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;.  All the component are in good condition all four map sheets , all 112 cards and 699 counter are present (1 counter appears to be missing).  All the contents are in excellent condition, the box is square no bows or splits just a little rubbed on the edges. Extra Photo if required.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 16 Jan 2004 11:33:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 13 Apr 2004 09:12:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>75</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box scuffed at the edges, but contents superb.  The cards are separated, but the counters are still unpunched.  All maps in wonderful condition.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 11 Jun 2004 18:51:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 16 Jun 2004 15:05:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>80</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Box shows some wear. The cover is the Balrog fighting Gandalf NOT the Ralph Bakshi cover. All pieces punched out and in bags. I am open to negotiations on the price.
This is the version with the cardboard game board. It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s a big three piece monster of a game board as a matter of fact.
There doesn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t seem to be any expansions with it. Everything listed on the instruction manual is in the box.
Also, as far as damage goes, the box is in really good shape with only some wear around the edges and one corner is split. There_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s some water stains on the inside of the lid but nothing big. One playing card, Celeborn, has a tear on the coating on the back but nothing that obscures any printing or artwork for the card. There_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s also 3 small brown stains on one of the map pieces but I had to look pretty close to find those. 
I am unable to host pictures but can send some pics by email if you like.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 28 Oct 2004 13:11:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 04 Feb 2005 23:24:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Box is worn, with some wrinkling, a bit of bowing, two split corners - repaired on the inside with transparent box tape. Missing two informational counters (game turn and shadow points) and one magic card (#54). Color scans and jpegs provided of all. Three of the tear-out record sheets are used, leaving three. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 23 Nov 2004 12:57:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 23 Nov 2004 16:15:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Includes War of the Ring, Sauron and Gondor. Good condition. All peices present. Maps and counters in good condition. Very few plays.  Slight separation of box bottom/sides. Outer box in good condition with typical wear of box thats been carefully stored for 24 years. The tables for the gondor game were pulled from the directions, but still present. A few pencil marks in directions. Pen addition to one character card (minor game balance change).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 06 Jan 2005 02:19:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 04 Aug 2005 13:44:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched but complete (I counted all the pieces!).  Mounted map boards.  Game componants are sorted by army and in excellent condition.  One of the stat sheets has some pencil markings.  The box is in good condition considering it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s age - some shelf wear is evident and 2 corners have been taped to repair minor splits.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 09 Jan 2005 23:02:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 10 Jan 2005 07:54:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>6</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>I have by some bizzarre coincidence 41 of the cards from _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;war of the ring. This is not the full set of cards as there are 121 in total.
These are numbers 1-40 and 98. (card numbers are in the top left hand corner)  They consist of the yello,buff,pink,white character cards.  The red servants of sauron and #98 the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;three naguls_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; search card.  I guess they might be of use to someone.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 20 May 2005 15:43:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Jun 2005 21:33:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>125</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Played/punched not shrinkwrapped. Part of a LARGE estate sale - most of the games are being sold to ONE buyer, some games are being sold to gamers...
This edition of _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; includes the games _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Sauron_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; as well.
Shipment will be in mid-late June, when full collection of games is removed from storage.
Will accept Paypal - but buyer must pay all associated fees. Will ship worldwide. For shipments in US, game will be shipped priority mail. For worldwide shipments, amount charged will be actual cost.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 03 Apr 2006 16:42:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 21:45:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>80</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>3 game edition all checked and 100% complete, includes 2 sheets of counters mostly unpunched (see photos)
All contents in excellent condition:
Rulebook (including chart and table sheets, and endurance level charts in centre pages)
700 die-cut counters (over half of these unpunched)
112 playing cards
4 games maps (east, west, Gondor and Sauron)
2 6-sided dice
2 sets standard rule booklets
Gondor exclusive rules
Sauron exclusive rules
2 sheets Gondor charts and tables
Counter tray
Box: Good condition considering its age - the top of the box dips in slightly and there is some minor scuffing but all corners are still intact. (see photos)
Buyer to pay shipping and optional insurance.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 23:23:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 01:05:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>125</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Box is slightly damaged but otherwise unpunched and in perfect condition.  A collector_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s dream item.  Shipping at buyer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s discretion.  Price is in US dollars.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Oct 2006 15:51:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 22:30:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>80</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The Sauron and Gondor games are unplayed (counters unpunched). Everything is in good shape. Not much else to add, really!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 12:37:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 08 Nov 2007 16:45:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>This is the SPI designer edition with mounted board.  Recreate J.R. Tolkein_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s classic tale in this game designed by Richard Berg and Howard Barasch.
Components, rules and charts are all intact, and game includes a chit tray.  Box is old and has some wear and torn edges, many of which have been repaired with tape.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 18:21:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 14:09:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>The game is punched but otherwise complete and in good condition (the map has some neat marker annotations of a victory point variant, but it is perfectly playable and otherwise as new, and the box inside is annotated with counter disposition. See photos). Also included issue no. 37 of Moves magazine, which contains an article with the rules to play the game with three players. Please note that this is NOT the complete Middle Earth trilogy, it just comes in its tombstone box: the only game contained is War of the Ring.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 21:18:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 15:35:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>80</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>80% Unpuched. Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition WITHOUT Sauron and Gondor games, but with mounted map. Box in fair shape with a bare spot where price tag was taken off (not by me). Complete and in great condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 22:06:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 12:52:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>70</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is the Middle Earth version, which includes the two operational games, Sauron and Gondor.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 15:36:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 17:36:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>105</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 14:05:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 19:42:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Maps have some tape residue stains at edges but are perfectly readable.
Box is scuffed and stained.
Shipping to UK destination = £6</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 04:10:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 16:20:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Description/Condition: Most of the game is unpunched and like new. However, one card has a nick on it. The rules are stained and well read. This is the white designer box and it is beat up.
FOR Bill Johnston ONLY - Winner of Geeklist Auction
$8 for Priority Mail
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 00:52:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:51:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>92</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition Olive green box. Unplayed, a few cards aren_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t even separated. Partial punched counters have been verified to be complete, counters like new. Mapboards like new. Punched counters are organized, separated and stored in ziplock as are the unseparated cards. Rules booklet is in excellent condition/like new. Box is better than the average I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve handled of this title. 3.5 on a 1-5 scale (5 best)with modest storing abrasions and shelving fade but there are no major imperfections. NUMEROUS EXTRAS PROVIDED
including periodical articles from ALL Moves issues and the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes too. Plus a WOTR additions article from Campaign magazine. And some _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;homemade_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; quality color deployment tables and additional charts. 
 </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 12:23:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 07:03:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>45</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This is the Middle Earth 3 game set, War of the Ring+Gondor+Sauron
Components complete and in very good condition.
Box has significant scuffs.
Shipping to UK destination £6</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 08:13:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 09:04:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete, and all components in excellent condition, apart from 5 cards which have been damaged by decayed elastic bands (see picture).
Shipping as follows:
UK - £2.90
Europe - £5.30
Rest of World - £10.10</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 18:18:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 09 May 2010 20:25:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box game punched
Postage
UK £7
Europe £10
Others £19</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 12:04:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 05:18:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>85</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>This listing is for the 1977 War of the Ring game by SPI.  It has never been played and all components are unpunched.  The box shows very minor dishing and scuffage with the only damage being one torn corner.  No signs of water damage, no odd smells, and comes from a pet free/smoke free environment.  This game has been stored for many years and unfortunately has never seen gameplay.
The version being sold is the following:  http://www.boardgamegeek.com/image/24750
Shipping is $13 to anywhere in the United States.  Thanks for checking out this listing!  Feel free to contact me with further questions on the condition of the game.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 02:50:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 21:15:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>107</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened but unpunched. Complete. Cards uncut. This is the mounted map version without Sauron and Gondor.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 20:22:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 11:27:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>War of the Ring by SPI (White Box, Bakshi Artwork)
Box intact (little grubby on the front)
Items present but the pieces are punched.
(Will also trade for Warhammer 40k Nurgle items)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 01:13:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 27 May 2010 21:54:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Mounted board.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 17 May 2010 18:28:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 21 May 2010 23:50:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>SPi War of the Ring Trilogy
Been in storage for many years
counters punched... only played once or twice
SPI _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;flat pack_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; box has some damage
pics available on request</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 00:51:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 14:29:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>89</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>1977 revised edition!
Very Good condition; includes Sauron and Gondor
(Sauron is unpunched!)
USA buyers may pay via check, MO, or PayPal
International buyer must pay via PayPal only.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 05:22:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 10:43:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete and in good condition. Most counters not punched.
Box scuffed
Shipping to UK destination £6</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 10:43:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 10:53:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>55</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>THIS ITEM IS NOT FOR SALE - UNDER OFFER
This is the highly collectible Middle Earth version with the Gondor and Sauron games included. The box looks exactly like the main BGG image. It has the thick card maps (not mounted). The counters, cards, boards, rules etc are in really good condition. The box has some slight scuffing to the edges and a tiny barely noticeable dent to the base but is in remarkable condition considering its age. I have owned the game from new and it has only been played a couple of times. I would be delighted to get this myself and I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m very picky about game condition!
Postage and Packing:-
World Wide - Air Mail, NOT Signed For: £15.00</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 00:31:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 20:51:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>99.95</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>The more desirable Ralph Bakshi art, white cover version. Pretty much perfect. Components including maps, cards, counters and rulebook are in excellent, never-been-played condition. Box has some very minor shelfwear. I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and I package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly - within 24 hours of receiving payment. Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 01:44:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 08:13:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>47</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is a copy of SPI_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Games of Middle Earth -- War of the Ring._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;  It is the edition that includes all 3 games (ie. Gondor, Sauron, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; War of the Ring).  The box is in good condition.  It has a little creasing in the lower left corner and a slight amount of fading, but overall is in quite good shape with no split corners or tearing of any kind.  The game contents are in very good condition.  I did a careful count of the cards and they are all there.  All the cards EXCEPT one are in very good condition.  The #89 card has a slight tearing in the upper left corner (see provided picture), but this is NOT visible when the card is face down, so it should NOT affect game play in any way.  All the maps, rules, and player aids are also present and in very good condtion.  I counted out all the game chits and the count totaled 700.  According to the rules there should only be 300 total chits, so I don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t know why my count came out so high.  Needless to say, I believe all the chits are there, perhaps with some extras.  I did an extensive search online and on BGG for a manifest of the chits but could not find one.
I am willing to ship via any method the buyer prefers, so just let me know.  If you have any questions or would like to see more pictures don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t hesitate to ask.  Also feel free to make me an offer on this game if you don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t like/can_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t afford the posted price.  I may just take you up on it.  Can_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t hurt to ask anyway.  :)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 11:33:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 12:36:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game components complete and in good condition except that maps were once taped together and where tape has come off has left a stain. Map is quite readable through this stain.
SPI edition
Shipping to UK destination £6</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 02:19:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 01:33:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>46.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Complete, played once, almost as good as new
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 05 May 2011 12:45:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 05 May 2011 13:06:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>46</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For Games into Equity auction winner Killing Joke.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 13:17:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 10 May 2012 18:47:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>140</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game in original shrink wrap
Boxed SPI ed. _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Middle Earth_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, containing _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Sauron_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;.
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling - Priority Mail excl. Insurance: 
Switzerland: CHF 10.-- 
Europe: USD 37.--
Others: USD 52.--
also available: boxed SPI game _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; (without the other 2 games, price $ 110.-- 
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 00:18:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 02:58:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>I bought this in 1977, and to my knowledge it hasn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t been opened since then.  Unpunched counters.  Original rubber bands on the playing cards, etc.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 23:45:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 20:17:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched and possibly played a few times.  All 112 cards present, chits not counted.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 19:55:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 04:08:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for fallen (Jamie Groulx)
In excellent condition and complete. The box has a couple of minor marks, only to be expected for a game of this vintage! The contents are absolutely perfect.
This is the version with the Bakshi movie cover.
Shipping will  £12 (airmail).
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 05:20:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 09:25:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:29:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 08 Sep 2011 08:39:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Contents are complete and in very good condition, with the exception of the rulebook which is in fair condition. The box is in poor condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 22:17:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 02:28:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Good to Very Good. Thrifted version that appears to have been well cared for. Chits punched and uncounted but are all neatly organized in the box. Maps and rule books in excellent condition. Charts and table and all rule books as well as all 112 cards accounted for. Box shows some wear but corners are intact.
This is the SPI 1977 version with paper maps.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 13:21:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 17:37:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>52</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Original owner. Maps, rules, cards and chits in excellent (like-new) shape; some chits never separated/punched. All chits kept in protective case. Box has minor wear on one bottom edge.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:27:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 09:59:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>100</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Main game punched   Includes the Gondor and Sauron mini games (unpunched). </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 19:10:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 07:05:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>cards and chits and maps are complete and in very good condition. The is the SPI 1977 yellow edition with plastic lid and tray for counters. The box and lid are intact but show signs of wear </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 01:12:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 01:58:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>140</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Middle Earth version with the two mini-games.  All components in like new condition.  There are maybe a dozen or so counters punched out; but the rest are still intact on the counter sheets.
Send me any questions you might have although there_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s not much else to say about it.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 07:22:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 13:25:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>selling a complete version of this game. it is the bakshi movie art cover and everything is accounted for. only on the side of the box there is a stain of some sort. shipping is on the buyer. pictures can be given on request.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 01:04:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 20:23:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Punched, missing one card and eleven counters. The box is in poor/fair condition: One split corner on the lid, one split corner on the bottom, and some concavity, wear, stains also on the lid. The rulebook generally shows its age and has some miscellaneous notations written inside. The maps are in very good condition. The event cards have their ID # circled in pen, and a couple of the character cards had been _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;improved_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; upon (I counted three) by the previous owner drawing an extra feature or two in pen. Besides that, the cards are in good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 08:10:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 21:24:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>55</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>SPI 3 game version.
Contents are like new. The Gondor and Sauron game counters have never been punched!
The main tiles, rules, cards are in _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;like new_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; condition.
Lid is very slightly creased in the corners and has some very light scuffing.
---
Postage/carriage at cost, rounded up to next pound to offset Paypal charges.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 15:00:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 21:53:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>punched, complete, never played
box has some wear</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 05:06:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 19:55:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Designers Edition. Box has shelf wear and one edge is broken up the seam. but over all in good condition. All pieces and parts are present. The play sheets have been marked in pencil (lightly) so easy enough to clean one up to make good copies. Great Illustration and very faithful to the story. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 17:37:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 19:56:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Flat tray_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s cardboard backing has come loose. Counters 60% punched. Charts and record sheets are still present in the rulebook and unmarked. In addition to the original paper mapsheets I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m including a set of the mounted mapboards from the designers edition of the game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 09:58:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 May 2013 15:59:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>65</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All maps are mounted on heavy (4 mm) cardboard (front and rear =_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt; 4 tiles = 2 43x55 cm and 2 43x27 cm). Gondor counters are still framed.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 23:08:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 01:16:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Middle Earth, the ring trilogy version with Gondor and Sauron games included.  The paper maps are included with this version and are in mint condition.  Counters and cards have been punched, but are lightly played and in excellent condition.  Box shows minor shelf wear with no split corners.  100% complete.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 09:06:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 18:11:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>140</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game
Boxed SPI ed. _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Middle Earth_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, containing _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Gondor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Sauron_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;.
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling - Priority Mail incl. Insurance: 
Switzerland: CHF 10.-- 
Europe: USD 41.--
Others: USD 52.--
also available: boxed SPI game _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;War of the Ring_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; (without the other 2 games, price $ 110.-- 
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 09:25:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 10:37:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>110</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling - Priority Mail incl. Insurance: 
Switzerland: CHF 10.-- 
Europe: USD 41.--
Others: USD 52.--
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 03:28:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 20:58:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>For a sheet of 400 counters with only 23 of 400 punched and they are present. Very nice sheet with still quite white Gondorians. VG color sheet too</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 01:18:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 11:14:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>90</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is the SPI game in the bookshelf box.  It is the designers edition with the mounted mapboards.  Game is punched, but 100% complete.  All the counters, cards and mapboards are in mint, like new condition.  The box is solid, all the corners are rigid, but there is shelfwear on the box top and bottom, especially in the corners.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 02:13:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 05:02:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For Lausus from auction</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 13:20:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 19:43:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>140</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition Trilogy. Unpunched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 21:55:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 00:26:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>20</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>This is the game with the paper (unmounted) maps and include the games Gondor and Sauron.  The game is complete, but unfortunately, humidity has impacted this game.  The game maps are in good shape, but have some staining.  The rules and charts are in good condition.  Some of the counters have serious staining, other counters are clean.  The cards are all stuck together.  So this game can be considered to be parted out.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 08:53:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 25 Aug 2013 08:53:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Game componets complete and in good condition except:
Rules are grubby from being studied often.
The War of the Ring map has been taped and tape glue has yellowed and some damage at folds.
Small stain on one card.
 This is _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Middle Earth_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; SPI edition including Gondor and Sauron battles.
Shipping to UK destination £7</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 20 May 2013 18:29:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 23:36:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>80</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched, complete
box shows some aging
cards are in Italian</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 17:53:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 07:42:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For sale: used copy of War of the Ring,  SPI Flat Pack British Edition.
Now, this is an old game (1977), so read carefully:
- Manual and original inserts are in good condition; some small stain on the cover of the manual
- The game is COMPLETE. All cards are accounted for, and in (very) good condition. I have counted the counters twice, and come to a total of 400 (which according, to the manual means the game is complete). The counters are in very good condition and have been bagged.
- Counters and cards have NO wear on them (looking quite new actually)
- Paper map (originally in 2 parts) has been carefully taped together at the back
- The plastic flat pack (a counter tray and a cover with an insert) has some damage, but minor (small pieces of the edge missing, but counter tray + cover still intact)
- The included day may not be the original one (damaged)
- Some errata and player aids marked on some game components in pencil
Pictures upon request; ships from the Netherlands.
Approximate shipping costs; around 10 euros. Exact costs upon request.
Payment through paypal or european money order.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 19:16:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 09:08:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>White box edition. Missing only a die, one of the (identical) game tables/aids (the other is present) and some of the original endurance sheets (there were 4 for marking losses etc on) there are a couple of photocopy replacements included.
Condition:-
- Box: a bit battered with one torn corner (repaired) and some bowing.
- Counters: all present and correct = good to very good condition.
- Cards: all present and correct - very good condition.
- Rule Book: shows significant use and repair attempts, and may have been consulted at the Battle of the Pelanor Fields. It is still readable and usable.
- Map (paper not mounted): Good condition although one of the two original panels is more faded than the other. everything is still clear and usable. The two panels were stuck together by a previous owner, but not very well. I have separated them, trimmed and restuck them. They are much better now, and no detail has been lost.
Also included are:-
- Print out of the revised 2nd edition rules.
- Counter manifest scan
- OOB and set up sheets.
From a smoke and pet free home and will be well packaged.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 15:40:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:03:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>62.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Comes with gondor and sauron mini expansions.  Plastic top is aged and cracked in a ocuple of places, contents are in great shape.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 19:12:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 05:25:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>95</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Games of Middle Earth edition with the two additional minigames.
Game is unpunched, and in very good condition.  See pictures attached to the listing.  Please pardon the mess as I was doing renos at the time the picture was taken.
Shipping is expected to be about $15 in Canada, and $20 to $25 to the US.  Please contact me for a firm quote first.
I will be listing this elsewhere when I get around to it, so please contact me to confirm it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s still available.
Thanks
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 03:51:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 12:03:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Sadly parting with some of my wargames after getting laid off....But the good homes they go to makes it easier..
All my games are in great condition and this one has a custom made box...kinda looks great</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 18:18:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 21:48:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Bakshi Movie Art Cover version.  Reserved for The Grinch.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 05:14:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 15:17:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>RESERVED FOR Meisterchow
Bundle includes:
War of the Ring
World War II: Pacific Theater of Operations
Pacific War
Guderian_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Blitzkrieg
Total price is $100 plus $15 shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 11:31:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 12:00:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>56</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 18:44:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 03:37:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>92.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>beautiful white box I put a like new set of mounted designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s edition map boards in. no paper maps. Like new counters albeit punched (verified) many in strips, e.g. the Gondorians are entirely unpunched, sorted and ziplock bagged by type. cards are like new (57-84 haven_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t been separated, still in sheet form) and the rules booklet still has the endurance charts and charts _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; tables center pages still attached. booklet itself is still quite bright white.
ALSO you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll receive a comprehensive article collection  with the SPI Moves material, the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes from Richard Berg, a set of variants from Campaign magazine and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Great Northern War_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; WotR fopr 2-5 players by Glenn Rahman (of Divine Right fame). AND 3 color at start set up charts I print onto cardstock. well done DIY effort from someone. the one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 12:38:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 23:51:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>100</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box faded on one edge, cards punched and bagged, otherwise unplayed.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 04:31:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 10:37:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for user Ray Regular
Will provide shipping quote later.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 22:15:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 20:43:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>200</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Used: Minor shelf wear to the box from long-term storage. The game and inserts/maps are all in excellent condition. The pieces are punched from their original sheets and carefully sorted into the plastic tray provided. (see photo)
US bidders; S/H for this item will be $25.00 from here in Canada to anywhere in the USA via Canada Post_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Expedited Parcel service - which INCLUDES sufficient insurance coverage!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 16 May 2015 04:32:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 May 2015 03:00:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Tray version. Missing both mini games: Gondor _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Sauron. Unpunched</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 15:59:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 13:31:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39.85</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Missing two _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;chits_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;. Nazgul 8 and Orcs 10-4. Both Brown with orange lettering.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 01:56:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 03:42:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>All components present. Punched and bagged. Excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 19 May 2013 09:03:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 02:12:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Box is solid and square with only mild shelf wear. Game components are used, and there are a couple of places on the maps where they look like they were taped together, and has caused some minor damage on the corners or around the edges. The War of the Ring game rules are photocopies. All other rule books are originals. 
Two missing counters:
Gondor is missing a Harad B-3-Y Cavalry
Sauron is missing Ringwraith 7 </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:20:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 00:22:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>game has been played, but is all accounted for and neatly stored
362311</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 10:41:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 18:00:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>103</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>MIDDLE EARTH version with Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition mounted mapboards. All 3 games punched and verified complete. Plus 112 cards. Rules booklets and charts all present plus I made cardstock copies of the various charts for use in play. very good game components. average standard Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition War of the Ring box OR a less than average Middle Earth Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition box. ALSO you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll receive a comprehensive article collection  with the SPI Moves material, the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement feature article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes from Richard Berg, a set of variants from Campaign magazine and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Great Northern War_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; WotR for 2-5 players by Glenn Rahman (of Divine Right fame). AND 7 color at start set up charts (the middle earth satellite games have 2 setup charts each as well) I color print those onto cardstock. well done DIY effort from someone. the one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:48:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 01:54:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/204889/item/4442884#4442884]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Auction-Boardgames,wargames and Chinese games_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 21:03:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 13:56:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete. Punched. No split corners on the box. No markings.
Additional photos available.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 21:21:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 10:08:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>punched game, complete, some damage to the box, it´s fixed with adhesive tape,  good condition. Please ask for shipping cost. Payment in advance. Payment SEPA transfer via IBAN/BIC or paypal (plus fees). Private sale without warranty.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 22:04:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 15:57:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box wear and showing its age but a great game for its time.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 13:15:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 11:12:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>70</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 20:43:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 23:39:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/215059/item/4924077#4924077]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Quick small auction (Yggdrasil, SSI War of the Ring Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition, Taluva)  with BINs_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 03:19:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 03:53:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/218072/item/5073556#5073556]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Auction ending 12/18.  _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Laid off for the Holidays auction._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;  (US, will ship internationally)_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 16:49:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 14:15:27 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>113</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched MIDDLE EARTH version with 3 sets of unpunched counters. The 112 cards have been separated from the sheets and are like new. Indeed I didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t do the separation but these cards appear as if they were not in sheets as there are no _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;spurs_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; present around the card edges. And I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve housed these A quality cards in a pair of perfect sized boxes for storing and transit (split the deck into two) Rules booklets and charts all present and like new perfect,  Plus I made cardstock copies of the various charts for use in play. Very good coversheet (I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;d frame it as it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s quite attractive and make for a cool decor item in your war cave). ALSO you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll receive a comprehensive article collection  with the SPI Moves material, the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement feature article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes from Richard Berg, a set of variants from Campaign magazine and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Great Northern War_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; WotR for 2-5 players by Glenn Rahman (of Divine Right fame). AND 7 color at start set up charts (the middle earth satellite games have 2 setup charts each as well) I color print those onto cardstock. well done DIY effort from someone. the one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 04:11:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 20:15:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>64.98</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Condition: Box lid is torn _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; taped in 2 corners</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 22:11:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 14:49:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>80</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is the SPI game in the white bookshelf box with the Bakshi movie art cover.  It has the designers edition mounted mapboards.  Game is punched, but 100% complete.  All the counters, cards and mapboards are in mint, like new condition.  The box has no split corner but does exhibit some wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 09:14:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 14:30:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Simpubs White box, *not* Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition so no mounted maps, unpunched, unplayed, cards bagged, no damage, very little wear. Rulebook has been read a few times.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 13:14:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 03:19:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>89</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>NICE BOX very HTF for this title ~ Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition ~ only a couple dozen punched hence; like new set of mounted designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s edition map boards ,of course Like new counters, cards are like new too and separated from sheets well (i.e. no spurs) The rules booklet is excellent, still quite white with the four centre removable pages still attached.
ALSO you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll receive a comprehensive article collection  with the SPI Moves material (3 articles), the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement feature article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes from Richard Berg, a set of variants from Campaign magazine and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Great Northern War_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; WotR for  2-5 players by Glenn Rahman (of Divine Right fame). AND 3 color at start set up charts I print onto cardstock. well done DIY effort from someone. I also cardstock print the standard charts for use during play, maybe even printout a half dozen endurance charts so you can be equiped for play immediately. the one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 19:59:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 06:59:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>400 counters only. a complete set of like new unused counters for the standard War of the Ring game</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 20:05:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:26:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Few counters punched and sorted in tray, most counters remain unpunched.  os shows minimal shelf wear, all corners are intact.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 17:23:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 18:37:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/238228/item/6019453#6019453]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Auction That Ate Milwaukee XII - The Twelfth Cheddar..._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 18:44:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 11:51:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box is square and tight, but well scuffed, especially on the corners. Counters are punched, neatly sorted, and bagged. Boards are tight. Rules were most likely read, but in very good condition (charts still stapled in center). I was not the original purchaser of this one, picked it up at auction. Everything is there for a great player_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s copy.
Add $13.00 for shipping via USPS.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 16:46:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 30 May 2018 19:21:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 16:42:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 18:30:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>150</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Includes both Sauron and Gondor mini-games. Counters for all three games are PUNCHED (nicely) and the WotR cards are SEPARATED. Map is the 4-panel MOUNTED version in Bakshi-cover bookcase edition box. Box in excellent condition - very light wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 16:19:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 02:51:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>111</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched  designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s edition with mounted mapboards. The countersheets are properly printed with still very good color and they_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re thick. Feel more sturdy than typical SPI. Probably due to this game being stored responsibly over the years. Not exposed to moisture nor sunlight. The 112 cards are still in unseparated sheets. Mapboards _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; rules booklet are like new. BOX IS VERY GOOD which is damn HTF for this titleI Plus I made cardstock copies of the various charts for use in play. ALSO you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll receive a comprehensive article collection  with the SPI Moves material, the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement feature article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes from Richard Berg, a set of variants from Campaign magazine and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Great Northern War_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; WotR for 2-5 players by Glenn Rahman (of Divine Right fame). AND 7 color at start set up charts (the middle earth satellite games have 2 setup charts each as well) I color print those onto cardstock. well done DIY effort from someone. the one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 18:47:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 01:41:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>The SPI flat pack is sound, but beat up. The maps are all in nice shape. The rules have been read, but are in good shape. The big campaign game is punched, neatly clipped and played; it is missing one counter, which is the game turn marker. All other components present. Two of the cards have slight tears from being taken out of the sprues. The two folio battle games are unpunched. 
$13 shipping East of the Mississippi except for Illinois, Wisconsin and Minnesota; $18 West of the Mississippi and to Illinois, Wisconsin and Minnesota.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 05:24:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:10:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>92</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition, like new set of mounted de luxe edition map boards , Like new counters albeit punched (verified complete), sorted and ziplock bagged by type. cards are like new (I have two plus reserve decks and replace blemished cards with the best available). The rules booklet is still very good and free of marks, underscoring and/or highlighting, still quite white.
ALSO you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll receive a comprehensive article collection  with the SPI Moves material (3 articles), the Fire _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Movement feature article with designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s notes from Richard Berg, a set of variants from Campaign magazine, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;One Ring to Rule Them All_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; 6 pages from Werbaneth_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Line of Departure variant newsletter and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Great Northern War_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; WotR for  2-5 players by Glenn Rahman (of Divine Right fame). AND 3 color at start set up charts I print onto cardstock. well done DIY effort from someone. I also cardstock print the standard charts for use during play, maybe even printout a half dozen endurance charts so you can be equiped for play immediately. the one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 08:41:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:04:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>45</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Some shelfwear and 2 split corners - see pics.
Otherwise a very decent copy of War of the Ring. Complete and hardly played.
Mounted map.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 01:48:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 14:38:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>The box is beaten up pretty bad -- almost as if this thing is more than 40 years old -- and the set is missing card number 27 for Nazgul #4, but if your interest is as a player, not a collector, then I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll be happy to ship it to a new home. All other pieces are accounted for.</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
