<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="2516">
   <yearpublished>1993</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>2</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>4</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>180</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>180</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>180</maxplaytime>
   <age>12</age>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; War</name>
         
   <description>Man O' War is the game of Raging Sea Battles in the Warhammer World. As an admiral of an ocean-going war fleet you must command your ships - which can be either  squadrons of Ships of the Line or heavily armored Men O' War, in the battle for supremacy of the high seas._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Players choose fleets from the multitude of races of the Warhammer world. Every ship is represented by a template showing individual areas, each with a description of the items (masts, cannons etc.) in those areas - as well as the damage that they can take before being destroyed. Each location has a value that must be rolled to hit that area when attacked, along with another value that can be rolled by the defending player to possibly prevent any damage that might occur. Ships are classified as Ship of the Line (SOL) - which are designed to move as a group of three (each moving and fighting to completion before continuing on with the next ship in the squadron), a Man O' War (MOW)- which are single ships that are much larger, more powerful and crewed by larger numbers than a single SOL classed ship, or finally as an Independent (IND) - which are used individually like a Man O' War but are more in line in strength and abilities to that of a Ship of the Line._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;At the beginning of each turn, players determine Initiative by each rolling a die which determines either who will go 1st in each phase - if the numbers are different, or how the wind direction changes if they both roll the same number. If the wind changes, the initiative roll and resolution is repeated until one player wins the die roll._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Players then conduct the Magic Phase with each Admiral having his Wizard make one spell attempt if desired. If a spell is successful, the other player can try and dispel that cast spell if they have a corresponding type of magic to make the attempt._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Next comes the Battle phase which is based on the previously determined initiative roll and players alternate between phases of Movement/Combat, each choosing a single MOW, IND or SOL Squadron and then conducting movement and making attacks before passing the turn sequence back to their opponent. This process continues until all ships have moved on both sides. Once that has occurred, the turn is over and a series of quick turn ending/record keeping events occurs before moving to the next turn. Game play continues for a predetermined time or until one side is destroyed, surrenders or flees the battlefield._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;There were two separate expansions to the main game. The first was Plaguefleet which added rules and templates for the Chaos fleets of Khorne, Slaanesh, Tzeentch and Nurgle (collectively known as a Plaguefleet), the Skaven and finally the Chaos Dwarfs. This expansion effectively doubled the number of available fleets for the game. This expansion also included color templates for the original 6 races as well (Imperial, Bretonnian, Dwarf, High Elf, Dark Elf and Orc)._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The 2nd expansion Sea of Blood mainly introduced new rules for Airpower, Sea Monsters _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;amp; Beasts and Allies as well as new ships for the Dwarfs and Imperial fleets. The inclusion of the Norse fleet wrapped up the content for this expansion._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Finally, complete rules for an Undead fleet - as well as some expansion rules for a few of the other races, were included in several of the issues of Game Workshop's Citadel Journal magazine._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;A wide variety of miniatures were produced to represent the many ships detailed in the main game and expansion sets but no miniatures were ever officially made for the Undead fleet. Assembling and painting the miniatures gave the game a feeling of being _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;collectible_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; as well as being a hobby in itself. Many players have created customized ships and new ships (and even complete fleets) including rules, ships templates and completed miniatures. The largest collection of these creations is housed at the Yahoo group Sea of Claws._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/evzRB4mk5xIxvPlNTTjZm_AttY8=/fit-in/200x150/pic1540285.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/lkH_W6qjUs8F34Z3whY4wSuKINw=/0x0/pic1540285.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgameartist objectid="9163">Dave Andrews</boardgameartist>
               <boardgameartist objectid="12369">John Blanche</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2072">Dice Rolling</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgameartist objectid="14937">Wayne England</boardgameartist>
               <boardgameversion objectid="155211">English edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1010">Fantasy</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgameversion objectid="434759">French edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameartist objectid="12370">David Gallagher</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="26">Games Workshop Ltd.</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="36574">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! episode 13: Guilty pleasure board games</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                      <boardgamedesigner objectid="695">Andy Jones</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="1028">Bill King</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="4134">Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; War: Plague Fleet</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="4135">Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; War: Sea of Blood</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1047">Miniatures</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1008">Nautical</boardgamecategory>
                      <boardgamedesigner objectid="40">Nigel Stillman</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgameartist objectid="14794">Geoff Taylor</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="5496">Thematic Games</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2079">Variable Phase Order</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2015">Variable Player Powers</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="4664">Wargames</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="4327">Warhammer Fantasy Wargames</boardgamefamily>
             
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="9">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="4" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="6" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="2" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="4" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="1" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="4" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="2" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="3">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="3" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="3">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>711</usersrated>
     <average>7.14206</average>
     <bayesaverage>6.07724</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="1912" bayesaverage="6.07724" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="4664" name="wargames" friendlyname="War Game Rank" value="259" bayesaverage="6.73686" />
              <rank type="family" id="5496" name="thematic" friendlyname="Thematic Rank" value="331" bayesaverage="6.33765" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.62517</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>1003</owned>
     <trading>42</trading>
     <wanting>80</wanting>
     <wishing>187</wishing>
     <numcomments>225</numcomments>
     <numweights>62</numweights>
     <averageweight>2.6613</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 08:04:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 06 Aug 2006 20:17:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This is both Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; War and Plague Fleet in the Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; War box.
The box has some wear from a long shelf life. 
Rulebook, counters and bits are a little worn, but not much.
The 12 plastic ships comes without masts and sails.
All counters and templates are expected to be present.
There are a few _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;wound_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;crew_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;damage_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;blaze_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; counters missing but not very many.
My prefered payment is either Paypal or Western Union
Shipping will be by airmail and will cost 41$ to USA
Feel free to email me other questions or other shipping costs to your country.
I am also selling Sea of Blood. Buy it all and save on shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 01:58:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 11:54:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>70</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Purchased on ebay but probably won_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t play it so someone should have it. Box is buckled worn and split on one corner, I am 99% sure it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s complete other than missing masts for 6 of the twelve ships. The ships are unpainted and 3 blue and 3 red have been removed from their sprue but the other 6 are still in their sprue. Many of the counters are unpunched and apart from the box, everything is in great condition. Looks like the guy I brought it from played it once or twice only.
Buyer to pay for Insurance (optional) but I won_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t be held responsible for uninsured items that get lost in the post (haven_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t lost one yet though).
I will accept Direct Deposit from Australian Buyers</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 02:06:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 01:51:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete. Partially punched. Most of the plastic ships are still on sprues. A feeble attempt was made to paint a couple ship, but not much progress.
I am not the original owner of the game and don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t know where the game_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s been stored for these past many years. I suspect a basement as I detect a feint basement smell. Box is in good shape, although quite faded.
Also included with this game is one Imperial Great Ship. Unpainted and unassembled (see picture in my gallery). The ship is missing one of the masts. No original packaging.
Shipping is $12. I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll ship for free if you purchase this and the Sea of Blood expansion together. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 23:12:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:38:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For GeekAuction: User artfuldodge2</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 17:22:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 03 May 2009 23:40:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>100</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Two core sets worth of rules, terrain, counters, galleys, etc. Also includes 30+ mixed Bretonnian, Empire and Elf ships. Also a few Dark Elf, Dwarf and Orc ships, plus flying units for Elves. Ships in various states of construction/painting. Spare masts and flag sheets included. Most of Sea of Blood also included.
Paypal or Direct Deposit.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 14:42:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 13:44:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>55</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.
Box minor shelf wear.
Any questions just ask.
Have other expansions also available.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 17:03:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 17:40:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>500</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is a lot consisting of the base game, the Plague Fleet and Sea of Blood expansions, White Dwarf #167, 55 painted/assembled ship/flyer models, and two opened but plain original-box sets consisting of Orc Bigchukkas and Dwarf War Balloons.
*****SALE HAS ALREADY BEEN FINALIZED WITH USER BoB3K*****</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 03:47:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 21:06:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>62</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Played, missing a few pieces. Outside of the occasional info marker, one of the two Amethyst markers is missing. One of the displays (Imperial) is missing. I am uncertain how many island pieces are supposed to be present. The twelve ships that come with the game are in poor condition.  The box is in fair condition. Lastly, there is a CD included with various player aid documentation.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 14:17:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 17:55:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Extra Ships for Sale
There are 6 war galleys for each of the Empire and Pirate fleets. Ships nicely
painted and assembled, but some masts will need re-gluing.
Some additional boxes with painted minis, one with 3 assembled and well painted Imperial War Galleys.
Additionally there are 3 metal Imperial Wolfships and 1 metal Imperial Greatship.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 01:59:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 03:49:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>90</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Complete, contents in near perfect condition. Box in okay shape.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 21:03:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 18:24:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>English Edition. 
Never played with only small damage on the box.
Shipping Costs (Germany): € 4,00 </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 10:54:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 14:15:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>75</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m selling this bundled with the rare Sea of Blood expansion, and three _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Bretonnian Corsairs_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; miniatures. One turning template and one plastic Pirate Wargalley is missing. As far as I know there are no other missing pieces, but as I haven_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t got a component list, I cannot guarantee this. Complete listing of contents available on request.
Cardboard components generally in very good condition, box a bit worn on the edges. Miniatures are glued a bit inexpertly, and some masts are broken (see pictures).
Shipping to europe will be 46 €, shipping to the US will be 65 €</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 00:55:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 01:27:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>MAN O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; WAR Rulebook
SEA OF BLOOD Rulebook
PLAGUE FLEET Rulebook
Tons of Counters, Ship Templates, Cards, Range Rulers, Wreck and Debris Markers, Fleet Lists, Terrain Pieces, Magic Decks, Sea Monster Templates, 
almost 8 lbs of cardboard and rulebooks.  Everything appears to be punched but in unplayed condition.  Many cards are protected in card sleeves.
*** No ships included ***
I have more pictures of collection available - email c.rett@hotmail.com
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 01:53:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 01:20:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Missing box. Reserved for mindg4m3</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 20:23:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 17:17:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>100</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>unpunched, complete
box is a bit smashed
more pictures available upon request</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 05:42:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 21:40:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>69</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>RARE _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; LONG OUT OF PRINT - This is a great deal for this completely UNPUNCHED and unplayed copy of this great Games Workshop classic. 
Pieces were hand counted to verify 100% complete, all are new in the box unused.  
Box is in good shape for its age and very solid with very little wear, the lid is dished from storage though with creases on both sides and also one on the back. 
Can send pictures of anything if wanted.
Will be packed VERY carefully before shipping (see my feedback) feel free to ask questions or for a shipping quote. Shipping will be actual cost quoted by Post Office only nothing more and the method of your choice. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 15:37:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 21:29:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for auction winner _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Texas gamer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 15:14:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 01:15:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale also includes Sea of Blood and Plague Fleet!!!  All materials are present, tossed in the original Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; War box.  Everything  is present, including the plastic ships.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 20:58:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 22:02:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Auction Win for:
Jeremy Fridy
(Freitag)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 05:11:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 06:19:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>222</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For neoshmengi only!!! Includes Man O War + two expansions $100, Antics $70, String Railway $15, Spyrium $25, 2 de Mayo $12.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 06:15:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 14:16:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>270</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/188929/item/3803839#3803839]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Man O_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;War Auction. Get your fleets here!! - Ends 4/13 - Shipping from 94596_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
For Jeff Coon ONLY!
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 06 Nov 2005 19:05:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 18:31:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched and complete, except for 1 mast sprue. Ship minis unassembled and unpainted. Components in very good condition. Fair amount of shelf wear on box.
Shipping costs:
Europe - €16,50 (tracked); €18,50 (tracked + insured)
Rest of the world - €25,30 (tracked), €27,30 (tracked + insured)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 23:23:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 17:24:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Includes Dwarf Monitors and Dwarf Nautilus.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 22:28:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 17:55:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>250</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>This auction provides 
Two copies of man o war games,
Two copies of Plague Fleet,
Two copies of Sea of Blood.
All counters, cards, ship templates, terrain included. Everything is inside two man o war and one plague fleet box ( see images).
Included are one copy of rule book for each of man o war, plague fleet  and sea of blood.
Plastic war galleys are no longer present instead there are various metal models
(See photo)- you need to glue the sails back. You get dark elves ships, five empire war galleys, six wolf ships, skaven ships, i see dwarf and high elf ship and nurgle ship.
I also have undead ship templates included.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 15:45:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 15:38:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>85</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>some lead miniatures as substitute for the Basic game and  BRETONNIAN-GALLION-set and NURGLE-PLAGUECRUSHERS-set included.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 23:57:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 21:46:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>60</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This game is missing the plastic ships. 
the box has no damage. All the counters and terrain are present.</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
