<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="3986">
   <yearpublished>1975</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>2</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>4</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>180</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>180</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>180</maxplaytime>
   <age>12</age>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">Battle for Germany</name>
         
   <description>Battle for Germany game is small, it only takes about three to four hours to play for players of normal skill and luck. The game starts in December of 1944 with the Ardennes Offensive (a variant allows the German player to skip this and save his strength). As a two-player game, it is interesting in that each player plays both an Allied army (Western Allies or Soviet Union) AND a German army (Western Front or Eastern Front). This forces each player to play offense and defense. The player playing the Western Allies and Eastern Germans has a very challenging task. The Western Germans have good defensive terrain (the Rhine river and Westwall defenses), while the Eastern Germans have weak units, a long front, very poor defensive terrain and they face a large Soviet and Yugoslav army. The only real advantage enjoyed by the East German player is the lack of victory points to be gained in the East, and the slow Soviet replacement rate. The Western Alllied units are very fast moving, but they don't usually get a chance to exploit this until the very end of the game (at best)._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The map is the same size as most SPI Quadrigames or folio games and has similar graphics. Cities are rated as 1 or 2 victory points, with Berlin worth 10. A line down the middle of Germany cannot be crossed (in the 2-player game), which makes Berlin the only city which can be captured by the Western Allies or the Soviets (ahistorical, but essential to the game's concept). Units are corps for the Germans and Western Allies and corps, armies, or fronts for the Soviet player. Each unit is rated for attack, defense and movement. Combat is decided by an odds-based combat results table and a die roll. Combat results include various combinations of retreat and elimination (there are no step losses, disruption or anything like this). Eliminated units can be replaced, but very slowly and (for some players) with the weakest available unit coming back first._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The game includes variants for 3- and 4-player versions where the Germans are played by 1 or 2 players, and a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;red star/ white star_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; scenario where the Western Allies and Soviets fight it out with some help from the remnants of the German army._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/AvB_hQfZ8k10pJz1NFOijCoyGF4=/fit-in/200x150/pic81914.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/uAS-PZeO_8eUp9WT43yE1D7jZ_U=/0x0/pic81914.jpg</image>
      
                   <boardgamedesigner objectid="1269">Michael Bennighof</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgameversion objectid="147103">Command Japan magazine edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="10643">Country: Germany</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgameversion objectid="43082">Decision boxed edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="102">Decision Games (I)</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2072">Dice Rolling</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="1081">Jim Dunnigan</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2026">Hex-and-Counter</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="1391">Hobby Japan</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="67759">Hobby Japan edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="3133">Kokusai-Tsushin Co., Ltd. (国際通信社)</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameartist objectid="20435">Christine Lockwood</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="3231">Magazine: Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgameartist objectid="1256">David McElhannon</boardgameartist>
               <boardgameartist objectid="140">Mark Simonitch</boardgameartist>
               <boardgameartist objectid="1030">Redmond A. Simonsen</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2070">Simulation</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="120">SPI (Simulations Publications, Inc.)</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameversion objectid="58776">SPI collector_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="31524">SPI folio edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="29011">Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics magazine edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="4664">Wargames</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1049">World War II</boardgamecategory>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="18">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="10" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="4" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="14" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="7" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="10" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="7" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="12" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="4">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="2" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="1" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="1" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="6">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>488</usersrated>
     <average>7.11238</average>
     <bayesaverage>5.95051</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="2394" bayesaverage="5.95051" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="4664" name="wargames" friendlyname="War Game Rank" value="280" bayesaverage="6.69586" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.2473</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>1062</owned>
     <trading>49</trading>
     <wanting>38</wanting>
     <wishing>108</wishing>
     <numcomments>318</numcomments>
     <numweights>70</numweights>
     <averageweight>2.1143</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 17:34:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 27 Mar 2006 19:27:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>19</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games boxed version of the game. Game has been just opened, but never played. All components unpunched.
Shipping at actual cost dependend on destination, total weight and method of shipment chosen.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 28 Jan 2007 01:27:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 28 Jan 2007 04:18:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>11.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>For sale here is one brand new, factory sealed, boxed wargame.
Battle for Germany is an excellent intro level wargame.
Buy it here for the great price of $11.99.
USA trackable shipping $4.95 Canada air $6.95 Europe air $9.95.
Buy more than one game from me and save on shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 05 Feb 2007 03:11:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 05 Feb 2007 14:47:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T #50.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 05 Mar 2007 18:10:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 18:59:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>17</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games edition. Box shows almost no wear. Inside everything there in great condition. All counters unpunched.
Shipping at actual cost dependend on destination, total weight and method of shipment chosen.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 17 May 2007 15:25:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 17:57:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Played once.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 16:48:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 11 Oct 2007 20:09:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>8</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>SPI version.  The game is complete with rules, map, and all counters.  This does not include the magazine that the game originally came in.  Counters are punched and in very good shape.  There are some markings made on a handful of map hexes indicating forts for one of the alternate scenarios. I will combine on shipping for multiple items so check out my other games for sale. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 20 May 2008 05:04:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 02:39:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Counters punched. Components in excellent condition. Comes with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T #50.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 31 May 2008 17:17:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 08:37:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>22</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Battle for Germany (Decision Games)
Condition: mint in shrinkwrap
Payment methods:
-France: personal check
-Europe: bank transfer or Paypal
-Rest of the World: Paypal
Shipping charges : depending on the number of games you buy from my list (please feel free to ask me for a quotation):
- 1 game: you will pay for the full shipping charges.
- 2 games: you will only pay for half of the shipping charges.
- 3 games or more: shipping charges will be free.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 16:37:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 18:29:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched. Includes magazine.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 04:12:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 20:44:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>13</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For sale to lesulm1 only, please. (From BGTG Auction #1, http://www.boardgamegeek.com/geeklist/33377)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 22:46:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 16:06:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This auction is for one brand new, factory sealed, boxed, wargame.
The classic, Battle for Germany.
Buy it here for the discounted price of $14.95.
Shipping: USA trackable $4.95 Canand $7.95 Everywhere else $13.95.
Paypal preferred.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 00:17:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 21:27:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is the original SPI magazine version of this game.
counters unpunched, map and magazine in excellent unused condition
magazine cover has some creasing.
comes with Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics issue #50 - May/Jun 1975.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 07:20:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 03:57:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>54</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>The Battle for Germany, a game that re-enacts the last days of World War Two, 1945. 
This game is completely mint and unused, counters unpunched. 
As an added bonus, comes w/a mint copy of Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics Magazine #50, containing strategy articles about this game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 00:55:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 09:55:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>SPI version. Punched. Complete. Includes mag.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 05:38:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 13:02:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Boxed DG version. 
The game starts in December of 1944 with the Ardennes Offensive (a variant allows the German player to skip this and save his strength). As a two-player game, it is interesting in that each player plays both an Allied army (Western Allies or Soviet Union) AND a German army (Western Front or Eastern Front). This forces each player to play offense and defense. 
Condition Notes:
Box has ever so slight dishing and minimal shelf wear.
Punched.  Clipped.  Rules have some notations.
Shipping Notes:
You are welcome to come to Community Game Night (see http://www.boardgamegeek.com/thread/127654) and pick up your game in person and pay $0 for shipping.
Yes, we will gladly combine orders to reduce your per item shipping costs. (To see other items to add to your order see http://www.boardgamegeek.com/geekstore.php3?action=viewuser_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;username=RoamDog). In fact, if you buy enough the shipping costs will be FREE. 
Please provide a contact phone number--this is ONLY in case there are shipping issues--I am NOT planning to call you. Also, if you would like tracking information, also provide a direct/external (non-BGG) email address.
Finally, if at all possible, please provide a business (rather than a residential) address (this will expedite delivery) and let us know that the address you are providing is a business address. 
Payment Notes:
US buyers: 
USPS money order is preferred. 
Western Union transfer is also acceptable.
However, I can also take a Paypal payment if you have _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt; 50 positive references on BGG. But the only type of Paypal payment that I can accept is one funded by a Paypal balance or an immediate bank transfer. I cannot take a Paypal payment that is funded via credit card. 
(Also see the note at the bottom regarding Paypal payments impact on the discounted price). 
If the receiver elects to not pay extra for insurance (totally up to the receiver) then the receiver agrees to assume responsibility for lost or damaged packages.
Non-US buyers:
Western Union wire transfer (see www.westernunion.com) is the only acceptable form of payment.
Non-US buyers--Please also note that the shipping charge will be outrageously high. Probably high enough that it does not make sense to purchase this item from me. I have no control over this.
Insurance will also be REQUIRED (at receiver_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s expense) for shipments to non-US addresses. Receivers outside the US must also agree to assume ALL responsibility for taxes, tariffs, customs duties, etc. If these terms are not acceptable, please do not order from me.
**Note that the offered price is the discounted price for a cash (cash, money order, western union) payment. The non-discounted price (i.e. paypal payments) will be 3.0% plus 30 cents higher. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 18 May 2009 20:13:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 19 May 2009 02:15:27 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
 By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich  collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but  some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that  Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
 This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual  battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
 The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 May 2009 20:44:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 25 May 2009 21:12:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 28 May 2009 18:33:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 04:54:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 15:32:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 07:59:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 13:40:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 13:29:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 16:51:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 01:27:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 14:13:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 16:43:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 14:33:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 23:17:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 12:50:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 07 Nov 2009 01:55:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 17:04:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 20:52:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>In very good condition. The box, the counters, the rules, the map,etc everything as new.
Take a look at the pictures: http://www.flickr.com/photos/kopiki/sets/72157622776081200/</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 17:30:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 19:16:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 01:15:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 03:05:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This game has some shelf wear, but the game is in great condition.
If you use paypal to pay, I ask that you share the cost of paypal fees by adding 2% to the total cost.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 15:53:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 02:30:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 23:33:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:37:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games (DCG 3003)
By mid-December, 1944, the question was how many more lives would be lost before the Third Reich collapsed. In the west, combined armies of France, Britain, and the United States stood on the very border of the German nation. acing them stood the same divisions that four years before had swept all before them. In the east, the massive Soviet forces were about to launch their winter offensive and drive the Wehrmacht to within 30 miles of Berlin. Numerically the German Army was overwhelmed, but some of their shattered divisions were still the best in the world. It was with these crack forces that Germany made one last offensive into the Ardennes. It was a gamble, and it failed. 
This game is a simulation of a real-world event. It is played on a map that is a simplified terrain reproduction of the actual battlefield. A grid of hexagons printed over the map is used to regulate movement much as the squares on a chess board. 
The pieces in the game represent the actual military units that took part in the historical conflict. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 04:25:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 22:21:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s/Collector_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s edition with mounted map. Game components are excellent as are the verified 100 counters punched. 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 15:36:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 21:42:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>19.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>2nd Edition by Decision Games. Punched, but compelte and only played once. Excellent condition! Includes printed copy of the errata. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 03:41:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 03:04:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Packed in a flat plastic box.  Includes rules/map.  Chits are punched but appear complete.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 04:34:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 17:55:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched, verified complete and includes a fine condition S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue and ALL published articles on BfG. Including the Alpenfestung variant (got a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;cool_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; Swastika counter for the bavarian redoubt) and the pair of HTF Battleplan variants</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 12 May 2011 12:52:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 09:25:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game. S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T Magazine Edition 1975. Ziplock bag lightly discolored
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling – Priority Mail excl. Insurance:
Switzerland: CHF 3.-- 
Europe: USD 9.--
US/ Canada/ Others Overseas: USD 13.--
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 22 May 2011 21:23:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 22:01:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>The game is punched and very clean. It is missing one Russian 6-4-6 counter. S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T magazine not included.
PayPal only outside of the US please. Shipping is USPS at cost, no extra fee_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 09:34:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 17:50:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>New unpunched game, Ziplock bag lightly discolored
Shipping_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;Handling – Priority Mail excl. Insurance:
Switzerland: CHF 3.-- 
Europe: USD 9.--
US/ Canada/ Others Overseas: USD 13.--
We will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 18:48:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 18:00:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, played.  COUNTERS IN GAME TRAY/ GAME IN GENERIC WHITE BOX.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 22:59:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 17:57:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched and complete game in excellent condition</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 22:07:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 19:08:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, verified complete and includes a fine condition S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue and ALL published articles on BfG. Including the Alpenfestung variant (got a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;cool_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; Swastika counter for the bavarian redoubt) and the pair of HTF Battleplan variants
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 18:04:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 16:14:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>1975 Collector_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition. Boxed with mounted map. Box scuffed and worn, components very good. Extra paper map included.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 01:56:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 02:06:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>SPI boxed edition.
Box slightly worn.
Board in excellent shape.
Rulebook complete and unmarked.
Counters punched, all present (I counted them personally).
Includes plastic tray, SPI minicatalog, original die, one typed sheet of errata , and a large ziploc bag.
Price and shipping details negotiable.
If you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re in the US, the Post Office has a flat rate box for 10.95 that goes anywhere in the lower 48. If that_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s acceptable, we_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll calculate shipping as $11. 
I always use delivery confirmation.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 00:54:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 08:23:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>23</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 20:06:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 21:31:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Solely for Auction Winner Chris Tham (chriswtham)!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 12:39:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 16:50:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>13.75</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Vintage S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T 50 published by SPI in 1975.  Magazine, game map, and counters in _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Very Good_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; condition.  Game map and magazine have minimal wear.  Counters are punched but complete.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 17:22:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 10:36:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched - never used</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 23:39:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 20:06:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>29</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched
Shipping Germany  4 Euro
Shipping World          7 Euro
PayPal plus 1 Euro
Money transfer via IBAN/BIC preferred
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 20:23:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 17:44:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 10 May 2013 17:27:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 15:00:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched verified complete with VG S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 00:09:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 17:33:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>16</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched and bagged, with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T magazine #50
An average played copy. All components in fine condition.
Magazine in poor condition. It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s intact and not damaged but covers show a lot of wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 15:08:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 05:37:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>26</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched but a dozen counters came loose. They are accounted for and ziplock bagged. With excellent S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more. The one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 04:58:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 09:58:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>3</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>This is for the magazine only, no game is included.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 02:48:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 16:44:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This is the boxed DG edition, new in the shrink.
CONUS shipping is USPS priority. I will tack on 4-6% to offset paypal and BGG charges, less if you pay by check or MO. I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m willing to ship international, but it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s very, very expensive (usually over $50US, so geekmail me first).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 16:01:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 12:07:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, complete, excellent condition
5 pounds postage to UK, 8 pounds to Europe</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 19:41:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 03:51:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T magazine edition. Punched. Game only, no magazine, in excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:30:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 13:13:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Decision Games, Complete in excellent condition. Game is out of print. Buyer to pay via Pay Pal or Money Order.  Buyer to pay actual shipping.  Will combine shipping if other items purchased.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 13:35:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 07:33:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/175628/item/3304692#3304692]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;Crate Full of Games Auction_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Combined shipping is $21 total.
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 22:26:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 13:29:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The Battle for Germany from S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T #50 by SPI. No magazine. Counters are verified complete; components are in good condition. Rulebook is stamped w/original owner_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s name (state university) and counters have their setup hexes hand-printed on backside. Ziploc. Free shipping</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 11 May 2014 05:24:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 17:47:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>27</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>unpunched, comes with the mag, S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T #50 NOt the boxed version.
Will ship to Australia, NZ and UK but be aware, shipping is $20 for one mag and weight must be under 500grams 
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 15:18:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 02:11:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>16.94</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.  Decision Games boxed version.  Contents verified complete and in like new condition.  Its a classic from the mid 70s revamped by Decision.  Smaller folio game with very interesting mechanics.  Box is square and straight with no dings, doinks or creases.  Some dishing, edge wear and corner rubs.  Worldwide shipping and will be packed well.  All forms of negotiable instruments considered.  Combine ship with multiple purchases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 00:22:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 22:08:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>9.5</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>In plastic bag. Punched and clipped. Includes map, rule book and d6. 
Contact me for shipping cost, but will likely be around $3-4.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 08:36:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 20:02:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched verified complete with VG S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Almost like new with bright white counter backsides, near perfect map and excellent rules and S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T. PLUS Includes a comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 13:34:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 17:42:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>33</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Battle for Germany - Boxed Edition (Decision Games)
Condition: mint in shrinkwrap
Payment methods: 
-France: personal check
-Europe: bank transfer or Paypal
-Rest of the World: Paypal
Shipping charges :
-France : 6 euros
-Europe : 8 euros
-Rest of the World : 12 euros</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 04:32:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 05:31:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>8</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>DG edition, no box, punched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 14:22:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 15:41:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched verified complete with VG S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Almost like new with bright white counter backsides, near perfect map and excellent rules and S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T. PLUS Includes a comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 15:36:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 05:26:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Designer Edition in box with mounted board. Clean, punched copy. Box shows normal wear for age.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 16:05:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 14 May 2015 00:20:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T #50; light wear.
Punched not clipped; complete with 1 drawn GE replacement counter.
Rules detached, unmarked.  light wear.
Map VG
US shipping via USPS first class:  $2.45</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 02:40:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 03:45:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For Bob Aarhus only. 
$6 for shipping for a total of $26.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 08:10:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 22:02:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24.45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched verified complete with VG S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Very good counters ( bright white backsides ), near perfect map and excellent rules booklet. PLUS Includes a comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2. And the usual  strategy articles covering both the SPI release and the Decision Games_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; version. AND I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve even made a cardstock TEC and CRT chart with maps and various End of the Reich minutiae on the reverse side. The one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 16:09:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 02:28:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrinkwrapped
Price may be negotiable if purchased with one or more of my sale items
Feel free to look over my entire BGG collection as nearly everything can be available for purchase
PRESOLD TO BGG USER THEELDEREYE
SOLD WITH SPI SPIES!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 May 2015 19:57:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 20:26:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Played a few times, but in very good conditions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 12:58:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 12:36:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>24.99</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Counters have been clipped</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 04:31:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 20:17:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unplayed, unpunched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 13:33:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 15:39:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrink wrap
PayPal or US Postal Money Order
Other methods of payment may be accepted but contact me before ordering.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 20:53:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 17:02:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>All components present
$6.10 shipping via USPS Priority</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 12:22:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 21:14:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched; verified complete; no S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T magazine.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 16:55:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 21:23:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>29.9</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>never opened
minor dent on box</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 23:52:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 21:56:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39.45</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>(RESERVED for a particular buyer until August)  Unpunched Kerry Andersen_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s custom die cut counter set (112 count) with a Designer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition box and mounted mapboard (one of the last remaining items from my own original collection from the 70s) and a very excellent rules booklet plus an average condition S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T 50. These custom counters retain the same numerical values and NATO symbols, but the colors are changed from the original SPI. The basic Wehrmacht units are slightly altered from gray to a feldgrau (green-gray) While the 6 SS are now black of course and the pair of Fallschirmjager/Luftwaffe korps are a light blue. American units remain drab green but the 6 British counters are now differentiated as a light orange and the 2 Canadian corps are a orange-brown. The 2 Free French are dark blue and the Polish corp is white with red numerals (cool looking given the Polish red/white flag colors). The Soviets are a light brown with red numerals. The 4 Yugoslavian are a darker brown with yellow numerals. The Soviet fielded Polish army is the same light brown as the Soviet counters but has yellow numerals and finally the Bulgarian army is a likewise light brown but with green numerals. I imagine the appearance of the game in play with these counters is quite attractive. Were these punched I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;d learn the rules again in 30 minutes and set it up solo with the Alpenfestung variant and have at it. Speaking of...PLUS Includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant, RedStar/WhiteStar2, Nazi super weapons and about half a dozen strategy articles covering both versions. I even have these white flak counters from Air War that match the War in Europe flak symbols that would make for a cool Flak Tower/Bunker variant like the pair in Berlin (_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;the Zoo_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;). Maybe give each Allied player one to setup where he wishes. e.g. the Soviet player builds the Zoo in the Ruhr area and the Western Allied player places his in Breslau. +1 to defense or a DRM. this ad has taken long enough. pics when I can. The one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:43:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 16:53:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28.72</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 20:38:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 18:27:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics Issue 50 complete with unpunched game: Battle for Germany.
CONDITION: Game complete, unpunched and like new in a new ziploc bag. The Magazine has slight cover wear and creasing.
POSTAGE COST:
UK postage: £4.00
European Postage: £8.00
Rest of World Postage: £11.50
Australia _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; New Zealand: £12.00</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 20:05:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 13:56:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 19:37:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 14:07:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrink wrap_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br /_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;PayPal or US Postal Money Order_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br /_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Other methods of payment may be accepted but contact me before ordering.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 23:50:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 14:29:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched with excellent S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more. The one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 21:52:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 16:08:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This item was once part of the Avalon Hill research library of games.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 20:01:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 13:26:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>The game is new in shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 17:29:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 22:06:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>1994 Decision Games boxed edition.  Unpunched and like-new.
Shipping within the U.S. will be by USPS priority mail unless otherwise noted or arranged.  USPS insurance will be used on all shipments worth more than $100 and is optional on others. 
Payment can be made by PayPal or by Amazon eGift card.  If you want to pay by PayPal and prefer to get a formal PayPal invoice before paying let me know and I will send you one.
I will happily combine shipping on multiple items.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 19:38:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 07 May 2017 14:04:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>UK shipping £3
Free collection from Brighton, UK</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 01:19:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 14:56:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Includes S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T 50
game has been punched and played
shipping - Flat rate envelope</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 28 May 2017 16:23:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:54:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics Issue 50 complete with unpunched game: Battle for Germany.
CONDITION: Game complete, unpunched and like new in a new ziploc bag. The Magazine has slight cover wear and creasing.
POSTAGE COST:
UK postage: £4.00
European Postage: £7.50
Rest of World Postage: £11.50
Australia _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; New Zealand: £12.00</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 16:14:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 03:22:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. Includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more. $4 domestic shipping media mail ~ unpunched magazine games I can ship media mail</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 06:16:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 16:53:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24.98</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Edition: SPI  Strategy _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Tactics Edition</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 16:43:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 20:40:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched Decision Games with still fine box. PLUS Includes comprehensive article collection that covers both this version and the previous SPI version. For SPI we have two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant, RedStar/WhiteStar2, Nazi super weapons and about half a dozen strategy articles. For the DG version we have a replay and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Advanced Rules_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; plus an additional scenario and the Paper Wars review/commentary.The one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 22:39:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:03:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17.44</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Allies are punched and clipped, but the Axis are UNPUNCHED.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 06:54:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 11:15:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 08:17:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:16:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too.very nice unpunched too with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T cover smooth and clear same goes for the map and rules booklet Includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 and more. $4 domestic shipping media mail ~ unpunched magazine games I can ship media mail</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 17:57:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 16:41:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched, counters clipped with setup numbers written on back. Box has bowing and scuffing.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 03:43:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 16:15:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>36</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched, verified complete, very good Collector_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Edition box, mounted mapboard and rules booklet. Counters have some usage wear but not _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;high use_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;. PLUS a very good S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T 50, VG but for three hole punch through the issue. AND I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve made a set of DTP counters with updated graphics/colors (more differentiation between for example Yugoslavia and the Soviets) mounted and cut ready for use when you want to try a different look. FINALLY includes an article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant, RedStar/WhiteStar2, Nazi super weapons and about half a dozen strategy articles covering both versions. I even have these white flak counters from Air War that match the War in Europe flak symbols that would make for a cool Flak Tower/Bunker variant like the pair in Berlin (_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;the Zoo_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;). Maybe give each Allied player one to setup where he wishes. e.g. the Soviet player builds the Zoo in the Ruhr area and the Western Allied player places his in Breslau. +1 to defense or a DRM. this ad has taken long enough. Everybody likes this game. The stairway to heaven of wargames</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 12:23:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 14:55:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Hello, I need to sell my collection due to space problems ((((
The game is punched and was played once. The box got some spots due to age.
Photos are available on request</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 04:36:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 07:36:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched  _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; verified Decision Games with a still nice box. PLUS Includes comprehensive article collection that covers both this version and the previous SPI version. For SPI we have two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant, RedStar/WhiteStar2, Nazi super weapons and about half a dozen strategy articles. For the DG version we have a replay and _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Advanced Rules_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; plus an additional scenario and the Paper Wars review/commentary.The one to buy to play</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 04:33:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 15:31:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched with S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T issue too. nice unpunched with the green two page subscriber insert present. Plus includes comprehensive article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant and RedStar/WhiteStar2 scenario and about a half dozen more tactics _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; strategy articles. $4 domestic shipping media mail ~ unpunched magazine games I can ship media mail</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 02:54:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 02:26:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Counters are punched, but complete.
Plus postage.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 03:09:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 15:10:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched and unplayed.
Plus postage.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 13:31:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 14:24:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Counters unclipped. Light pencil marking on map for Red Star/White Star deployment, pen notes on TRC of effects. Back of Counters has W or E in pen. Other than this superficial stuff I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;d have called it Very Good condition. Mails as large letter.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 03:07:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 17 May 2018 10:55:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched and unplayed.
Including an extra copy of the magazine.
Plus postage.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 04:28:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 23 May 2018 15:24:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>unpunched custom die cut counters (high quality I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m impressed), average SPI rules, very good SPI/S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T map,  includes an article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant, RedStar/WhiteStar2, Nazi super weapons and about half a dozen strategy articles covering both versions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 23:18:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:05:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>12</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T magazine edition. Includes the game and the magazine. Used condition. Two counters are missing, which have been replaced by home made copies.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 02:20:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 16:16:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>24.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched and in perfect condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 03:25:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 16:37:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>punched sorted shelf ware</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 21:00:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:26:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched, played a few times. Looks pretty good after all these years.
Includes magazine.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:26:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 16:42:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.95</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 03:00:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 19:40:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>very good punched and verified. counters high quality like new albeit punched, very good SPI/S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T map,  includes an article collection with the two Battleplan variant scenarios and the Moves_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Alpenfestung_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; variant, RedStar/WhiteStar2, Nazi super weapons and about half a dozen strategy articles covering both versions.</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
