<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="4090">
   <yearpublished>1986</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>1</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>2</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>240</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>240</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>240</maxplaytime>
   <age>12</age>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">2nd Fleet</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Second Fleet</name>
         
   <description>2nd Fleet is a refinement of Victory Games (I) popular Sixth Fleet game system, and examines the strengths and weaknesses of the Soviet Red Banner Northern Fleet and the US Second Fleet and its NATO allies in future conflict for control of the North Atlantic and Arctic Oceans. Players are placed in command of the opposing superpower fleets. The mighty aircraft carriers and escorting capital ships must be protected from the devastating firepower of modern missiles, torpedoes, and bomb attacks. Attack submarines threaten the enemy task forces and replenishment convoys while searching out their submerged rivals. Limited air assets must be carefully assigned to combat air patrols, long-range strategic missions and attack strikes. 2nd Fleet, with its multitude of options and strategies, is one of today's most realistic recreations of modern naval warfare on the high seas._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Each 8 hour game turn is broken into 3 distinct phases (sub, surface, and air) and each player takes turns choosing which phase they wish to conduct. Ex. if the US player chooses _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;Air_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;, they conduct all bombing, shipping strikes, anti-sub, and interception actions for all their aircraft._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Players also use their units to attempt to _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;detect_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; enemy forces so that an attack can be made. Ships and aircraft are always detected once a unit moves close enough to them, but players have to roll to try to detect subs._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Optional rules include nuclear weapons and logistics._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;About 10 scenarios are included which range from about 60 minutes (for Introductory Scenarios) to 3 to 6 hours (for Intermediate Scenarios) to 20 or more hours (for the Advanced Scenario)._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Part of Victory Games Fleet Series._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/f3klNHBKxpOx852tgyhiQH_9z0k=/fit-in/200x150/pic147226.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/l_gRJZYCFiTdVr_iqUkT3ylF1e0=/0x0/pic147226.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamedesigner objectid="673">Joseph M. Balkoski</boardgamedesigner>
                      <boardgamefamily objectid="11966">Country: Russia</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="14835">Country: USA</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2072">Dice Rolling</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgameversion objectid="23871">First edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="106">Fleet Series</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2026">Hex-and-Counter</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="1391">Hobby Japan</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="28050">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! episode 10: Gateway games</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgameartist objectid="15063">Ted Koller</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1069">Modern Warfare</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1008">Nautical</boardgamecategory>
                      <boardgameartist objectid="13649">James Talbot</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="123">Victory Games (I)</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="4664">Wargames</boardgamesubdomain>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="9">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="7" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="4" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="4">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="4" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="7">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>512</usersrated>
     <average>7.23837</average>
     <bayesaverage>5.98222</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="2258" bayesaverage="5.98222" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="4664" name="wargames" friendlyname="War Game Rank" value="234" bayesaverage="6.78341" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.39058</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>1274</owned>
     <trading>53</trading>
     <wanting>43</wanting>
     <wishing>90</wishing>
     <numcomments>225</numcomments>
     <numweights>86</numweights>
     <averageweight>3.407</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Nov 2003 23:14:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 Apr 2004 16:34:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 31 Mar 2004 23:30:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 22 Aug 2004 04:48:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game appears complete and in excellent condition. Pictures available upon request.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 11:34:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 21 Nov 2004 19:33:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Complete, punched, great player_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s copy.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 18 Oct 2004 17:05:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 14 Nov 2004 12:31:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Played once, 50% unpunched. All counters, maps, documentation included. Box has light shelf wear, no tears.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 07 Jan 2005 05:16:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 06 Feb 2005 13:29:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>6</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Missing 10 counters.  Everything is in very good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 05 Apr 2005 05:33:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 20 May 2005 15:08:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Counters punched and sorted into counter trays.  Game is complete with all components in excellent condition.  A small amount of shelf wear on one corner of the box.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 11 Nov 2005 16:03:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 Oct 2006 14:35:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>All counters have been accounted for and are in the storage tray.  None of the logistic sheets have been used.
A non-credit card Paypal payment is highly preferred.  I am only shipping to locations in the U.S. using UPS Ground.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 02 Feb 2007 21:57:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 31 May 2007 17:07:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, complete.  Moderate wear on the box, heavier around the edges.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 12 Mar 2007 04:32:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 27 Apr 2007 23:24:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in shrinkwrap.  </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 04 May 2007 14:00:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 25 May 2007 10:26:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>17.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>2nd Fleet: Modern Naval Combat in the North Atlantic
1986 edition - Victory Games, Inc.
This game is in very good shape, and was played only twice.
Contents:
Rules Booklet
Counters: 50% Unpunched; punched 50% in storage tray
2 Charts and Tables Booklets
Pad of Logistics Rosters
2 Deployment/Reinforcement Cards
1 10-sided Die
Ships USPS Priority Mail; $ depends on buyer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s zipcode.  Ships no later than next business day after payment clears.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 21:28:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 02:27:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, missing 30 markers (See below).  Everything is in very good condition.
MISSING:
15 x NATO Detection markers (out of 30)
15 x Soviet Detection markers (out of 30)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 19:36:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 16:24:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, except 4 counters which fell out in a batch in the box. $10 shipping. Please pay with check or money order.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 07:27:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 01:58:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>21</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game complete, never played, unpunched,no shrink wrap, box in good condtion and slightly scuffed, contents like new.
Buyer to play for Priority shipping. Please send zipcode if you would like a shipping estimate.
Combined shipping available for multiple items. Optional insurance available for $1.70. FREE delivery confirmation.
Currently, I can only accept payment by cashier_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s check, money order, or NON-credit card Paypal transfer.
Thanks for looking!
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 01:02:07 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 01:36:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29.95</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Complete. Partially punched. Components in excellent, played once condition. Box has moderate wear on edges. I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly, within 24 hours of receiving payment. Shipping weight is 7 pounds.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 20:07:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 28 May 2009 21:08:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>45</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CONDITION: Brand new, in original shrinkwrap - just one small tear in the shrinkwrap on the back of the box.
POSTAGE COST:
UK postage:  £5.50
European Postage: £9.00
Rest of World Postage: £17.50
Any buyers in and around London are welcome to collect in person (cash on collection).
COMBINED SHIPPING:
I will always combine multiple items to reduce your shipping costs where possible.  Please note that it is NOT always cheaper to combine shipping on games outside the UK due to the weight limit of 2KG on the Small Packet service. As a rough approximation, outside the UK it is usually cheaper to combine 5 or more games, while 4 or less are best sent individually.  This depends entirely on the specific games - please contact me before buying if you wish to purchase multiple games so that I can give you an accurate shipping cost.
ABOUT ME:
I have been playing and collecting games for over 25 years and I also sell games and magazines on ebay with the same username (saabdastard) where I have a 100% positive rating and a feedback score of over 4000. I am a verified PAYPAL Premier account holder (since 2004), with over 650 PayPal Verified Buyers.
SELLERS TERMS AND CONDITIONS:
PAYMENT TERMS: 
Please wait until you receive my invoice before sending payment. 
Payment is due within 5 days of the date you receive my invoice. 
Please do not purchase if you do not intend to pay, or cannot pay within this time frame.
PAYMENT METHODS: 
UK buyers may use PayPal, cheque or cash-on-collection.
Overseas buyers MUST USE PAYPAL only.
SHIPPING:
Buyer is responsible for all shipping costs. Europe and Rest of World rates shown above are for Airmail. Surface Mail rate to Rest of World is available if you wish (same as Europe Air rate), but Surface Mail to Rest of World can take up to 2 months!  There is no real difference between Air and Surface rates for Europe.
INSURANCE:
Insurance is optional on all items, unless noted. Failure to take out optional insurance limits my liability for loss or damage in the mail to the amount automatically covered by Royal Mail (currently £39 per package for Small Packets, £150 for International Standard).
CUSTOMS:
Buyers outside the EU are responsible for all Customs charges applicable to their country.
RETURNS:
New Unopened items may be returned for a refund of the purchase price of the item, excluding shipping charges, within 7 days of the delivery date. All returned items must be in the original packaging and in the condition that they were shipped to you.
Defective or damaged items can be returned for an exchange or refund within 7 days of the delivery date. All returns require authorization from me BEFORE returning the item.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 19 May 2009 07:12:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 02:51:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The game is punched, but neatly sorted in two counter trays (you get one more as a bonus). The counters are in beautiful condition. They pretty much look new. The maps are in very good condition. There were a couple of very minor stains on at least one of them. Also the maps had been taped down at one point, so you can see where it had been removed at the corners. The rulebook has been thumbed through a little bit and a couple of the log sheets have been used. The charts are in excellent condition. The box has a small amount of shelf wear, but the corners are all intact and they are not splitting.
For some reason there is an extra southern map in this game. It is the map with Scotland in it.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 11 Oct 2009 14:43:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 22:00:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 20:54:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 28 Dec 2009 17:26:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All but one sheet of counters are completely unpunched. One sheet has about 1/3 of counters punched out (these counters are all present and kept in a small ziploc bag). Maps are in excellent unused condition. Complete Logistics Roster pad also included. Box top shows age, but is in sturdy condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 15:30:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:57:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>40</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Excellent unpunched still in shrinkwrap. 
All games are 100% checked and details sent to you before paying. 
All games will be well packed. Buyer pays shipping and optionally insurance otherwise posted at your risk. I do however get a certificate of posting for all parcels. 
Feel free to ask for more info/details. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 18:39:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 20:21:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>counters partly punched, all components including tray and tray cover</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 23:23:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 18:20:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>40</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Complete, unpunched game: only the shrinkwrap is missing! Box in excellent condition. (Yes, another game bought with the best of intentions many years ago...)
Estimated shipping on this is 10-12 euros within Europe, a bit higher to the US.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 20 May 2010 17:12:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:35:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>like new except for counters being punched and sorted
pics available on request</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 05:46:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 15:00:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components including game maps, counters, charts, log book, and rulebook are in excellent condition. Box has some shelf wear. I store my games in a pet-free and smoke-free environment and I package my games for shipment with the utmost care. I ship quickly - within 24 hours of receiving payment. Shipping weight is 5 pounds.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 02:49:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 08:24:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>27</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Very good.  Very slight box wear.  Chits are partly punched but clearly unplayed.  Chits appear complete but have not been inventoried.  Sold as-is.
Ships via USPS Priority Mail</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 03:43:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 22:04:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>31</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, complete.  The box has moderate to heavy wear, nearly all of it along the bottom edges. Everything inside the box is in like new condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 09:48:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 19:24:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Components complete and in good condition.
Box scuffed, some heavy
Shipping to UK destination £6</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 14:05:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 May 2011 02:03:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Includes all original components.
Counters are punched; well sorted by nation in storage tray and plastic bags (for the 1/2_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; counters).
No markings on the Logistics Roster Pad, Rules or elsewhere.
Box has handling/rubbing and shelf wear but no major damage. If not for the box wear it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;d be Very Good.
Ships via USPS Flat-rate Priority Mail ($10.95, I think it is these days).
Use PayPal.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 11:34:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 May 2011 19:07:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>48</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Shipping Germany  4 Euro
Shipping European Union 9 Euro
Shipping World         14 Euro
PayPal plus 2 Euro
Money transfer via IBAN/BIC preferred
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 12:53:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 May 2011 06:37:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>32</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Would love to give this a go but just can_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t see me getting it to the table so it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s up for sale. Complete, good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 May 2011 22:23:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 21:54:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Game is complete. Maps, counters and rules in very good shape. Box is square and solid. Moderate shelf wear and one minor ding on box corner. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 05:50:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 15:16:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>44.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>USED - VERY GOOD CONDITION - COMPLETE
Contact Information:
Phone: 1-407-925-7782 24/7 Live Customer Support
Email: nws-online@nws-online.net or warshipfc@yahoo.com</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 15:48:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 04:53:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>A LOT of tiles in this one, 600+.  Multiple countings and study of the scans of the counters show the only missing ones are blanks on both sides.  The rules don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t mention blank tiles as being used as far as I have determined.  I am calling this complete and possibly unplayed.   </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 04:08:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 05:56:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is for petegs who won item in an auction.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 23:28:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:57:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>missing 2 ammo counters. otherwise complete. Box worn with 1 split corner.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 17:59:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 19:36:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Pretty hard to find in this condition.
Game is still in shrink.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 20:11:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 17:17:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 20:53:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 18:27:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box in excellent condition. No missing pieces.
Tracked postage to USA is more than game cost</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 04 May 2012 10:45:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 00:34:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The game is complete and components/maps are in great condition.
Chits have been bagged into proper groups.
The box is a little worn and dished but has no split corners.
Will ship to the lower 48 United States.
Will consider other locations Based on BGG ratings and activity.
Can do FTF transaction if in the Torrance or Irvine areas of Los Angeles.
I accept PayPal or cash if FTF.
Shipping will run about $10 (will charge the actual cost)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 11:38:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 23:55:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>this is for both 2nd and 5th fleet by Victory Games - both games used/punched
only for Kev.
(hipshot)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 14:31:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 23:00:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 21:51:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 22:28:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 01:41:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 02:25:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched and complete.  Very clean.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 15:46:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 22:36:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Some markers have fallen out of the counter sheets.  Extra marker sheet included, as well as a complete extra set of ship/air counters.  One US ship has fallen out of the countersheet, but is in the box.  One box corner cracked.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 20:20:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 16:16:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>The box has some minor wear due to shelf life and being in a shipping box for some time.  Am missing the NATO chart, however all other components and pieces are accounted for.  This is a good game if you are in need of replacement parts yourself.
I can provide pictures of the game and all components if you would like.  Simply email me with the request.
I ship using flat rate boxes as this seems to be the most cost effective means to shipping these games.  If you would like to insure the game then please add $1.85 to the cost.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 16:01:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 15:51:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>65</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Payment in advance by money transfer.
Vorausbezahlung durch Banküberweisung.
!!!Please ask for special details if you want to use PayPal!!!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 00:04:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 21:08:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 13:01:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 19:01:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>85</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Payment in advance by money transfer.
Vorausbezahlung durch Banküberweisung.
!!!Please ask for special details if you want to use PayPal!!!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:24:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 00:37:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For user calandale from my auction.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 24 Mar 2013 20:27:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 04 May 2013 18:55:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>The game is punched but in very good condition. Looks like never used.
It_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s most probably complete but I did not check all the counters (more than 600).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:10:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 13:04:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched, complete.  Components are in great condition</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 13:58:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 14:18:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>250</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This is for user: Belz only.
This is for 2 complete sets of this series. That means that you get 2 copies of each game:
(2)2nd Fleet
(2)3rd Fleet
(2)5th Fleet
(2)Sixth Fleet
(2)7th Fleet
Condition: The boxes have significant shelf-wear, but are structurally intact and the actual game components are in gorgeous shape. Mostly unplayed (most of the maps have never been unfolded, much less played on) and we have verified that each game is complete (we did not inventory each counter, however). Looking at the condition of the components, I have no worries that all the counters are there.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 12:05:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 10:09:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched and sorted in tray. All components in near new condition.
Box is undamaged and shows average shelf wear.
Will ship in first class or priority box for $10 to U.S. addresses. $18 to Canada. $30 international.
I will combine shipping if you purchase other games at the same time. Magazines and non-boxed games can usually fit in the same box so no additional charge. I will send you a postage total on multiple game orders before confirming your order. I’ve rarely had any issues with loss or damage but U.S. post office does not track first class packages once they leave the U.S. so foreign buyers assume all risk of loss or damage.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 21:37:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 02:09:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is punched, but complete and in great shape.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 14:04:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 11:41:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Un-punched, Complete and in excellent condition
£5 postage to UK, Other countries please ask</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 19:22:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 23:51:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched into counter tray.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 20:02:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 19:31:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box is a little scuffed from storage, but the game is UNPUNCHED, never played. 
Canadian shipping may be slightly higher, please contact for details.
If you wish to pay using something other than PayPal, please contact me.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 15:15:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 05:32:41 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>23</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Punched. Box worn and some rules highligting but contents in very good shape.
Please add $12 S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;H
US only
Paypal only</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:27:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 02:43:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>All components present. 
Played a few times.
Counters in very good condition, clipped and sorted in small baggies.
Maps in very good condition.
*** No box *** 
Packed and sent in folio</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 05:59:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 14:34:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Mint and shrinkwrapped.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 12:46:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 07:17:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Never played and in excellent condition. Some scuffing to the box as a result of its age, but only cosmetic. All components have been punched but are sorted and bagged up, and all of the components are in as new condition. I look after all my games, and considering this one is getting on for thirty years old, it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s in very good shape.
Shipping to UK addresses would be £4.20 via MyHermes 3-day parcel delivery. Overseas delivery: just let me know your location and I will provide a quote.
I look forward to hearing from you with any questions.
Check out my other games for sale on BGG and ask for a bundle price for multiple games.
Paul</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 31 May 2014 21:57:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 11:34:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>for auction winner Brad K. only</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 00:14:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 13:47:14 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Second game in the VG Fleet series, and my personal favorite. Not as difficult as the traditional big VG rule book makes it look.
Box shows some shelf wear but no splits, dishing, or repairs. Counters are neatly cut, maps and charts are clean. Rules have been neatly highlighted.
If bought with my VG Sixth Fleet item, I will combine shipping and take an extra $5 off of the total price.
I will insure the item, if requested, for an additional $5
S_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;H of $12 is for US addresses only.
I am willing to ship worldwide if you are willing to pay the international shipping charges.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 09:15:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 11:38:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Parts either in original plastic tray or in zip lock bags. Very minor scuffs to box corners but otherwise in excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 18:19:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 18:58:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For TwichyBoy. Includes shipping.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 15:00:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 18:27:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>70</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 04:12:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 01:31:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Includes all components, I never played it, only thing that keeps it from being Very Good is the box is slightly creased and the instructions are slightly dog eared (I read through them a couple of times as a kid.) I also accept payment in Bitcoin.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 01:07:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 01:39:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>2nd Fleet: Modern Naval Combat in the North Atlantic (1986)
b. Designer: Joseph Balkoski
c. Publisher: Hobby Japan / Victory Games
d. Great/Very Good Condition! (Punched). Minor tear/worn edges on box’s upper left corner. Includes color maps, rule book, logistics record sheets, charts and tables, two player records, and two plastic compartment trays with punched counters inside.
This game is for J Macc only. Shipping will cost $12.35.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 06 Dec 2014 18:24:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:26:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Box shows some wear but is solid. Components are in like-new condition and are all present.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 11:27:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 11:56:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box shows some very slight shelf wear, not uncommon for age, counters punched and bagged/in counter tray, otherwise complete and all in excellent condition.
Photos available on request.
Will ship worldwide; please contact for costs.
Thanks for looking!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 12:19:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 20:30:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Misses 1 die
Rest 100% complete</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 20:53:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 18:04:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>All items present, box in excellent condition</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 13 Sep 2014 21:34:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 09:28:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Punched out some of the counters. All maps,charts,record sheets in great condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 20:46:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 20:36:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>£5 to post in UK. Worldwide - at cost (please enquire for quote)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 22 May 2015 13:16:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 18:26:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>1986 Victory Games.  Box has moderate scuffing.
All components verified present.  
One strip has shaken loose and is bagged, balance unpunched.
US shipping via priority mail $5.50 - $10.00 (depends on distance from 20912).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 18:11:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 19:41:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>2nd Fleet, punched, played once or twice, box is a little rough around the edges and has some discolouration. Can provide pictures at buyers discretion.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 11:16:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 09:04:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Un punched counters all rules and maps in very good condition.  The box has wear and tear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 17:32:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 03:10:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/197178/item/4161577#4161577]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Raise the Roof - An Auction in D_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;oh Minor_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
Shipping $12.30
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 18:44:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 01:33:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched, box has some shelf wear otherwise very nice. 
non smoker. 
Ships via USPS Priority mail. 
Please no trades or counteroffers.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 19:17:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 20:40:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Box is just open. Never played.
Pictures availables.
Bonus : Rules translated in french.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 03 May 2015 18:09:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 02:39:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>69.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Board Game Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! 
2ND FLEET: $69.95
Victory Games [VG 2ND FLEET]
* Unpunched.  Game box intact and in good+ to very good- condition.
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - $14.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 21 May 2015 13:10:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 15:49:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Partially punched, some of the charts have been cut away from the map for ease of play, all parts are present (see pictures  below and in my gallery)
PayPal or US postal Money Order
Other methods of payment may be accepted but contact me before ordering.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 02:02:46 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 03:19:28 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>For Alecc (Alecc) only, from my recent auction.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 20:32:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 01:17:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, box intact; minor shelfwear</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 23:39:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 12:43:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Partially punched, but never played.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 05:18:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 02:46:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Boxed, unpunched, contents in mint condition.  Box has some minor wear and tear.
Willing to discuss split for postage outside of Australia (likely to be expensive, the box is heavy)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 11:08:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 22:26:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>some box ageing, I dont think it has been played. £4 postage to Uk, other countries please ask</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 15:53:39 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 16:06:14 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>55</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Game is in very good condition. All counters are punched and clipped and sorted.
The map of the game is DIY mounted. Its very good preserved this way, but the downside is, that there are minor gaps between the boards. This doesn´t affect playability.  
I´m selling most of my wargame collection. Have a look at my other offers!
I will send worldwide and the buyer is paying shipping cost.
Shipping cost estimates:
Germany 5,- Euros
Europe 9,- Euros
USA 16,- Euros
Please take contact if you have questions or want to know the exact shipping costs.
Payment by Paypal or direct transfer to my bank account.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 10:40:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 22:49:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>59.95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Very good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 May 2016 13:37:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 23:22:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>72.11</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>100% complete. Contents are like new / unused.  Counters are punched some are still in the strips (info sheet was not punched).  Counters  were counted and verified complete.   Components all look unused.
Box is showing a fair amount of shelf wear.
US Shipping is $13. $11 if within 2 states of MN.  International is at cost.  Weight is 2pounds 14oz (first class international)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 08:27:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 02:29:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>the game is mint  unpunched box is in great condition
You can always pick the game up in our local shop :-)
You can make a bank transfer free of charge from our side to an EU bank account using IBAN/BIC if your bank account is nominated in EURO.
You can use paypal adding a 3.5% paypal fee. (That should be the first choice for non-EU customers)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 06:42:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 13:47:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>51.98</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Condition: box lid _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; corners are heavily scuffed _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; discolored from use, 2 corners are lightly tearing</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 21:03:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 18:57:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.
I accept only Payment through Paypal without any charge or payment in hand if you live in Madrid.
Shipping and handling:
1-España 7 euros carta certificada.Posible recogida en mano si vives en Madrid.
2-Europe:15 Eur (Registered mail).
3-USA,Japan,Australia:25,50$ USD (registered mail)
The games shall be sent next saturday after the payment has been received.
I offer combined shipping if you buy more than one item.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 01:25:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 21:34:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Components - Very Good+; mostly punched, played a couple times.  Complete.  Rulebook has been paged through - light soiling along spine and edges but it is free of any writing/highlighting.
Box - Good+ condition; the box is intact, no splits, moderate wear to edges and corners.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 21:22:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 17:11:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Shipper pays actual shipping +$2 from zip code 15217.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 19:06:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:06:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>72</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Box worn, but contents in fine shape. Unpunched. $8 shipping in U.S.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 19:08:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 12:06:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>79</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Shipping Germany  5 Euro
Shipping European Union 9 Euro
Shipping World         16 Euro
PayPal plus max. 4 Euro
Money transfer via IBAN/BIC from EURO accounts usually free</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 19:31:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 23:36:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>39</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Player_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s copy. Punched, played, all components present except for the die, the counter tray, and the 13 blank 5/8th-inch counters. I also counted 12 extra 1/2-inch counters (272 instead of 260), not sure what those extras are. Maps looks good, charts _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; tables are used but functional, counters are good, rulebook is worn and dog-eared, but sound and readable. Box is quite worn, lots of scuffing and shelf wear, but sound.
$9 shipping East of the Mississippi except for Illinois, Wisconsin and Minnesota; $14 West of the Mississippi and to Illinois, Wisconsin and Minnesota.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 03:05:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 18:44:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>74.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Condition: Wear on corners</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:31:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 11 May 2018 17:33:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>65</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:47:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 24 May 2018 18:17:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>49</price>
    <condition>acceptable</condition>
    <notes>Complete, good player‘s copy. The box however, shows heavy shelf wear.
NOTE: The previous owner put adhesive foil on all the counters and the map sheets. Therefore the maps won‘t lay flat anymore and have to be weighed down with glass or plexiglas.
ALSO includes a copy of the General magazine with the Bay of Biscay expansion and the rules for the French fleet. Home made counters for that expansion are also included!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 31 May 2018 01:44:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 31 May 2018 03:37:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>1986 Victory Games 
book shelf box
very good condition, complete
https://boardgamegeek.com/geeklist/241271/phil-baird-collection</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:14:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 17:26:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>69</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, played two or three times.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 20 May 2018 17:01:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 03:13:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>59</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Pretty good condition, see pictures in my gallery.  One map has a water/coffee spot and some discoloration on the rules.  Box has some shelfwear, but not a lot.
Shipping will be $14 for USPS Flat Rate medium box.
Will throw in a kinda beat-up copy of Sixth Fleet if you want to add $5 for the larger flat rate shipping box.  Pictures also in gallery.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 02:28:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:18:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 11:42:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 07:32:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>90</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>slightly used box, unpunched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:34:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 11:46:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>49</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This is a very nice copy of 2nd Fleet.  Box show some wear but contents are in excellent condition.  Really deserves a Like New rating except for some minor box wear.  Rulebook/map are pristine, and counters are mostly unpunched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 02:39:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 03:15:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/225622/item/6043517#6043517]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Moving and don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t wan_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t to take all these games with (53716)_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 10:44:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 18:01:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>UK shipping £10. 
Will ship worldwide at cost (please enquire for quote before purchase)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 22:03:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 01:19:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>75</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Counters punched but all present with crisp, sharp edges.  All other game materials MINT.  Original owner.  Pet and smoke free home.  GREAT condition overall.</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
