<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="23418">
   <yearpublished>2008</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>2</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>2</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>360</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>360</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>360</maxplaytime>
   <age>14</age>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">Pursuit of Glory</name>
         
   <description>Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East is a sequel to the award-winning Paths of Glory. This game puts you in the driver's seat of the British/Russian alliance or the Ottoman Empire during World War One. Gallipoli, holy war, mutiny, and the Russian Revolution await. Walk in the shoes of men such as Churchill, Lawrence of Arabia, Enver, and Falkenhayn._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;The action stretches from India to the Balkans, from the Black Sea to Suez. Can the Germans inspire a Persian uprising or forge an alliance with Afghanistan? Can the Russians capture a warm water port? Can the British guard the oil that fuels the Royal Navy? Can the Turks capture the Suez Canal and spark a revolt in Egypt?_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;In Pursuit of Glory, your hand of 7 cards presents you with an array of strategic and operational opportunities. You must decide whether to use each card for its historic event, command points, or resources. You must then commit your forces to a variety of objectives: the Turkish-Russian frontier in Caucasia, the violation of neutral Persia, oil-rich Mesopotamia, the Suez Canal, the Balkans and its vital railroads. You must judge when it is right to invade Serbia or launch a new naval invasion (perhaps on the inset map representing Gallipoli)._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;As the British, you must hold on while your Russian allies break through the Turkish lines in Caucasia and you bring your forces to bear through invasion and a gradual build-up of imperial might. As the Turks, your objective is to gain complete victory early, uniting your strength with Germany and crippling the British Empire in Egypt and India or to persevere._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;(from GMT website)_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Pursuit of Glory is a stand alone sequel to Paths of Glory, a card-driven strategy game covering the first World War.  Unlike the original game, which focused on the European theater of World War I, Pursuit of Glory focuses entirely on the Great War in the Middle East.  Pursuit of Glory uses the same card-driven mechanics and point-to-point of the first game, but with some rules changes and modifications to better simulate the conditions of the war in the Middle East._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;It was developed by Brad and Brian Stock with the permission of Ted Raicer, the designer of the original Paths of Glory._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;(BGG description)_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Game Features_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;TIME SCALE    Approx. 1 year per hand of cards_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;MAP SCALE    Point-to-Point_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;NUMBER OF PLAYERS    One or Two_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;DESIGNER: Brad Stock _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;amp; Brian Stock_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;DEVELOPER: Tony Curtis _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;amp; Neil Randall_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;MAP, CARD, _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;amp; COUNTER ART: Mark Simonitch_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/_dja4s8rwS4-tT0TSExSj_BFRHM=/fit-in/200x150/pic394801.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/1LgbvO2jauvIQ8Ea9seVIgeGCRU=/0x0/pic394801.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamehonor objectid="21278">2008 Charles S. Roberts Best Pre-WW2 era Board Game Nominee</boardgamehonor>
               <boardgamehonor objectid="8416">2009 Golden Geek Best Wargame Nominee</boardgamehonor>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2018">Campaign / Battle Card Driven</boardgamemechanic>
                      <boardgamemechanic objectid="2072">Dice Rolling</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgameversion objectid="25010">First edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="52">GMT Games</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="73074">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! episode 29: 2011 in review</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="115504">I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ve Been Diced! episode 51: The PrezCon 2014 edition</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgameartist objectid="71">Rodger B. MacGowan</boardgameartist>
                             <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="7435">Point 2 Point 39: They_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re Ba-ack and Pursuit of Glory</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2078">Point to Point Movement</boardgamemechanic>
                             <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="7762">Pursuit of Glory</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                      <boardgameartist objectid="140">Mark Simonitch</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="7064">Brad Stock</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="7065">Brian Stock</boardgamedesigner>
                      <boardgamecategory objectid="1019">Wargame</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="4664">Wargames</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1065">World War I</boardgamecategory>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="15">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="7" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="12" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="8" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="8">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="6" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="2" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="9">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="6" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>457</usersrated>
     <average>7.88751</average>
     <bayesaverage>6.12921</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="1740" bayesaverage="6.12921" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="4664" name="wargames" friendlyname="War Game Rank" value="75" bayesaverage="7.23879" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.62306</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>1316</owned>
     <trading>29</trading>
     <wanting>96</wanting>
     <wishing>312</wishing>
     <numcomments>219</numcomments>
     <numweights>90</numweights>
     <averageweight>3.8778</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 19:32:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 16:03:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Boardgame Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
***** ***** PRE ORDER ***** *****
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $32.95 (pre-order)
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
Publisher_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s estimated release date: Fall 2008.
***** ***** PRE ORDER ***** *****
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - FedEx: $13.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - USPS Priority Mail: TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 02:00:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 17:24:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Boardgame Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $33.95 ...in stock now...no waiting
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - FedEx: $13.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - USPS Priority Mail: TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 20:58:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 19:28:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Boardgame Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $33.95 ...in stock now...no waiting
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - FedEx: $13.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - USPS Priority Mail: TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 19:05:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 00:02:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>GMT Games (GMT 0810)
The First World War in the Near East and Balkans was largely a clash of civilizations and of proud leaders intent on pursuing glory, regardless of the cost. Great Britain was at the height of its imperial power, while the Russian Empire was entering its last days, having just avoided revolution and global disgrace in 1905. The Ottoman Empire was adjusting to the Young Turks_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; revolution and the devastation of the Balkan Wars of 1912-1913. The Germans (Britain_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s primary rivals) were only too glad to bolster the Ottoman_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s fading power, seeing the region as ripe for economic and military exploitation. Indeed, if the Germans completed their new railroad from Berlin to Baghdad, German troops would be able to travel to India more quickly than British troops could sail from London to Bombay. German troops would also then be poised to seize southern Persia, the region which contained the British fleet_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s main new source of fuel -- oil. Behind all this lay the pent up ethnic and religious tensions of millennia, in countries such as Serbia, Persia, and Afghanistan, and in the countless tribes of Arabia and Northern Africa waiting for new leaders who would lead them on a holy war (jihad). The entire region was a powder keg waiting for a match. 
 
Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East is a sequel to the original, award-winning Paths of Glory by Ted Raicer and is designed with his permission. The new game puts you in the driver_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s seat as theater commanders for either the British/Russian alliance or the Ottoman Empire. The action stretches from the Balkans to the borders of India, from the Black Sea to Suez. Invasions by sea, holy war, revolts, revolution await, as well as some of the most famous personages of the First World War - Lawrence, Allenby, Enver, the Grand Duke Nicholas, Churchill, Kitchener. 
Take for example, the case of Jafar Pasha. He was an Iraqi Arab trained for military leadership at Istanbul and in Germany. He was decorated by the Turks, awarded the German Iron Cross, assisted in fortifying Gallipoli, and was hand picked to lead the Senussi rebellion against the British in Egypt. While engaged in this mission, he was captured and imprisoned, escaped and was recaptured, eventually winning the hearts of his British captors, for Jafar was a model of civilization and decorum. When the Arab Revolt broke out, Jafar helped recruit Ottoman POWs to join the Arab cause, and the British eventually released him for service in the Arab Revolt. He became Prince Faisal_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s chief of staff, leading the Arab Northern Army against the Turks, earning a decoration from the British general Allenby (his guard of honor being the very ANZAC cavalry unit that had almost killed him when he was leading the Senussi). After the war, the British installed him as Iraq_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s minister of defense, and he later served as Iraqi Prime Minister and as Iraq_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s ambassador to England, spending the night twice in Buckingham Palace. This story epitomizes the nature of World War One in the Near East. It captures the wild-eyed flavor of Pursuit of Glory - razor-edged, variable, tense, exciting. 
In Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East, the Central Powers (CP) player, representing the Ottoman Empire and its allies, attempts to use his central position and initial superiority of forces to defeat his opponents early on, or to endure defensively until the enemy tires of the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;sideshow_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; and goes home. It is possible for the Ottoman player to win military victory or to exhaust the British Empire_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s patience, leading to a negotiated peace in the region - and Ottoman dominance of the region_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s oil at the beginning of the twentieth century. The Allied (AP) player, representing primarily the British and Russian empires, attempts to delay the Russian Revolution and bring his superior forces to bear before he is required to bring the boys back home. Of course, once the Russian Empire collapses, all bets are off -- the Turks and the Brits must race to gain control of the Caucasian and Persian regions, including the oil. The problem for the Turks is that the British blockade is crippling the Ottoman economy and the Turkish manpower pool is running dry - the longer the war continues, the fewer the Turkish recruits, the less reliable the Arab draftees, the more dependent Turkey becomes on German aid through that all-important railroad to Berlin. The problem for the Allied player is to stave off disaster long enough to build up his forces for an all-out assault, while using his naval supremacy wisely. 
How does this game differ from the original? Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East uses all of the core rules from the original Paths of Glory. Players who know the original will find the new game easy to learn. The rules have been rewritten with both the newcomer and experienced player in mind. For the newcomer, the rules are clearly written, with examples and elaboration. For the experienced player, the new rules specific to Pursuit of Glory are clearly indicated, allowing him easily to skip rules with which he is already familiar. Quick Start guides will be included for both newcomers and experienced players. 
There are special rules to address the issues of invasions by sea, including an entire Gallipoli sub-map. There is Holy War (jihad), allowing the Ottoman player to foster tribal uprisings and national rebellions (including the possibility of Egyptian and Indian mutinies against the British). Historically, jihad was a very conscious strategy of both the Turks and the Germans, with real efforts to gain access to Persia, Central Asia, Afghanistan, and India -- this is a key new dynamic in the game. The Russian Revolution is handled in a very realistic, yet simple manner, allowing the Allied player to postpone the revolution if he is successful militarily, especially if he achieves the age-long dream of the czars -- obtaining a warm-water port (particularly if that port is Constantinople). Units are primarily corps and divisions, with simple rules for cavalry, headquarters, German heavy artillery, and other special units, such as camel corps and armoured car detachments. The Armenian situation is not neglected. Even the Christian Assyrians of Lake Urmia make an appearance, fighting valiantly on the Allied side. Yet all of these extra features play with the same smoothness as the original Paths of Glory. Once the new systems are learned, experienced Paths of Glory players will find that they are integrated seamlessly with the original game system that they know and love. And newcomers should find the game accessible without any knowledge of the original. 
We hope that the game will help you better understand the political and economic situations of today. The Middle East as we know it is the result of decisions made during the Great War, usually by white males in positions of power sitting in comfort far away. The game propounds no particular view as to the rightness or wrongness of actions by the Ottomans or Europeans, but attempts to simulate the dynamics of events objectively. As the player begins to understand these dynamics, the history of the region comes alive, greatly enhancing one_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s understanding of current events. The response from playtesters seems to indicate that a Western-oriented bias has been largely avoided--and this includes those familiar with the war from the Ottoman side, including one playtester in Istanbul. 
What are some of the dynamics that have direct parallels to today? 
the ongoing jockeying for dominance in the Black Sea, Caspian Sea, and Persian Gulf regions, culturally, politically, and economically; 
the vital importance of oil, especially for the naval forces of the superior English-speaking power of the day; 
the perceived necessity of _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;proving_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; that the great Western powers will not capitulate to _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;backwards_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; Muslim tribes or _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;third-rate_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; Muslim nations - but the fact is that the public, press, and political opposition (even from your leading generals) may force you to bring the boys back home before your mission is accomplished, resulting in strategic disaster and national humiliation; 
the troubling importance of Persia (Iran), with Russian and Muslim influence interfering with the economic and military goals of the West; 
the Muslim leadership_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s desire that their peoples should again rise to a position of dominance in the Near East and Central Asia, thereby proving that they are the equals of the Europeans, if not their superiors; 
concerted efforts by the warriors of jihad to drive the infidel forces out; 
the rivalry between the Western powers, including acute rivalry between supposed allies (e.g., France and Great Britain); 
the Muslim leadership_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s fear that any aid accepted from the European powers will result in dependence and some form of colonialism; 
the inability to impose security in a region where guerilla or tribal elements can appear instantly on your lines of communication and supply, rendering the concept of a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;front_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; dangerous or obsolete. 
Each of the above statements describes the dynamics of the First World War in the Balkans and Near East. The nature of oil, power, religion, prestige remain largely unchanged today. 
And, yes, for those who frequently ask - the great German battleship, the Goeben, is present and can bombard Batum successfully. The Russian Black Sea Marines can land at the Bosphorus and seize Constantinople. And Churchill can attempt to bombard the Turkish forts at the Dardanelles, then run his fleet up past The Narrows, bringing fear to the Turk and succor to the Russian, who will gladly accept British aid. 
If you are looking for a game that is relevant topically, will teach you much, and will offer you a fun, tense, wild, frantic roller coaster of a ride, please consider Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East. We think you will be pleased. 
Components: 
1 map 
dice 
110 card deck 
2 player aid cards 
1 sheet of Large Combat Unit counters (5/8_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;) 
1 sheet of Small Combat Unit counter (1/2_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;) 
1 rulebook 
1 playbook, with scenarios and extended example of play 
1 quick start guides (4-6 pages) 
Designer: Brad Stock and Brian Stock 
Developers: Tony Curtis and Neil Randall </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 02:44:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 16 May 2009 11:50:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>49.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>English game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 17:50:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 19:20:29 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>still in original shrinkwrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 20:52:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 16:15:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Out of shrink but otherwise brand new.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 18:50:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 09:30:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>32</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 11:40:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 15:24:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shipping
Italy 9,50
Europe 12,50</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 01:23:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:17:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>27.5</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened and examined. Otherwise like new.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 04:19:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 05:13:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Boardgame Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $33.95
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - FedEx: $13.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - USPS Priority Mail: TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 02:55:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 04 Oct 2009 18:17:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>27.5</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Complete and in generally like-new condition. Box has only tiny amounts of shelf-wear and looks almost brand-new. Counters are neatly trimmed, sorted, and bagged, and cards bound with magic tape, and neither have been used. Map shows some minimal crease wear but is otherwise in excellent condition. Rulebook shows signs of thumbing through, but the playbook is in excellent condition and the player aids are like-new.
Shipping weight is 2+ lbs, so shipping in the US will be via USPS Priority Mail, which will max out at $9.85 for flat-rate; if you_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;re on or near the West Coast, it may be slightly cheaper.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 15:21:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 00:49:00 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Domestic Shipping: USPS PRIORITY MAIL with Delivery Confirmation = $10.99</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 17:31:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 14:10:06 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33.33</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Domestic Shipping: USPS PRIORITY MAIL with Delivery Confirmation = $10.99</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 00:29:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 02:12:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>26</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 16 Apr 2010 16:15:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 16 Apr 2010 16:44:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>27.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New in Shrink. £3.50 postage to UK, £7 to Europe
I will ship worldwide (please ask, if outside the UK, for a shipping quote before ordering), combine orders for cheaper postage and will give a  2.5% discount for purchases over £50 and  5% for purchases over £100. All items (750+ unique games) I list are in stock and will be posted within 24 working hours of payment being received.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 16 Apr 2010 16:53:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 13:58:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>27.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New in Shrink. £4 postage to UK, £8 to Europe
I will ship worldwide (please ask, if outside the UK, for a shipping quote before ordering), combine orders for cheaper postage and will give a  2.5% discount for purchases over £50 and  5% for purchases over £100. All items (750+ unique games) I list are in stock and will be posted within 24 working hours of payment being received.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 19:28:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 07:17:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>27.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New in Shrink. £4.40  postage to UK.
I will ship worldwide (please ask, if outside the UK, for a shipping quote before ordering), combine orders for cheaper postage and will give a  2.5% discount for purchases over £50 and  5% for purchases over £100. All items (750+ unique games) I list are in stock and will be posted within 24 working hours of payment being received.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 14 May 2010 03:08:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 15 May 2010 12:43:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrink removed, nothing else.
Shipping via USPS medium flat rate w/delivery confirmation.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 21:31:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 18:38:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>33</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>auction - reserved to 
    Kris Coppoolse</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 18:33:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 13:04:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>36.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>GMT Games (GMT 0810)
The First World War in the Near East and Balkans was largely a clash of civilizations and of proud leaders intent on pursuing glory, regardless of the cost. Great Britain was at the height of its imperial power, while the Russian Empire was entering its last days, having just avoided revolution and global disgrace in 1905. The Ottoman Empire was adjusting to the Young Turks_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; revolution and the devastation of the Balkan Wars of 1912-1913. The Germans (Britain_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s primary rivals) were only too glad to bolster the Ottoman_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s fading power, seeing the region as ripe for economic and military exploitation. Indeed, if the Germans completed their new railroad from Berlin to Baghdad, German troops would be able to travel to India more quickly than British troops could sail from London to Bombay. German troops would also then be poised to seize southern Persia, the region which contained the British fleet_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s main new source of fuel -- oil. Behind all this lay the pent up ethnic and religious tensions of millennia, in countries such as Serbia, Persia, and Afghanistan, and in the countless tribes of Arabia and Northern Africa waiting for new leaders who would lead them on a holy war (jihad). The entire region was a powder keg waiting for a match. 
Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East is a sequel to the original, award-winning Paths of Glory by Ted Raicer and is designed with his permission. The new game puts you in the driver_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s seat as theater commanders for either the British/Russian alliance or the Ottoman Empire. The action stretches from the Balkans to the borders of India, from the Black Sea to Suez. Invasions by sea, holy war, revolts, revolution await, as well as some of the most famous personages of the First World War - Lawrence, Allenby, Enver, the Grand Duke Nicholas, Churchill, Kitchener. 
Take for example, the case of Jafar Pasha. He was an Iraqi Arab trained for military leadership at Istanbul and in Germany. He was decorated by the Turks, awarded the German Iron Cross, assisted in fortifying Gallipoli, and was hand picked to lead the Senussi rebellion against the British in Egypt. While engaged in this mission, he was captured and imprisoned, escaped and was recaptured, eventually winning the hearts of his British captors, for Jafar was a model of civilization and decorum. When the Arab Revolt broke out, Jafar helped recruit Ottoman POWs to join the Arab cause, and the British eventually released him for service in the Arab Revolt. He became Prince Faisal_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s chief of staff, leading the Arab Northern Army against the Turks, earning a decoration from the British general Allenby (his guard of honor being the very ANZAC cavalry unit that had almost killed him when he was leading the Senussi). After the war, the British installed him as Iraq_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s minister of defense, and he later served as Iraqi Prime Minister and as Iraq_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s ambassador to England, spending the night twice in Buckingham Palace. This story epitomizes the nature of World War One in the Near East. It captures the wild-eyed flavor of Pursuit of Glory - razor-edged, variable, tense, exciting. 
In Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East, the Central Powers (CP) player, representing the Ottoman Empire and its allies, attempts to use his central position and initial superiority of forces to defeat his opponents early on, or to endure defensively until the enemy tires of the _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;sideshow_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; and goes home. It is possible for the Ottoman player to win military victory or to exhaust the British Empire_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s patience, leading to a negotiated peace in the region - and Ottoman dominance of the region_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s oil at the beginning of the twentieth century. The Allied (AP) player, representing primarily the British and Russian empires, attempts to delay the Russian Revolution and bring his superior forces to bear before he is required to bring the boys back home. Of course, once the Russian Empire collapses, all bets are off -- the Turks and the Brits must race to gain control of the Caucasian and Persian regions, including the oil. The problem for the Turks is that the British blockade is crippling the Ottoman economy and the Turkish manpower pool is running dry - the longer the war continues, the fewer the Turkish recruits, the less reliable the Arab draftees, the more dependent Turkey becomes on German aid through that all-important railroad to Berlin. The problem for the Allied player is to stave off disaster long enough to build up his forces for an all-out assault, while using his naval supremacy wisely. 
How does this game differ from the original? Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East uses all of the core rules from the original Paths of Glory. Players who know the original will find the new game easy to learn. The rules have been rewritten with both the newcomer and experienced player in mind. For the newcomer, the rules are clearly written, with examples and elaboration. For the experienced player, the new rules specific to Pursuit of Glory are clearly indicated, allowing him easily to skip rules with which he is already familiar. Quick Start guides will be included for both newcomers and experienced players. 
There are special rules to address the issues of invasions by sea, including an entire Gallipoli sub-map. There is Holy War (jihad), allowing the Ottoman player to foster tribal uprisings and national rebellions (including the possibility of Egyptian and Indian mutinies against the British). Historically, jihad was a very conscious strategy of both the Turks and the Germans, with real efforts to gain access to Persia, Central Asia, Afghanistan, and India -- this is a key new dynamic in the game. The Russian Revolution is handled in a very realistic, yet simple manner, allowing the Allied player to postpone the revolution if he is successful militarily, especially if he achieves the age-long dream of the czars -- obtaining a warm-water port (particularly if that port is Constantinople). Units are primarily corps and divisions, with simple rules for cavalry, headquarters, German heavy artillery, and other special units, such as camel corps and armoured car detachments. The Armenian situation is not neglected. Even the Christian Assyrians of Lake Urmia make an appearance, fighting valiantly on the Allied side. Yet all of these extra features play with the same smoothness as the original Paths of Glory. Once the new systems are learned, experienced Paths of Glory players will find that they are integrated seamlessly with the original game system that they know and love. And newcomers should find the game accessible without any knowledge of the original. 
We hope that the game will help you better understand the political and economic situations of today. The Middle East as we know it is the result of decisions made during the Great War, usually by white males in positions of power sitting in comfort far away. The game propounds no particular view as to the rightness or wrongness of actions by the Ottomans or Europeans, but attempts to simulate the dynamics of events objectively. As the player begins to understand these dynamics, the history of the region comes alive, greatly enhancing one_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s understanding of current events. The response from playtesters seems to indicate that a Western-oriented bias has been largely avoided--and this includes those familiar with the war from the Ottoman side, including one playtester in Istanbul. 
What are some of the dynamics that have direct parallels to today? 
the ongoing jockeying for dominance in the Black Sea, Caspian Sea, and Persian Gulf regions, culturally, politically, and economically; 
the vital importance of oil, especially for the naval forces of the superior English-speaking power of the day; 
the perceived necessity of _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;proving_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; that the great Western powers will not capitulate to _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;backwards_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; Muslim tribes or _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;third-rate_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; Muslim nations - but the fact is that the public, press, and political opposition (even from your leading generals) may force you to bring the boys back home before your mission is accomplished, resulting in strategic disaster and national humiliation; 
the troubling importance of Persia (Iran), with Russian and Muslim influence interfering with the economic and military goals of the West; 
the Muslim leadership_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s desire that their peoples should again rise to a position of dominance in the Near East and Central Asia, thereby proving that they are the equals of the Europeans, if not their superiors; 
concerted efforts by the warriors of jihad to drive the infidel forces out; 
the rivalry between the Western powers, including acute rivalry between supposed allies (e.g., France and Great Britain); 
the Muslim leadership_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s fear that any aid accepted from the European powers will result in dependence and some form of colonialism; 
the inability to impose security in a region where guerilla or tribal elements can appear instantly on your lines of communication and supply, rendering the concept of a _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;front_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; dangerous or obsolete. 
Each of the above statements describes the dynamics of the First World War in the Balkans and Near East. The nature of oil, power, religion, prestige remain largely unchanged today. 
And, yes, for those who frequently ask - the great German battleship, the Goeben, is present and can bombard Batum successfully. The Russian Black Sea Marines can land at the Bosphorus and seize Constantinople. And Churchill can attempt to bombard the Turkish forts at the Dardanelles, then run his fleet up past The Narrows, bringing fear to the Turk and succor to the Russian, who will gladly accept British aid. 
If you are looking for a game that is relevant topically, will teach you much, and will offer you a fun, tense, wild, frantic roller coaster of a ride, please consider Pursuit of Glory: The Great War in the Near East. We think you will be pleased. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 13:01:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 17:36:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>UK Shipping
£3.99
EU Shipping 
£6.99
If you wish to purchase more than one item please let me know so I know to combine.
I am based in Gateshead in the North East of England and will happily offer local pickup as an option to avoid having to pay the postage. If you are reasonably local I may even offer to drop the items off if I am feeling in a good mood!
My address is Unit 10A, Design Works, William Street, Gateshead, Tyne and Wear, NE10 0JP</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 05:15:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 15:54:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Never played.  Bits have been separated _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; sorted.  The box is a little weathered from storage, but bits inside are in good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 19:04:20 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 21:10:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>44.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>GMT Games - Pursuit of Glory
Language: English 
Players: 2
Age: 14+
Duration: up to 6 hour 
Weight: 0.970 kg
New - mint condition - unopened - still in shrink wrap.
Theme: Pursuit of Glory is a stand alone sequel to Paths of Glory, a card-driven strategy game covering the first World War. Unlike the original game, which focused on the European theater of World War I, Pursuit of Glory focuses entirely on the Great War in the Middle East. Pursuit of Glory uses the same card-driven mechanics and point-to-point of the first game, but with some rules changes and modifications to better simulate the conditions of the war in the Middle East. 
See Details (more info) or below for complete selling, payment and shipping conditions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 06:07:03 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 14:23:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched and unplayed. 100% complete. In very good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 18:39:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 19:31:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>played several times</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 18:19:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 23:41:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened unpunched</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 15:19:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 17:47:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 17:28:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 10:01:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Very nice shape, no issues, opened but not played. Should be a 3 pound package from zip 80015. I don_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t charge for packing/handling, and I ship USPS Priority by the lowest rate.
Please let me know if you have questions.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 02:44:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 20:21:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>33.5</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Brand New!
A portion of the earnings from each sale are donated to St. Jude Children_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Research Hospital.
Standard Shipping to USA48: $9.00</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 11:11:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 23:18:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>36</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in shrinkwrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 14:27:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 20:30:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink. Please check out my other games for sale!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 14:03:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 13:20:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>29.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Board Game Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $29.95
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - FedEx: $13.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - USPS Priority Mail: TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 15:08:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 14:36:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>35</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>English edition.
Shipping EU 14€</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 06 May 2012 22:15:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 04:32:05 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:19:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 11:54:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>25</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in shrinkwrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 25 May 2012 12:01:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 17:37:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 16:16:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 09 Jun 2012 17:56:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>19.5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Pursuit of Glory (GMT) . Punched and clipped and sorted in bags. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 17:03:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 12:58:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Pursuit of Glory – 2008 – Unpunched. Opened Once. Great Condition. Will ship Priority Mail for $8.00</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 13:10:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 12:03:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shipping cost from Denmark are insanely high for single games but are more reasonable for bigger orders, so please check my profile and see if any of my other games interest you.
Shipping costs within the EU(+Norway):
Less than 2 kg: 30 euro
Less than 5 kg: 40 euro
Less than 10 kg: 60 euro
Shipping costs to countries outside the EU:
Base price is 32 dollars/25 euros + 9 dollars/7 euros for each kg of weight
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 23:35:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:35:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>22</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Posted for auction winner Michael Fralish.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 10:32:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 19:31:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>never used - unpunched</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 23:16:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 19:54:14 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.49</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Brand New!
A portion of the earnings from each sale are donated to St. Jude Children_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Research Hospital.
Standard shipping to a continental USA street address: $9.95</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 17:17:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 07 May 2013 14:39:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink. Please check out my other games for sale!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 01 May 2013 23:47:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 03:02:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrinkwrap copy.  No holes in the shrink.  No box damage.  Straight from the factory minty fresh.  Unsoiled by human hands and waiting to be opened.  Worldwide shipping and will be packed well. All forms of negotiable instruments considered.  Combine ship with multiple purchases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 20 May 2013 23:56:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 02:31:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>28</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Brand new in shrink. Mint.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 16:53:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 21:41:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>18</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This item was sold in an auction and is reserved for ________.  
Please do not attempt to purchase this item unless this is your username.  Thanks!
Shipping charges assume that I am shipping to the country designated in your user avatar.  If the country is different, or if you do not live in the CONUS, your shipping charges may be incorrect.
Thanks again - if you have any questions during this transaction, GM me or e-mail me at chrismontgomery@comcast.net</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 23:58:37 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 20:36:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>29.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unopened in shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 00:58:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 00:32:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>reserved for Leppy</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 00:03:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 14:24:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32.5</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 23:05:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 09:10:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>15</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>Bought on BGG Marketplace. I punched the game, read the rules, but never got chance to play it, and the complex rules did strange things to my brain. I now have to make some space in the house for baby things, so the really heavy games that I want to play but never get the opportunity have to go. Will ship to the UK. Postage is extra.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 14:07:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 02:19:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Sold to Operadragon ONLY
For delivery at BGG.CON 2013
Pursuit of Glory
New in every respect except:
Rules clearly have been read.
Unpunched. Cards still in shrink. Baggies still in rubber bands.
New Delivery Information!: I can deliver all games at the Virtual Flea Market Official Exchange or some other time before 7:30 PM on Thursday or Saturday.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 22:10:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 10:15:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Board Game Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $34.95
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - $13.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 18:24:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 12:21:31 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>32.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New in Shrink.
UK postage is £4.95 including tracking.  Contact me for other destinations.  I combine shipping where possible.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 07:02:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:33:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Condition: new in shrink
Payment via PayPal, or cash for local pickup.
Buyer pays actual shipping from the 95051 zip code. I will work with you to minimize shipping costs and combine shipping wherever possible. I prefer USPS fixed rate priority boxes, which usually means $12.35 for a medium box.
Please check out my other games for sale. I recently added a bunch of war games. Mostly GMT.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 02:04:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 19:30:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>27</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Complete, unpunched, unplayed, excellent condition, only the shrink removed.
CONUS shipping is USPS priority. I will tack on 4-6% to offset paypal and BGG charges.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:17:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:31:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>32</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>only for user Mike Welker
Auction win</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 17:06:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 22:05:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>No shipping costs for Germany!
All games are new and in their original wrapping and all prices include the German VAT (7% or 19%).
We offer only goods that we have in stock.
We ship worldwide – please ask for a quote about exact shipping costs (rest assured that we always try to keep them as low as possible).
Payment may be made by Paypal or bank transfer in advance.
For orders above €50 we grant a discount of €5 on shipping costs.
If you have any questions, feel free to send us an email (laden@gamers-hq.de), give us a call (+49 30 79706126) or visit our homepage (www.gamers-hq.de).
Our Terms and Conditions
1. General
All transactions between Gamers HQ and you, the customer, are subject to the following conditions, which you acknowledge by accepting delivery of your ordered products. These conditions do not affect your statutory rights and in all cases German law applies.
2. Orders and prices
We do our level best to ensure that the information on our website is up-to-date. Please note that offers and prices are subject to change. We work to ensure that our prices are all correct, but cannot be held responsible for accidentally displaying the wrong price of a product.
All prices are quoted in Euros and already include all necessary taxes.
3. Lead times and delivery costs
Our products are delivered directly from our Berlin base, and orders are usually dispatched within two working days. Dispatch and transport are at the expense of the customer. We usually ship orders with DHL but explicitly reserve the right to choose another method of transport. If an order is split into several deliveries, each delivery counts as a separate transaction.
Delivery within Germany is free of charge if your order amounts to a total of 50 euros or more. Below that amount, we charge a one-off fee of 5 euros.
Our products can also be ordered for delivery outside Germany. In that case, an estimate of the delivery costs is added to your order during checkout. Please note that this delivery cost estimate does not necessarily constitute the final amount. We shall contact you personally by email after you have placed your order to present you with delivery options and to quote the final price for delivery costs.
4. Payment options
We currently offer the following three payment options: direct debit from your bank account (only within Germany), bank transfer (prepayment) and PayPal. Once you have placed three orders, we also offer you the option to pay by invoice. Such privileges can, however, be withdrawn should we encounter repeated delays in settling invoices.
5. Cancellations, Refunds _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Returns
Should you wish to cancel your order, you can do so by notifying us by fax, email, letter or by simply returning your product(s) to Gamers HQ. No questions asked. Please note that such a cancellation has to be done within two weeks after having received your ordered product(s). Should you have already paid for your order, we shall refund those costs to you as soon as we have received your cancellation notification.
Please ensure that any products returned are in good condition. If you check the products in a manner that you will have done, for example, in a shop, this is fine. Any other handling of the product(s) might entitle Gamers HQ to some compensation from you, which might in rare cases amount to the original sum paid for the product(s). So should you feel that you might cancel your order by returning the products, please limit your inspection of the products to optical checks and do not use them on a regular basis.
If you return your order within two weeks in the above manner, we shall refund you the costs for sending the product(s) back to us (unless your cancelled order amounts less than 20 euros, in which case you as the customer will bear the cost of return postage). Please ensure that you use appropriate packing material when sending back the product(s) — preferably using the original wrapping.
Please note that German law, following the EU directive 97/7/EG of 20 May 1997, specifies that the right to return items and receive a full refund is not applicable to the purchase of newspapers, magazines or journals (§312d BGB) as well as the purchase of audio- or video-recordings and software once you have broken the seal of the package.
Should we accidently send you the wrong products, please return them to us and we shall refund you the return postage immediately. Any cancellation of an order has to be done in writing (by post, fax or email).
6. Ownership
Please note that ordered products remain our property until you have fully paid for them.
7. Personal data
We are committed to protecting your personal information and will keep the information you entrust to us safely and securely.
We may collect information from you to monitor website visitor patterns, so that we can improve our website. We also collect information from you to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products and services, update our records and generally maintain your customer profile with us. However, we shall never sell or share your personal information with third parties.
Our customer data — in so far as required to provide the above services and within the limits defined by the data protection laws of Germany (paragraph 26 BDSG) — is saved and handled on a separate, network-independent computer.
8. Other matters
We reserve the right to reject orders without any explanation. Also please note that you as a customer cannot assert a claim against Gamers HQ if, for whatever reason, we are unable to source the item(s) you have ordered. Such cases arise only very exceptionally; we try to ensure that everything we advertise in our web shop is in stock. Where, for whatever reason, we are unable to deliver we promptly refund in full everything you have paid.
9. Limitation of liability: external links
Although we check the content of external links provided on our website, we have no control over or responsibility for these domains to which we provide the links or which link to us. That responsibility solely rests with those who manage the respective domains.
10. Place of jurisdiction
Any disputes arising hereunder will be settled before a Berlin court. We reserve the right to choose the customer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s place of jurisdiction instead.
11. Severability clause
If parts of these terms and conditions become ineffective, the remainder of these terms still apply.
Keine Versandkosten innerhalb Deutschlands!
Innerhalb Deutschlands gilt:
Alle Spiele sind Neuware und in Orginalverpackung . Alle Preise sind inklusive der gesetzlichen Mehrwertsteuer von 7% bzw. 19%.
Die Versandkosten betragen 5,00 € innerhalb Deutschlands, bzw. weniger (z.B. Scenariobände, Magazine).
Ab einem Bestellwert von 50,00 € fallen keine Versandkosten innerhalb Deutschlands an!
Bezahlt werden kann per paypal, Vorauskasse, Bankeinzug oder direkt bei uns im Laden (wenn ihr aus Berlin kommt).
Wenn ihr noch irgendwelche Fragen habt, ruft uns an (030 79706126), schickt uns ne Mail (laden@gamers-hq.de) oder besucht unsere Homepage (www.gamers-hq.de).
AGB:
1. Allgemeines
Alle Transaktionen zwischen dem Gamers HQ und seinen Kunden unterliegen ausschließlich den nachfolgenden Allgemeinen Geschäftsbedingungen und basieren auf der Grundlage des Rechts der Bundesrepublik Deutschland.
Diese AGB gelten mit der Annahme der Sendung des Gamers-HQ als anerkannt.
2. Auftragsannahme und Preise 
Alle Angebote und Preise sind freibleibend; Liefermöglichkeit vorbehalten.
Preisänderungen, auch ohne Ankündigung, oder Irrtümer sind jederzeit vorbehalten. 
Alle Preisangaben sind in Euro und inklusive der gesetzlichen Mehrwertsteuer.
3. Lieferung
Alle Lieferungen erfolgen ab dem Gamers-HQ. 
Alle Lieferungen erfolgen auf Rechnung des Käufers. 
In der Regel liefern wir mit DHL, in besonderen Fällen kann davon abgewichen werden. Die Entscheidung hierüber liegt beim Gamer´s HQ. Alle Bestellung werden normalerweise innerhalb von 2 Werktagen verschickt. 
Teillieferungen gelten als jeweils separates Geschäft. 
Der Versand erfolgt ab einem Rechnungsbetrag von Euro 50,- € innerhalb Deutschlands versandkostenfrei. Bei Bestellungen unter diesem Betrag erheben wir innerhalb Deutschlands eine Versandkostengebühr von Euro 5,-€.
4. Zahlungsbedingungen 
Wir bieten standartmäßig 3 Möglichkeiten der Bezahlung an:
Per Bankeinzug, Vorkasse oder  per PayPal .Nach der dritten Bestellung räumen wir unseren Kunden auch die Möglichkeit des Kaufs auf Rechnung ein, wir sind jedoch befugt, diese Möglichkeit bei mehrmaligem Zahlungsverzug auch wieder zu widerrufen.
5. Rückgaberecht 
Sie können ohne Angabe von Gründen durch Erklärung per Fax, E-Mail oder einfaches Briefschreiben oder durch Rücksendung unserer Waren eine Bestellung widerrufen. Für die Absendung der Widerrufserklärung oder unserer Waren ist eine Widerrufsfrist von zwei Wochen einzuhalten, die mit Eingang unserer Lieferung bei Ihnen beginnt.
Ein Widerrufsrecht steht Ihnen - auch innerhalb der Widerrufsfrist - in keinem Fall bei folgenden Waren zu:
- Audio- oder Videoaufzeichnungen bzw. Software, wenn Sie die entsprechenden Datenträger entsiegelt haben, 
- Zeitungen, Zeitschriften und Illustrierten. 
Unsere Ware ist sofort nach der fristgerechten Ausübung des Widerrufsrechts auf unsere Kosten und Gefahr an uns zurückzusenden, wenn der Widerruf nicht bereits durch Rücksendung ausgeübt wurde. Achten Sie bitte bei der Rücksendung darauf, dass Sie eine geeignete Verpackung benutzen, vorzugsweise die Originalverpackung. Ausnahmsweise sind die Kosten der Rücksendung von Ihnen zu tragen, wenn der Rechnungswert unserer Ware nicht mehr als Euro 20,00 beträgt. In keinem Fall haben Sie die Kosten der Rücksendung zu tragen, wenn die von uns gelieferte Ware nicht der bestellten Ware entspricht.
Sollten Sie bereits den Kaufpreis für die Ware bezahlt haben, werden wir diesen nach einem Widerruf unverzüglich zurückerstatten. Wenn Sie unsere Ware nach dem Widerruf ganz oder teilweise nicht oder nur in verschlechtertem Zustand zurücksenden, sind Sie uns gesetzlich zu Wertersatz verpflichtet. Das gilt nicht, soweit Sie unsere Ware lediglich so geprüft haben, wie Sie es z.B. im Ladengeschäft hätten tun können. Jede darüber hinausgehende Nutzung der Ware berechtigt uns jedoch zu Ersatzansprüchen, die unter Umständen die Höhe des Kaufpreises erreichen können. Sollten Sie also einen Widerruf in Betracht ziehen, beschränken Sie sich möglichst auf eine optische Prüfung und nehmen Sie die Ware nicht regulär in Gebrauch.
6. Eigentumsvorbehalt
Gelieferte Artikel bleiben bis zur vollständigen Bezahlung Eigentum der Firma Gamers-HQ.
7. Datenspeicherung 
Unsere Kundendaten – soweit geschäftsnotwendig und im Rahmen des Bundesdatenschutzgesetzes (Paragraph 26 BDSG) zulässig – werden EDV-mäßig gespeichert und verarbeitet (auf einem netzexternen Rechner). Kundendaten werden unter keinen Umständen Dritten zur Verfügung gestellt.
8. Sonstiges 
Die Ablehnung von Aufträgen, auch ohne Angaben von Gründen, behalten wir uns ausdrücklich vor.
Aus Lieferschwierigkeiten unsererseits erwachsen keinerlei Ansprüche gegen das Gamers-HQ. Können Bestellungen aus irgendwelchen Gründen nicht ausgeführt werden, werden bereits geleistete Zahlungen umgehend zurückerstattet. 
9. Haftungshinweis
Trotz sorgfältiger inhaltlicher Kontrolle übernehmen wir keine Haftung für die Inhalte externer Links. Für den Inhalt der verlinkten Seiten sind ausschließlich deren Betreiber verantwortlich.
10. Gerichtsstand
Erfüllungsort und Gerichtsstand ist für beide Teile Berlin.
Nach unserer Wahl kann auch am allgemeinen Gerichtsstand des Kunden geklagt werden.
11. Salvatorische Klausel 
Die Unwirksamkeit einzelner Bestimmungen berührt die Gültigkeit der Geschäftsbedingungen im übrigen nicht.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:18:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 05:10:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>49.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>CLS Games - Atlanta_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s Board Game Warehouse - is the largest retailer of board games in metro Atlanta! All games are new _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; still in factory shrink-wrap.
PURSUIT OF GLORY: $49.95
GMT Games [GMT 0810]
SHIPPING
Continental U.S. - $14.95
International (Including AK _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; HI) - TBD</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 20:32:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 01:21:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for Gregg Casillo - auction winner</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 20:17:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 02 May 2014 22:09:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened but unpunched</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 08 May 2014 03:27:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 09 May 2014 01:47:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>59</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Brand new in shrink wrap. No damage to box. No tears in shrink wrap. Price does not include postage. Send email for shipping quote from zip code 11365 in the USA. </notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 10 May 2014 23:31:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 02:03:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New in the factory shrink wrap. No wear or damage to the box.
No holes in the shrink wrap. Price does not include postage. Send email for shipping quote from zip code 11365 in the USA.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 12:20:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 15:38:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>52</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink. Check out my other games for sale!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 20:25:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 16:34:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>25</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, played, still like new.
Paypal please. 
I ship to CONUS only.  
$25.00 plus $12.00 Priority Mail.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 16:19:43 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 18:46:26 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; in excellent condition. The cards are out of shrink but are in plastic bags.
UK postage £5 by Myhermes.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 23:06:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 10:38:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New in factory shrink wrap. No damage to box. A few small holes in shrink wrap. 
Price does not include postage. Send email for shipping quote from zip code 11365 in the USA.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 02:04:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 21:05:27 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened and examined but never played. Game is in like new condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 02:57:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 14:00:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Rules read, cards unpacked and looked at.  Counters never punched, never played.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 16:52:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 11:52:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>29</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 18:52:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 15:15:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>44</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>New....opened but unpunched and never played. I will pay for Parcel Post shipping to you in the U.S.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 00:59:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 06:12:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrinkwrap
Payments: PayPal or US Postal money orders.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 22:28:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 01:05:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>38</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>2008 GMT Games. Unpunched, complete, in very good condition. The game once had a smokey odor (from previous owner), but it seems to have sufficiently aired out.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 06:58:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 00:09:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, out of shrink, cards out of shrink. Includes C3i addenda/errata counters. Shipping not included; method is up to you, I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m happy to price-check any of them since I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m not looking to make a cent on that side of the deal.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 17 May 2014 12:35:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 22:29:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in shrink.  For American buyers, ask about the possibility of my shipping to you from within the States during one of my trips.  Insurance is strongly encouraged, and paid by the buyer.  The price is in U.S. dollars.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 03:46:28 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 06:07:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In the shrinkwrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 11 May 2015 19:02:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 17 May 2015 13:45:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>55</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in original shrinkwrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 31 May 2015 00:28:42 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 08:50:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>34</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 21:44:19 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 14:10:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>70</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>shrinkwrapped</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 29 May 2015 14:43:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 14:45:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>63</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>*** With every sale we donate a percentage to the Veterans Support Foundation (including this sale). ***
Wargame Depot has donated over $7,500 to this wonderful cause thanks, largely, to the wonderful Boardgamegeek community. Thank you so much for your continued support of Wargame Depot which has allowed us to give generously to the VSF.
Mint, in shrink copy available.  No dings, no dents, or anything wrong with the game.  Non-smoking environment and kept in a humidity-controlled location.
$12 shipping to US - write me for a quote to the rest of the world.
I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m the owner of Wargame Depot so a purchase from me will always be packed professionally and I can accept Paypal, MO/Check, or MC/Visa/Discover/AMEX.
And if you want this game plus anything else that I am selling on BGG, I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll of course be happy to add other items on in order to save you on shipping!
North Carolina residents pay 7% sales tax.
Cheers,
Jason
PS:  We have many Osprey books in stock not listed on BGG.  The prices are well under publisher rates; if you are interested in them, please let me know!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 18:18:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 20:34:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>69.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Partially punched, excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 15:25:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 23:55:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>67</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>*** With every sale we donate a percentage to the Veterans Support Foundation (including this sale). ***
Wargame Depot has donated over $7,500 to this wonderful cause thanks, largely, to the wonderful Boardgamegeek community. Thank you so much for your continued support of Wargame Depot which has allowed us to give generously to the VSF.
Mint, in shrink copy available.  No dings, no dents, or anything wrong with the game.  Non-smoking environment and kept in a humidity-controlled location.
$12 shipping to US - write me for a quote to the rest of the world.
I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m the owner of Wargame Depot so a purchase from me will always be packed professionally and I can accept Paypal, MO/Check, or MC/Visa/Discover/AMEX.
And if you want this game plus anything else that I am selling on BGG, I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ll of course be happy to add other items on in order to save you on shipping!
North Carolina residents pay 7% sales tax.
Cheers,
Jason
PS:  We have many Osprey books in stock not listed on BGG.  The prices are well under publisher rates; if you are interested in them, please let me know!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 20 May 2015 12:12:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 19:10:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Game is unpunched and in excellent shape.
I will ship anywhere in the world and never ask more then actual shipping costs. Shipping of multiple items can be combined.
Payment through PayPal (worldwide) or bank transfer (within EU).
Any questions? Just ask!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 15:56:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 12:13:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, complete in very good condition.
Shipping anywhere in Europe: 14 euros
Shipping anywhere else in the world: 20 euros</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 00:56:14 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 01:15:33 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.  Never touched.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 08:23:08 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 09:51:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>70</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, like new.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 10:25:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 23:49:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>79</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched, but never played. Excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 21:39:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 23:08:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>counters punched, trimmed and sorted in plastic tray. cards sleeved. includes living rules 2010. play aids in document protectors.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:48:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 05 Oct 2015 18:39:09 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>52</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>For user throwingmuse only.
Punched, counters in tray. $8 shipping in U.S. Check out my other games for sale!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 17:25:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:56:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>64.99</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Cards in SHRINK, counters UNPUNCHED, all in great shape!</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 21:17:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 19:03:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched no shrink. Complete</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 17:36:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 02:34:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>40</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Never played.  Counters clipped and shrink removed from cards.  Near perfect condition.  Slight self wear from me taking it off the shelf and putting it back on.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:33:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 11:00:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>47.5</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened but unplayed.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 12:06:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 14:41:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>25</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/201336/item/4330286#4330286]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;GMT Games clearout, with Dan Verssen and Worthington in the mix_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 05:58:47 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 18:33:16 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Complete and unpunched, cards in shrink.  It has done nothing but sit on my shelf.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 16:54:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 01:33:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>80</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Brand new in shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 23:21:44 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 06:53:49 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Like new. Only outer shrink removed.
Add 13.00 for shipping via USPS.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 16:46:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:34:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>65</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched, opened once to check contents.
Paypal + fees</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 18:33:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 15 May 2016 21:05:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched and bagged but unplayed</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 18 May 2016 11:27:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 18 May 2016 14:03:27 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>70</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unwrapped, unplayed, punched incl. pastic boxes for the counters</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 03:06:57 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 15:03:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched but removed from shrink wrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 19:32:10 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 16:13:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched, clipped (OL 2.5mm), counters in GMT tray, cards sleeved, and box has minor shelf wear.  local pickup available near san diego, otherwise i will use usps or fedex.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 21:48:52 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 06:37:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>The game is like new, complete, never played and counters uncut.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 15:26:27 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 18:54:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>75</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 18:36:36 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 15:39:32 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>85</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in original shrink.  One very small corner ding.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 19:30:00 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 13:17:39 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>40</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>U.K. Postage £2.85</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 13:35:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 14:00:44 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>45</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/215813/item/4965040#4965040]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Huge Auction - Wargames, A_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;A, Risk, CDGs, Netrunner, etc._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 12:59:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 22:04:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>35</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Have laminated map only played once.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 21:59:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 20:27:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Only the shrink wrap removed. New.
$15.00 shipping CONUS, overseas based on estimated cost.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:32:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 04:53:38 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>75</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 17:09:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 02:45:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>69.95</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>This is brand new in shrink. Domestic shipping is $13. Shipping to Canada is $60. All other international locations is $75 . I ALWAYS combine shipping on multiple purchases at +$1 per item.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 02:00:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 16:30:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>80</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink mint condition game, never opened.  I shall pay shipping USPS in U.S. If you desire another shipping method or need to insure it you must pay the cost. Once payment clears I shall ship the game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 22:24:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 00:06:48 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Still in shrinkwrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 15:17:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 03:50:37 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>74</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Includes an extra copy of the rules and a laminated copy of the player aid cards.  All counters are tastefully clipped.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 01:50:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:44:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>94.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 15:11:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 20:11:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched in excellent condition - cards still in shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 19:53:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 02:35:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='CAD'>55</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>The game is complete, unplayed and unpunched. The cards are stored in deck protectors. There are no box dents but there is some visible shelf wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 03:49:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 04:22:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>110</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Counters unpunched; cards out of shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 12:52:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 09:10:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Never played</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 01:50:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 02 May 2017 18:05:07 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>99.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 06 May 2017 03:38:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 06 May 2017 15:41:36 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened but unplayed. Counters are arranged in counter-traces.
Shipping prices:
Germany: 6,99€
I don´t know the exactly weight. The international shipping prices from Germany are graduated up to 2kg (4lbs) or more than 2kg (4lbs). 
If the weight is less than 2kg, it´s:
Europe: 9€
Overseas: 18€
If it´s more than 2kg:
Europe: 18€
Overseas: 38€
If the game weight is less than 2kg, I´ll send the difference back.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 10:21:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 13:13:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>55</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 01:24:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 01:33:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>84.94</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched.  Cards have been sleeved.  Contents verified complete and in like new condition.  Obviously has not been played.  Great game from a great system now out of print.  Box is square and straight with no dings, doinks or creases.  Very little edge wear or corner rubbing.  4 strong tight corners.  Nice copy.  Worldwide shipping and will be packed well.  All forms of negotiable instruments considered.  Combine ship with multiple purchases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 14:04:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 15:22:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>105</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>The game is  new,unpunched and shrinkwrapped
COSTI DI SPEDIZIONE / SHIPPING COST
ITALIA:
LA SPEDIZIONE SARA_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039; EFFETTUATA CON SPEDIREWEB - SDA Euro 7,00
EUROPA - U.S.A. - CANADA - ASIA - AUSTRALIA:
THE DISPATCH OF THE GAME WILL HAVE EFFECTED WITH THE SERVICE OF FOREIGN RECOMMENDED LETTER OF POSTE ITALIANE 
L_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;ENVOI DU JEU EST EFFECTUÉ PAR SERVICE DE POSTE LETTRE RECOMMANDÉE ÉTRANGÈRE DES POSTE ITALIANE : 
EUROPA: 19 Euro 
UNITED STATES - CANADA - ASIA: 29,00 Euro 
AUSTRALIA: 34,00 Euro 
If you are in doubt about any aspect please Email me with any question.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 21:49:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 14:19:35 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>1</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>C3i STUFF ONLY - NOT THE ENTIRE GAME - DOES NOT INCLUDE MAGAZINE(s)
From C3i #23:
Replacement counters (2)
Feel free to look over my entire BGG collection as nearly everything can be available for purchase and discounts may be available if multiple items are purchased at the same time.
PayPal accepted with Verified Account/Verified Address.
USPS Money Orders accepted.
Personal checks accepted only if drawn on BB_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;T bank.
Collectibles, easily damaged or higher value items require insured shipment.
Please ask for more information or images if you have a particular question or concern about a game.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 14:09:09 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:40:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>punched/clipped, excellent shape</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 15:26:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 19:31:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Never played, so it_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s mint. Bought it new and was never able to get anyone in my group interested. Hate to see such a fine game sit unplayed. Time to sell.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 15:30:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 19:56:20 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>66</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>In shrink-wrap.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 20:52:24 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 21:17:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>80</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>unpunched 
buyer pay fees of pay pal.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 07:44:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 11:07:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>44.99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched and carefully clipped ...played once or twice
Please request postage fees prior to purchase ...
Payment by Paypal only thank you ...
Ric</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 17:36:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 01:37:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>80</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Clean, punched, carefully clipped copy with minor shelf wear.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:14:05 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 06:20:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>100</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Factory shrinked.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 07:08:54 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 12:34:13 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>95</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:26:30 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 19:03:27 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>99</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Only played this game once.
All components are present and in good condition.
The paper board folds are slightly worn out only from a single use.
From a smoke free home, very well stored.
Cleaning out the closet.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 12 May 2017 18:10:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 11:55:17 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>89</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Shipping Germany  5 Euro
Shipping European Union 9 Euro
Shipping World         16 Euro
PayPal plus max. 5 Euro
SEPA transfer via IBAN/BIC usually free</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 18:29:59 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:51:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>90</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>all components accounted for and still in excellent condition: counters nicely (i.e. barely) clipped in baggies; cards are sleeved</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 18:06:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:36:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>50</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>box is scuffed up. counters are punched. cards are sleeved (penny). shipping is from spokane wa</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 23:44:41 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 23:54:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>cards in shrink, unpunched. added for Andrew - already paid for it.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 18:04:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 04:50:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='AUD'>65</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unused</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 16:34:13 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 16:27:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>139</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>VG condition, unpunched, includes 2 errata counters, PM me with questions, buyer pays actual shipping cost.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 18:20:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 02:48:12 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>99.94</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched not clipped.  Contents verified complete and in excellent condition.  Have verified all counters and cards.  It may have been played but it shows with very little wear. Box is square and straight with little to no wear.  4 strong tight corners.  No dings, doinks or creases.  Worldwide shipping and will be packed well.  All forms of negotiable instruments considered.  Combine ship with multiple purchases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 01:25:02 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 04:17:45 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>New except shrink wrap was taken off the box and the card decks.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 17:27:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 18:15:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>50</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>unplayed.  Photographs on demand</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 18:11:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 05 May 2018 13:27:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>105</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This game has been opened, and the cards have been removed from their cellophane, but it is unpunched and has never been played.  It is in very good condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:43:49 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 17 May 2018 20:21:47 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>40</price>
    <condition>good</condition>
    <notes>In excellent condition.
Played through a few times. 
Units are all bagged up by country and type etc 
There are 2 pieces missing (i.e units), this is out of several hundred. All cards and other pieces are present in excellent condition.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 20:09:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 13:35:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>125</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>still in shrink</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 20:15:58 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 19:12:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>75</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Slight wear on box edges being up against other games but all components in excellent condition.
All cards sleeved and GMTGames tray provided.  Some wargame chits clipped.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 13:20:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 06:29:43 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unminted. Price excluding shipping</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 03:43:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 20:23:51 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>99.94</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Punched and corner nipped.  Contents verified complete and in excellent condition.  Have verified all counters and cards (includes 2nd deck of unused cards).  It may have been played but it shows with very little wear. Box is square and straight with little to no wear.  4 strong tight corners.  No dings, doinks or creases.  Worldwide shipping and will be packed well.  All forms of negotiable instruments considered.  Combine ship with multiple purchases.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 20:44:16 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 04:54:24 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>125</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>in original shrink wrap</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:04:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 06:56:34 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>75</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 02:12:01 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 04:57:21 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>65</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched. Cards in shrink.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 06:32:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 20:56:01 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>69</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Very good / like new condition. Counters punched, map new, cards still in shrink.
Shipping within Germany + 6 €, EU + 15 €. 
Payment by PayPal to friends or IBAN.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 19:13:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 01:20:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>70</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>All components in excellent condition.
Counters punched and sorted into tray.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:29:31 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 08:12:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>109.49</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>CONDITION: Like new.
PAYMENT: Bank transfer is free. Paypal is +2€.
SHIPPING: Germany 4,99€, EU 9,99€.
SHIPPING: For multiple games Germany 5,99€, EU 11,99€ (GRE/BUL/CRO/ROM 18,99€).
SHIPPING: Pickup at our weekly game night in Berlin is possible.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 01:29:23 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 19:34:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>130</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This copy is in the original shrink wrap.  Great follow up to Paths of Glory.  
Shipping via USPS Priority Mail only.  I_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;m happy to combine items for shipping.  4lbs from 43035.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 04:41:26 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 07:22:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 19:44:33 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:05:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>79</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Unpunched</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 19:22:53 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 16:15:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>89.49</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>CONDITION: Very Good, but the box has a dent on the cover.
PAYMENT: Bank transfer is free. Paypal is +2€.
SHIPPING: Germany 4,99€, EU 9,99€.
SHIPPING: For multiple games Germany 5,99€, EU 11,99€ (GRE/BUL/CRO/ROM 18,99€).
SHIPPING: Pickup at our weekly game night in Berlin is possible.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 04:01:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 04:30:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Shrink off the box, game has never been played. 
Shipping $10
Any questions please ask.
non-smoker</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 23:09:04 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:33:04 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>88</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Shrink removed, otherwise brand new</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:44:29 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:47:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>90</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Clean, unpunched copy with spae deck of cards. Both decks of cards in shrinkwrap.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:29:55 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 15:26:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>95</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>All components in very good condition.  Counters unpunched.  Cards in shrinkwrap.
Shipping costs extra. Shipping from Maryland (21146). Will ship worldwide but note that it will be expensive (better to have someone receive it for you in the U.S.). Regional Rate box for cheaper shipping in U.S. will be used if allowed.
Shipping costs can be combined if you purchase other items that I am selling.
PayPal for payment. USPS for shipment.
If you are outside the U.S., please add 2 percent of the total (to include shipping costs) to cover the extra PayPal fees.</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
