<boardgames termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
     <boardgame objectid="163166">
   <yearpublished>2015</yearpublished>
   <minplayers>3</minplayers>
   <maxplayers>7</maxplayers>
   <playingtime>10</playingtime>
   <minplaytime>10</minplaytime>
   <maxplaytime>10</maxplaytime>
   <age>8</age>
       <name  sortindex="1">1 Nacht Weerwolven _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Waaghalzen: Dageraad</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Loup-garou pour un crépuscule</name>
       <name primary="true" sortindex="1">One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak</name>
       <name  sortindex="1">Werwölfe Morgengrauen</name>
         
   <description>One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak is a fast game for 3-7 players in which everyone gets a hidden role, each with a special ability. (No plain _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot;villagers_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp;quot; here!) In the course of a single morning, your village will decide who among them is a werewolf...because all it takes is finding one werewolf to win!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;Daybreak includes eleven new roles, and it can be played on its own or combined with the original One Night Ultimate Werewolf game; when combined, you can have up to ten players in a single game._T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_lt;br/_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_gt;</description>
       <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/Eanbyzhr7UKIu2k-rg9Nah4ebrs=/fit-in/200x150/pic2225958.jpg</thumbnail>
    <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/7CB2n5DttYL0VT4aQm0pj9ZQLos=/0x0/pic2225958.jpg</image>
      
            <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="175924">#116 – Tabletop – Ted Alspach</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                             <boardgamehonor objectid="34507">2015 Golden Geek Best Party Board Game Nominee</boardgamehonor>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="6046">Ted Alspach</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgameartist objectid="70607">Gus Batts</boardgameartist>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="5774">Bézier Games</boardgamepublisher>
                      <boardgamecategory objectid="1023">Bluffing</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1002">Card Game</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="8374">Crowdfunding: Kickstarter</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="188794">Cult of the New Board Game Podcast Episode 000 (2016) – Top 25 Games</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                      <boardgamecategory objectid="1039">Deduction</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="139326">Dukes of Dice - Ep. 32 - Expansion Roundup</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgameversion objectid="281359">Dutch edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="247207">English first edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="412132">English second edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="164043">Ep 24 Horror Games</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="133247">Episode 3: Expedition Northwest Passage, Robocop, BGGcon, and Skulls of the Shogun</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="169866">Episode 41 - Viticulture Essential Edition BA Holiday Special</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="131909">Essen 2014 - Daybreak</boardgamepodcastepisode>
                      <boardgameversion objectid="330105">French edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgameversion objectid="338515">German edition</boardgameversion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1024">Horror</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="132679">MN 0025 Expansions!</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamepodcastepisode objectid="151532">MN 0062 Werewolf</boardgamepodcastepisode>
               <boardgamedesigner objectid="69462">Akihisa Okui</boardgamedesigner>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="27945">One Night</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="204431">One Night Ultimate Alien</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="255293">One Night Ultimate Super Villains</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="180956">One Night Ultimate Vampire</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="147949">One Night Ultimate Werewolf</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameaccessory objectid="170112">One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak: Playmat</boardgameaccessory>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="168633">One Night Ultimate Werewolf: Bonus Pack 1</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="184075">One Night Ultimate Werewolf: Bonus Pack 2</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="228578">One Night Ultimate Werewolf: Bonus Pack 3</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgamecategory objectid="1030">Party Game</boardgamecategory>
               <boardgamesubdomain objectid="5498">Party Games</boardgamesubdomain>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="34">Ravensburger Spieleverlag GmbH</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgamemechanic objectid="2028">Role Playing</boardgamemechanic>
                      <boardgamemechanic objectid="2015">Variable Player Powers</boardgamemechanic>
                      <boardgamemechanic objectid="2017">Voting</boardgamemechanic>
               <boardgamefamily objectid="2989">Werewolf / Mafia</boardgamefamily>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="186273">Werwölfe Vollmondnacht: Der Prinz</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgameexpansion objectid="267734">Werwölfe Vollmondnacht: Nachwuchs-Gerber</boardgameexpansion>
               <boardgamepublisher objectid="4932">White Goblin Games</boardgamepublisher>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="204431" inbound="true">One Night Ultimate Alien</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="255293" inbound="true">One Night Ultimate Super Villains</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="180956" inbound="true">One Night Ultimate Vampire</boardgameintegration>
               <boardgameintegration objectid="147949" inbound="true">One Night Ultimate Werewolf</boardgameintegration>
      
   <poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="18">
   
  <results numplayers="1">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="12" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="2">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="12" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="3">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="9" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="4">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="9" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="2" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="5">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="8" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="1" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="6">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="11" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="3" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="7">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="12" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="2" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
   
  <results numplayers="7+">  
     <result value="Best" numvotes="6" />
     <result value="Recommended" numvotes="5" />
     <result value="Not Recommended" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="7">
   
  <results>  
     <result level="1" value="No necessary in-game text" numvotes="4" />
     <result level="2" value="Some necessary text - easily memorized or small crib sheet" numvotes="3" />
     <result level="3" value="Moderate in-game text - needs crib sheet or paste ups" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="4" value="Extensive use of text - massive conversion needed to be playable" numvotes="0" />
     <result level="5" value="Unplayable in another language" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   <poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="6">
   <results>  
     <result value="2" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="3" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="4" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="5" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="6" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="8" numvotes="4" />
     <result value="10" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="12" numvotes="1" />
     <result value="14" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="16" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="18" numvotes="0" />
     <result value="21 and up" numvotes="0" />
    </results>     
 </poll>
   
   
      <statistics page="1">
            <ratings >
     <usersrated>3792</usersrated>
     <average>7.45759</average>
     <bayesaverage>6.95097</bayesaverage>
     
     <ranks>
       
              <rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="393" bayesaverage="6.95097" />
            
       
              <rank type="family" id="5498" name="partygames" friendlyname="Party Game Rank" value="15" bayesaverage="7.23452" />
            
           </ranks>
     
     <stddev>1.5257</stddev>
     <median>0</median>
     <owned>9376</owned>
     <trading>129</trading>
     <wanting>101</wanting>
     <wishing>717</wishing>
     <numcomments>672</numcomments>
     <numweights>76</numweights>
     <averageweight>1.4605</averageweight>
    </ratings>
               </statistics>
  
    <marketplacehistory>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 07:26:51 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 15:36:57 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>60</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Free Shipping.  Kickstarter edition includes extras that will not be in retail version.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 16:40:25 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 17:35:11 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>59.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Free Shipping.  Kickstarter edition includes extras that will not be in retail version.
Three new role cards: Aura Seer, Cursed, and Prince.
Three new alternative artwork cards for: Werewolf, Werewolf, and Tanner
Three new artifact tokens: Bow of Hunter, Cloak of the Prince, and Sword of the Bodyguard.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 02:10:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 02:17:19 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>30</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Open but unplayed kickstarter.  Free shipping when you buy any three games from me.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 13:01:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 09:53:02 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>60</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Includes:
One Night Ultimate Werewolf
One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak
One Night Ultimate Werewolf Bonus Pack 1
One Night Ultimate Werewolf Playmat
All Cards are sleeved in Premium sleeves
Postage is £10 in the UK Tracked</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 16:43:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 20:00:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>25.95</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>All games are new and in their original wrapping and all prices include the German VAT (7% or 19%).
We offer only goods that we have in stock.
We ship worldwide – please ask for a quote about exact shipping costs (rest assured that we always try to keep them as low as possible).
Payment may be made by Paypal or bank transfer in advance.
For orders above €50 we grant a discount of €5 on shipping costs.
If you have any questions, feel free to send us an email (laden@gamers-hq.de), give us a call (+49 30 79706126) or visit our homepage (www.gamers-hq.de).
Our Terms and Conditions
1. General
All transactions between Gamers HQ and you, the customer, are subject to the following conditions, which you acknowledge by accepting delivery of your ordered products. These conditions do not affect your statutory rights and in all cases German law applies.
2. Orders and prices
We do our level best to ensure that the information on our website is up-to-date. Please note that offers and prices are subject to change. We work to ensure that our prices are all correct, but cannot be held responsible for accidentally displaying the wrong price of a product.
All prices are quoted in Euros and already include all necessary taxes.
3. Lead times and delivery costs
Our products are delivered directly from our Berlin base, and orders are usually dispatched within two working days. Dispatch and transport are at the expense of the customer. We usually ship orders with DHL but explicitly reserve the right to choose another method of transport. If an order is split into several deliveries, each delivery counts as a separate transaction.
Delivery within Germany is free of charge if your order amounts to a total of 50 euros or more. Below that amount, we charge a one-off fee of 5 euros.
Our products can also be ordered for delivery outside Germany. In that case, an estimate of the delivery costs is added to your order during checkout. Please note that this delivery cost estimate does not necessarily constitute the final amount. We shall contact you personally by email after you have placed your order to present you with delivery options and to quote the final price for delivery costs.
4. Payment options
We currently offer the following three payment options: direct debit from your bank account (only within Germany), bank transfer (prepayment) and PayPal. Once you have placed three orders, we also offer you the option to pay by invoice. Such privileges can, however, be withdrawn should we encounter repeated delays in settling invoices.
5. Cancellations, Refunds _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Returns
Should you wish to cancel your order, you can do so by notifying us by fax, email, letter or by simply returning your product(s) to Gamers HQ. No questions asked. Please note that such a cancellation has to be done within two weeks after having received your ordered product(s). Should you have already paid for your order, we shall refund those costs to you as soon as we have received your cancellation notification.
Please ensure that any products returned are in good condition. If you check the products in a manner that you will have done, for example, in a shop, this is fine. Any other handling of the product(s) might entitle Gamers HQ to some compensation from you, which might in rare cases amount to the original sum paid for the product(s). So should you feel that you might cancel your order by returning the products, please limit your inspection of the products to optical checks and do not use them on a regular basis.
If you return your order within two weeks in the above manner, we shall refund you the costs for sending the product(s) back to us (unless your cancelled order amounts less than 20 euros, in which case you as the customer will bear the cost of return postage). Please ensure that you use appropriate packing material when sending back the product(s) — preferably using the original wrapping.
Please note that German law, following the EU directive 97/7/EG of 20 May 1997, specifies that the right to return items and receive a full refund is not applicable to the purchase of newspapers, magazines or journals (§312d BGB) as well as the purchase of audio- or video-recordings and software once you have broken the seal of the package.
Should we accidently send you the wrong products, please return them to us and we shall refund you the return postage immediately. Any cancellation of an order has to be done in writing (by post, fax or email).
6. Ownership
Please note that ordered products remain our property until you have fully paid for them.
7. Personal data
We are committed to protecting your personal information and will keep the information you entrust to us safely and securely.
We may collect information from you to monitor website visitor patterns, so that we can improve our website. We also collect information from you to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products and services, update our records and generally maintain your customer profile with us. However, we shall never sell or share your personal information with third parties.
Our customer data — in so far as required to provide the above services and within the limits defined by the data protection laws of Germany (paragraph 26 BDSG) — is saved and handled on a separate, network-independent computer.
8. Other matters
We reserve the right to reject orders without any explanation. Also please note that you as a customer cannot assert a claim against Gamers HQ if, for whatever reason, we are unable to source the item(s) you have ordered. Such cases arise only very exceptionally; we try to ensure that everything we advertise in our web shop is in stock. Where, for whatever reason, we are unable to deliver we promptly refund in full everything you have paid.
9. Limitation of liability: external links
Although we check the content of external links provided on our website, we have no control over or responsibility for these domains to which we provide the links or which link to us. That responsibility solely rests with those who manage the respective domains.
10. Place of jurisdiction
Any disputes arising hereunder will be settled before a Berlin court. We reserve the right to choose the customer_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;s place of jurisdiction instead.
11. Severability clause
If parts of these terms and conditions become ineffective, the remainder of these terms still apply.
Innerhalb Deutschlands gilt:
Alle Spiele sind Neuware und in Orginalverpackung . Alle Preise sind inklusive der gesetzlichen Mehrwertsteuer von 7% bzw. 19%.
Die Versandkosten betragen 5,00 € innerhalb Deutschlands, bzw. weniger (z.B. Scenariobände, Magazine).
Ab einem Bestellwert von 50,00 € fallen keine Versandkosten innerhalb Deutschlands an!
Bezahlt werden kann per paypal, Vorauskasse, Bankeinzug oder direkt bei uns im Laden (wenn ihr aus Berlin kommt).
Wenn ihr noch irgendwelche Fragen habt, ruft uns an (030 79706126), schickt uns ne Mail (laden@gamers-hq.de) oder besucht unsere Homepage (www.gamers-hq.de).
AGB:
1. Allgemeines
Alle Transaktionen zwischen dem Gamers HQ und seinen Kunden unterliegen ausschließlich den nachfolgenden Allgemeinen Geschäftsbedingungen und basieren auf der Grundlage des Rechts der Bundesrepublik Deutschland.
Diese AGB gelten mit der Annahme der Sendung des Gamers-HQ als anerkannt.
2. Auftragsannahme und Preise 
Alle Angebote und Preise sind freibleibend; Liefermöglichkeit vorbehalten.
Preisänderungen, auch ohne Ankündigung, oder Irrtümer sind jederzeit vorbehalten. 
Alle Preisangaben sind in Euro und inklusive der gesetzlichen Mehrwertsteuer.
3. Lieferung
Alle Lieferungen erfolgen ab dem Gamers-HQ. 
Alle Lieferungen erfolgen auf Rechnung des Käufers. 
In der Regel liefern wir mit DHL, in besonderen Fällen kann davon abgewichen werden. Die Entscheidung hierüber liegt beim Gamer´s HQ. Alle Bestellung werden normalerweise innerhalb von 2 Werktagen verschickt. 
Teillieferungen gelten als jeweils separates Geschäft. 
Der Versand erfolgt ab einem Rechnungsbetrag von Euro 50,- € innerhalb Deutschlands versandkostenfrei. Bei Bestellungen unter diesem Betrag erheben wir innerhalb Deutschlands eine Versandkostengebühr von Euro 5,-€.
4. Zahlungsbedingungen 
Wir bieten standartmäßig 3 Möglichkeiten der Bezahlung an:
Per Bankeinzug, Vorkasse oder  per PayPal .Nach der dritten Bestellung räumen wir unseren Kunden auch die Möglichkeit des Kaufs auf Rechnung ein, wir sind jedoch befugt, diese Möglichkeit bei mehrmaligem Zahlungsverzug auch wieder zu widerrufen.
5. Rückgaberecht 
Sie können ohne Angabe von Gründen durch Erklärung per Fax, E-Mail oder einfaches Briefschreiben oder durch Rücksendung unserer Waren eine Bestellung widerrufen. Für die Absendung der Widerrufserklärung oder unserer Waren ist eine Widerrufsfrist von zwei Wochen einzuhalten, die mit Eingang unserer Lieferung bei Ihnen beginnt.
Ein Widerrufsrecht steht Ihnen - auch innerhalb der Widerrufsfrist - in keinem Fall bei folgenden Waren zu:
- Audio- oder Videoaufzeichnungen bzw. Software, wenn Sie die entsprechenden Datenträger entsiegelt haben, 
- Zeitungen, Zeitschriften und Illustrierten. 
Unsere Ware ist sofort nach der fristgerechten Ausübung des Widerrufsrechts auf unsere Kosten und Gefahr an uns zurückzusenden, wenn der Widerruf nicht bereits durch Rücksendung ausgeübt wurde. Achten Sie bitte bei der Rücksendung darauf, dass Sie eine geeignete Verpackung benutzen, vorzugsweise die Originalverpackung. Ausnahmsweise sind die Kosten der Rücksendung von Ihnen zu tragen, wenn der Rechnungswert unserer Ware nicht mehr als Euro 20,00 beträgt. In keinem Fall haben Sie die Kosten der Rücksendung zu tragen, wenn die von uns gelieferte Ware nicht der bestellten Ware entspricht.
Sollten Sie bereits den Kaufpreis für die Ware bezahlt haben, werden wir diesen nach einem Widerruf unverzüglich zurückerstatten. Wenn Sie unsere Ware nach dem Widerruf ganz oder teilweise nicht oder nur in verschlechtertem Zustand zurücksenden, sind Sie uns gesetzlich zu Wertersatz verpflichtet. Das gilt nicht, soweit Sie unsere Ware lediglich so geprüft haben, wie Sie es z.B. im Ladengeschäft hätten tun können. Jede darüber hinausgehende Nutzung der Ware berechtigt uns jedoch zu Ersatzansprüchen, die unter Umständen die Höhe des Kaufpreises erreichen können. Sollten Sie also einen Widerruf in Betracht ziehen, beschränken Sie sich möglichst auf eine optische Prüfung und nehmen Sie die Ware nicht regulär in Gebrauch.
6. Eigentumsvorbehalt
Gelieferte Artikel bleiben bis zur vollständigen Bezahlung Eigentum der Firma Gamers-HQ.
7. Datenspeicherung 
Unsere Kundendaten – soweit geschäftsnotwendig und im Rahmen des Bundesdatenschutzgesetzes (Paragraph 26 BDSG) zulässig – werden EDV-mäßig gespeichert und verarbeitet (auf einem netzexternen Rechner). Kundendaten werden unter keinen Umständen Dritten zur Verfügung gestellt.
8. Sonstiges 
Die Ablehnung von Aufträgen, auch ohne Angaben von Gründen, behalten wir uns ausdrücklich vor.
Aus Lieferschwierigkeiten unsererseits erwachsen keinerlei Ansprüche gegen das Gamers-HQ. Können Bestellungen aus irgendwelchen Gründen nicht ausgeführt werden, werden bereits geleistete Zahlungen umgehend zurückerstattet. 
9. Haftungshinweis
Trotz sorgfältiger inhaltlicher Kontrolle übernehmen wir keine Haftung für die Inhalte externer Links. Für den Inhalt der verlinkten Seiten sind ausschließlich deren Betreiber verantwortlich.
10. Gerichtsstand
Erfüllungsort und Gerichtsstand ist für beide Teile Berlin.
Nach unserer Wahl kann auch am allgemeinen Gerichtsstand des Kunden geklagt werden.
11. Salvatorische Klausel 
Die Unwirksamkeit einzelner Bestimmungen berührt die Gültigkeit der Geschäftsbedingungen im übrigen nicht.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 22:08:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 04 May 2015 14:57:58 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12.5</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>★ CURRENT SALE: 8%
★ Condition: Brand new in shrink wrap
☆ Same as:
http://amzn.to/1amQIYb
——————
★ Shipping Information
Shipping: $5.75 Expedited
No combined shipping discounts
No international shipping
Non-negotiable
——————
★ Sales Tax
Sales Tax collected for the following states: AZ, CA, CT, FL, GA, IN, KS, MD, MA, MN, NV, NJ, NY, NC, ND, PA, TN, TX, VA, WA, WV, WI
——————
★ Accepted Payment Methods:
☆ Same Day Processing:
* Any Credit Card
* Google Wallet (Fastest)
* Venmo
* Bitcoin
* Verified Paypal Gift/Friends _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; Family
☆ 3-5 Day Processing:
* Verified Paypal Goods/Services
Non-payment will result in order cancellation. Please pay promptly within 24 hours following order confirmation to prevent cancellation. Price fluctuations may cause order cancellation. Prompt payment will help prevent cancellation due to fluctuations.
Please be sure to include your entire address (including ZIP code) on your account prior to submitting your order.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 22:08:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 16 May 2015 03:38:53 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>11</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>★ CURRENT SALE: 8%! List price reflects discount
★ Condition: Brand new in shrink wrap
☆ Same as:
http://amzn.to/1amQIYb
——————
★ Shipping Information
Shipping: $5.75 Expedited
No combined shipping discounts
No international shipping
——————
★ Sales Tax
Sales Tax collected for the following states: AZ, CA, CT, FL, GA, IL, IN, KS, MD, MA, MN, NV, NJ, NY, NC, ND, PA, TN, TX, VA, WA, WV, WI
——————
★ Accepted Payment Methods:
☆ Same Day - One Day Processing:
* Debit Card (Visa _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; MC)
* Google Wallet
* Venmo
* Bitcoin
☆ Extra 2-5 Day Processing:
* Verified Paypal
Non-payment will result in order cancellation. Please pay promptly within 24 hours following order confirmation to prevent cancellation. Price fluctuations may cause order cancellation. Prompt payment will help prevent cancellation due to fluctuations.
Please be sure to include your entire address (including ZIP code) on your account prior to submitting your order.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 01:01:21 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 00:32:08 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>15.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Bezier Games (BEZONDB)
One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak is a fast game for 3-7 players in which everyone gets a hidden role, each with a special ability. (No plain _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;villagers_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; here!) In the course of a single morning, your village will decide who among them is a werewolf...because all it takes is finding one werewolf to win! Daybreak includes eleven new roles, and it can be played on its own or combined with the original One Night Ultimate Werewolf; when combined, you can have up to ten players in a single game. This game can be combined with One Night Ultimate Werewolf.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 22:08:18 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 18:04:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>11.25</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>★ CURRENT SALE: ~10%! List price reflects discount
★ Condition: Brand new in shrink wrap
☆ Same as:
http://amzn.to/1amQIYb
——————
★ Shipping Information
Shipping: $5.75 Expedited (US ONLY)
No combined shipping discounts
No international shipping
——————
★ Sales Tax
Sales Tax collected for the following states: AZ, CA, CT, FL, GA, IL, IN, KS, MD, MA, MN, NV, NJ, NY, NC, ND, PA, TN, TX, VA, WA, WV, WI
——————
★ Accepted Payment Methods:
☆ Same Day - One Day Processing:
* Debit Card (Visa _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_amp; MC)
* Google Wallet
* Venmo
* Bitcoin
☆ Extra 2-5 Day Processing:
* Verified Paypal
Non-payment will result in order cancellation. Please pay promptly within 24 hours following order confirmation to prevent cancellation. Price fluctuations may cause order cancellation. Prompt payment will help prevent cancellation due to fluctuations.
Please be sure to include your entire address (including ZIP code) on your account prior to submitting your order.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 20:29:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:28:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>14</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 05:06:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 13:55:25 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 10:22:17 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 02:58:59 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>22.5</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Shrinkwrapped and in stock
Language: English
Within The Netherlands € 4,- per shipment to a Kiala service point near you or € 6,75 per shipment for delivery at your doorstep.
Shipment to Belgium by Kiala is € 7,50.
Payment is possible by bank transfer or Paypal (costs +3%)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 20:29:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 10:19:03 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>16.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 17:04:50 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 20:28:40 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>8</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>For Wardsman - Flat Rate Auction
Payment via PayPal, Amazon gift card or cash on delivery (local pickup).</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 10:57:06 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:18:15 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>16.99</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 09 May 2016 17:58:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 09 May 2016 18:55:18 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>20</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/208301/item/4622644#4622644]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;Origins Virtual Flea Market 2016_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 21:39:32 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 22:34:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5.75</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Like new copy of One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak + One Night Ultimate Werewolf (2014 release).
Box and components are in mint condition. Components punched but not played.
No box for One Night Ultimate Werewolf. All components in the One Night Ultimate Werewolf Daybreak box.
Shipping via USPS Priority Flat Rate Envelope.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 12:15:34 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 16:17:23 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Reserved for auction winner (Fuwjax)</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 19:40:11 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 19:45:56 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='EUR'>10</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>This sale is for the PLAYER MAT and has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/211885/item/4917099#4917099]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;The Essen 2016 no-shipping auction list. Post your own items for sale!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 16:17:45 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 17:02:42 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>9</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/220121/item/5134061#5134061]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;AUCTION - Games for cheap! Clearing the shelves! 97213 local pick up and worldwide shipping too!_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
Shipping $5.00
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 05:53:12 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 04:15:55 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>14.94</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes></notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 05:05:40 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 13:12:30 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>7</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>For purchase by Gordon only.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 21:52:35 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 18:00:22 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='GBP'>13</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>Opened, punched and sorted but never played. The only thing missing is the shrink wrap! 
I am also selling 1 copy of the original base game (listed separately) for which shipping can be combined at no extra cost.
Pet and smoke free home.
Shipping in the UK will be £2.80 or you can collect from Hove area.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 20:23:56 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 09:27:52 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>10</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>Sealed</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 03:17:22 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:11:50 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>Shipping costs will be calculated and added to the purchase price
For atraangelis.</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:43:48 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Tue, 22 May 2018 21:59:10 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>2</price>
    <condition>likenew</condition>
    <notes>This sale has been auto-generated for the auction: [geekurl=/geeklist/241436/item/6158004#6158004]Item for Geeklist _T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot;cheap Bundle Auction - 19 games available - must buy 4+ - US only from 12054_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_quot; [/geekurl]
Please do not purchase if you didn_T_E_M_P_T_A_G_#039;t win this auction.
</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 04:48:38 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 10:06:54 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>12</price>
    <condition>new</condition>
    <notes>FREE SHIPPING</notes>
   </listing>
      <listing>
    <listdate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 19:48:15 +0000</listdate>
    <saledate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 22:11:46 +0000</saledate>
    <price currency='USD'>5</price>
    <condition>verygood</condition>
    <notes>DO NOT BUY - listing indicates a local purchase</notes>
   </listing>
     </marketplacehistory>   
  
    
  </boardgame>
 </boardgames>
